<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Child Safety Seat Recalls</title>
    <link>http://www-odi.nhtsa.dot.gov/</link>
    <description>The Office of Defects Investigation (ODI) is an office within the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA). ODI conducts defect investigations and administers safety recalls to support the NHTSA&apos;s mission to improve safety on our Nation&apos;s highways. NHTSA is authorized to order manufacturers to recall and repair child_seat or items of motor vehicle equipment when ODI investigations indicate that they contain serious safety defects in their design, construction, or performance. ODI also monitors the adequacy of manufacturers&apos; recall campaigns. Before initiating an investigation, ODI carefully reviews the body of consumer complaints and other available data to determine whether a defect trend may exist.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>TUE, 25 SEP 2018 05:59:52 EST</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <title>www-odi.nhtsa.dot.gov</title>
      <url>http://www-odi.nhtsa.dot.gov/images/NHTSA_Logo2.gif</url>
      <link>http://www-odi.nhtsa.dot.gov/recalls</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>HARMONY  ( 18C001000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: APR 17, 2018 Harmony Juvenile Products (Harmony) is recalling certain Harmony Big Boost Deluxe booster seats.  In the event of a crash, the seat belt may cause excessive force to be applied to the restrained child...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=18C001000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 25 SEP 2018 05:59:52 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">HARMONY  ( 18C001000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIONO  ( 17C003000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: SEP 14, 2017 Diono is recalling certain Radian R100, Radian R120, Radian RXT, Olympia, Pacifica, and Rainier convertible and booster car seats.  When the seat is installed in the forward facing position and secure...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=17C003000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 25 SEP 2018 05:59:52 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DIONO  ( 17C003000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRITAX  ( 17C002000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: JUN 15, 2017 Britax Child Safety, Inc. (Britax) is recalling certain  B-Safe 35, B-Safe 35 Travel Systems, B-Safe 35 Elite, B-Safe 35 Elite Travel Systems and BOB B-Safe rear-facing infant child safety seats, mode...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=17C002000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 25 SEP 2018 05:59:52 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">BRITAX  ( 17C002000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRACO  ( 17C001000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: MAY 10, 2017 Graco Children&apos;s Products Inc. (Graco) is recalling certain Graco My Ride 65 convertible child restraints, models 1871689, 1908152, 1813074, 1872691, 1853478, 1877535, 1813015, and 1794334.  In the ev...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=17C001000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 25 SEP 2018 05:59:52 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">GRACO  ( 17C001000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4MOMS  ( 16C009000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 30, 2016 Thorley Industries LLC d/b/a 4moms (4moms) is recalling certain 4moms Self Installing Rear-facing Infant Car Seats, model number 1032,  manufactured July 1, 2016, to October 31, 2016.  Due to a tight ...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=16C009000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 25 SEP 2018 05:59:52 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4MOMS  ( 16C009000 )</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

