<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls-old?field_rc_date_value%5Bmin%5D&amp;field_rc_date_value%5Bmax%5D&amp;field_rc_heading_value=&amp;field_rc_hazard_description_value=&amp;field_rc_manufactured_in_value=&amp;field_rc_manufacturers_value=&amp;field_rc_number_value=" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:fb="http://www.facebook.com/2008/fbml" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:article="http://ogp.me/ns/article#" xmlns:book="http://ogp.me/ns/book#" xmlns:profile="http://ogp.me/ns/profile#" xmlns:video="http://ogp.me/ns/video#" xmlns:product="http://ogp.me/ns/product#" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#">
  <channel>
    <title>Recall List</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls-old?field_rc_date_value%5Bmin%5D&amp;field_rc_date_value%5Bmax%5D&amp;field_rc_heading_value=&amp;field_rc_hazard_description_value=&amp;field_rc_manufactured_in_value=&amp;field_rc_manufacturers_value=&amp;field_rc_number_value=</link>
    <description></description>
    <language>en</language>
     <atom:link href="https://www.cpsc.gov/Newsroom/CPSC-RSS-Feed/Recalls-RSS" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
    <title>Michaels Recalls Tassel Keychain Mobile Power Banks Due to Fire and Burn Hazards </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/michaels-recalls-tassel-keychain-mobile-power-banks-due-to-fire-and-burn-hazards</link>
    <description>The lithium ion battery in the keychain’s mobile power bank can overheat, posing fire and burn hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>October 29, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Federal Cartridge Recalls Blackhawk Gun Holsters Due to Injury Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/federal-cartridge-recalls-blackhawk-gun-holsters-due-to-injury-hazard</link>
    <description>The holster design can change the position of the safety switch on the firearm without the user knowing it. When this occurs, if the trigger is pulled the gun could fire unexpectedly, posing an injury hazard to the user and bystander.</description>
     <pubDate>October 22, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Soft Play Recalls Spider Climb Playground Climbers Due to Fall Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/soft-play-recalls-spider-climb-playground-climbers-due-to-fall-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The climbing level platforms were designed too far apart, posing a fall hazard to children who can fall climbing from one level to the next.</description>
     <pubDate>October 18, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Carrier Recalls Carrier- and Bryant-Branded Heat Pumps Due to Fire Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/carrier-recalls-carrier-and-bryantbranded-heat-pumps-due-to-fire-hazard</link>
    <description>The fan motor on the heat pumps can fail, causing the units to overheat, posing a fire hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>October 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ronson Brand Tech Torch Recalled by Zippo Due to Fire Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/ronson-brand-tech-torch-recalled-by-zippo-due-to-fire-hazard</link>
    <description>The Ronson Tech Torch can continue to produce a flame after the activation trigger is released into the off position, posing a fire hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>October 8, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>IKEA Recalls Infant Bibs Due to Choking Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/ikea-recalls-infant-bibs-due-to-choking-hazard</link>
    <description>The snap on the bibs can detach, posing a choking hazard to young children.</description>
     <pubDate>October 8, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Kawasaki Motors USA Recalls Lawn Mower Engines Due to Burn and Fire Hazards (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/kawasaki-motors-usa-recalls-lawn-mower-engines-due-to-burn-and-fire-hazards-recall</link>
    <description>The fuel injector can leak excessive amounts of fuel into the engine, posing burn and fire hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>October 8, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Harbor Freight Tools Recalls Gordon Folding Knives Due to Laceration Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/harbor-freight-tools-recalls-gordon-folding-knives-due-to-laceration-hazard</link>
    <description>The locking mechanism can fail to engage on extension of the blade, posing a laceration hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>October 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>fluidfreeride Recalls Mercane WideWheel Electric Scooters Due to Fall and Injury Hazards (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/fluidfreeride-recalls-mercane-widewheel-electric-scooters-due-to-fall-and-injury</link>
    <description>The brake caliper can fail causing the rider to lose control and suffer serious bodily harm, posing fall and injury hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>October 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Fit For Life Recalls SPRI Ultra Heavy Resistance Bands Due to Injury Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/fit-for-life-recalls-spri-ultra-heavy-resistance-bands-due-to-injury-hazard</link>
    <description>The rubber resistance bands can separate from the handle and strike consumers, posing an injury hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>October 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>VIQUA Recalls Solenoid Valve Kits for UV Water Treatment Systems Due to Electrical Shock Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/viqua-recalls-solenoid-valve-kits-for-uv-water-treatment-systems-due-to-electrical</link>
    <description>Electrical current could leak from the solenoid valve, posing an electrical shock hazard to the user.</description>
     <pubDate>October 3, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Signature Hardware Recalls Bath Stools Due to Fall and Injury Hazards (Recall Alert)

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/signature-hardware-recalls-bath-stools-due-to-fall-and-injury-hazards-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The bath stools can break during use, posing fall and injury hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>October 3, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ridgewood Recalls Four-Drawer Dressers Due to Tip-Over and Entrapment Hazards

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/ridgewood-recalls-four-drawer-dressers-due-to-tip-over-and-entrapment-hazards</link>
    <description>The recalled dressers are unstable and can tip over if not anchored to the wall, posing serious tip-over and entrapment hazards that can result in death or injuries to children. Additionally, those models of dressers over 30 inches tall do not comply with the performance requirements of the U.S. voluntary industry standard (ASTM F2057-14).</description>
     <pubDate>October 3, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>E&amp;amp;E Recalls Bedroom Dressers Due to Tip-Over and Entrapment Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/e-e-recalls-bedroom-dressers-due-to-tip-over-and-entrapment-hazards</link>
    <description>The recalled dressers are unstable if they are not anchored to the wall, posing serious tip-over and entrapment hazards that can result in death or injuries to children. The dressers do not comply with the performance requirements of the U.S. voluntary industry standard (ASTM 2057-17).</description>
     <pubDate>October 3, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>DEWALT Recalls Utility Bars Due to Injury Hazard

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/dewalt-recalls-utility-bars-due-to-injury-hazard</link>
    <description>The utility bar can break while being used for prying, posing an injury hazard to the user.</description>
     <pubDate>September 26, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>ASKO Recalls Dishwashers Due to Fire Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/asko-recalls-dishwashers-due-to-fire-hazard</link>
    <description>The dishwasher power cord can overheat, posing a fire hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>September 26, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Home Meridian Recalls Three-Drawer Chests Due to Tip-Over and Entrapment Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/home-meridian-recalls-three-drawer-chests-due-to-tip-over-and-entrapment-hazards</link>
    <description>The recalled chests are unstable if they are not anchored to the wall, posing serious tip-over and entrapment hazards that can result in death or injuries to children.&amp;nbsp; The chests do not comply with the performance requirements of the U.S. voluntary industry standard (ASTM F2057-17).</description>
     <pubDate>September 24, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Chronicle Recalls Power Armor Collectible Helmets Due to Risk of Mold Exposure (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/chronicle-recalls-power-armor-collectible-helmets-due-to-risk-of-mold-exposure-recall</link>
    <description>Mold can be present on the fabric insert inside the helmet, posing a risk of respiratory or other infections in individuals with compromised immune systems, damaged lungs or an allergy to mold.</description>
     <pubDate>September 19, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Exploding Kittens Recalls Safety Goggles Sold with Extreme Edition Dodgeball Game Sets Due to Laceration Hazard; Sold Exclusively on Kickstarter (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/exploding-kittens-recalls-safety-goggles-sold-with-extreme-edition-dodgeball-game-sets</link>
    <description>The goggles contain glass lenses, posing a laceration hazard if shattered. &amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>September 19, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Kichler Lighting Recalls Pendant Lights Due to Fire Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/kichler-lighting-recalls-pendant-lights-due-to-fire-hazard</link>
    <description>The light sockets can overheat, melt, or catch fire, posing a fire hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>September 18, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Humanscale Recalls QuickStand Lite Workstations Due to Injury Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/humanscale-recalls-quickstand-lite-workstations-due-to-injury-hazard</link>
    <description>The recalled workstation’s arm can break and cause the workstation to fall, posing a risk of injury.</description>
     <pubDate>September 17, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Healing Solutions Recalls Essential Oils Due to Failure to Meet Child Resistant Packaging Requirements; Risk of Poisoning</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/healing-solutions-recalls-essential-oils-due-to-failure-to-meet-child-resistant</link>
    <description>The bottles are not child resistant as required by the Poison Prevention Packaging Act, posing a poisoning risk if the contents are swallowed by young children.</description>
     <pubDate>September 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Air Rifles Recalled by DIANA Can Unexpectedly Discharge; Risk of Serious Injury and Death </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/air-rifles-recalled-by-diana-can-unexpectedly-discharge-risk-of-serious-injury-and</link>
    <description>The air rifle can unexpectedly discharge even if the safety is engaged. This can result in a serious injury or death.</description>
     <pubDate>September 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ragdoll &amp;amp; Rockets Recalls Children’s Loungewear Due to Violation of Federal Flammability Standard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/ragdoll-rockets-recalls-childrens-loungewear-due-to-violation-of-federal-flammability</link>
    <description>The children’s loungewear fails to meet the flammability standards for children’s sleepwear, posing a risk of burn injuries to children.</description>
     <pubDate>September 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>MW Company Recalls MOMO Quick Release Steering Wheel Adapters Due to Crash Hazard; Risk of Serious Injury and Death</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/mw-company-recalls-momo-quick-release-steering-wheel-adapters-due-to-crash-hazard-risk</link>
    <description>The steering wheel adapter’s quick release can activate inadvertently and cause the race car’s steering wheel to suddenly detach from its steering column while the vehicle is in motion, rendering the vehicle impossible to steer and posing a crash hazard and risk of serious injury and death to the driver.</description>
     <pubDate>September 5, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Walker Edison Furniture Recalls Children’s Bunk Beds Due to Fall and Injury Hazards (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/walker-edison-furniture-recallschildrens-bunk-beds-due-to-fall-and-injury-hazards</link>
    <description>The bunk bed’s support boards can break, posing fall and injury hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>September 5, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>STIHL PolyCut Mowing Heads Recalled Due to Injury Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/stihl-polycut-mowing-heads-recalled-due-to-injury-hazard</link>
    <description>The bolts connecting the plastic blades and holding the mowing head together can come loose and the mowing head can come apart, posing a risk of injury to the user or bystanders.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>September 5, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Kawasaki USA Recalls Recreational Off-Highway Vehicles Due to Crash and Injury Hazards (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/kawasaki-usa-recalls-recreational-offhighway-vehicles-due-to-crash-and-injury-hazards</link>
    <description>Incorrect joint assembly can cause steering control loss, posing crash and injury hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>September 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>John Deere Recalls Frontier Grooming Mowers Due to Entanglement Injury Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/john-deere-recalls-frontier-grooming-mowers-due-to-entanglement-injury-hazard-recall</link>
    <description>Incorrect assembly of the mower’s drivelines can prevent the safety shield from spinning independently, posing an entanglement injury hazard to consumers.</description>
     <pubDate>September 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Artizen Oils Recalls Essential Oils Due to Failure to Meet Child Resistant Packaging Requirements, Risk of Poisoning</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/artizen-oils-recalls-essential-oils-due-to-failure-to-meet-child-resistant-packaging</link>
    <description>The bottles are not child resistant as required by the Poison Prevention Packaging Act, posing a poisoning risk if the contents are swallowed by young children.</description>
     <pubDate>September 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gator Utility Vehicles Recalled by John Deere Due to Crash Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/gator-utility-vehicles-recalled-by-john-deere-due-to-crash-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The plastic sheathing on the throttle cable can melt due to improper routing, causing the throttle to stick. This could result in the operator not being able to stop the vehicle, posing a crash hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>September 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Beaufort Bonnet Company Recalls Handmade Knit Dolls Due to Injury Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/the-beaufort-bonnet-company-recalls-handmade-knit-dolls-due-to-injury-hazard</link>
    <description>A sewing needle was discovered in the stuffing of one of the handmade knit dolls, posing a puncture injury hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>September 3, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>GreatCall Recalls Lively Mobile Plus Emergency Alert Device Due to Risk of Call Button Failing in an Emergency (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/greatcall-recalls-lively-mobile-plus-emergency-alert-device-due-to-risk-of-call-button</link>
    <description>The call button can fail when pushed by the consumer in an emergency.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>August 30, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>RH Recalls Turkish Robes Due to Violation of Federal Flammability Standard </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/rh-recalls-turkish-robes-due-to-violation-of-federal-flammability-standard</link>
    <description>The Turkish robes fail to meet the flammability standards for clothing textiles, posing a risk of burn injuries to consumers.</description>
     <pubDate>August 30, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>RH Recalls Children’s Chairs and Stools Due to Violation of Federal Lead Paint Ban</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/rh-recalls-childrens-chairs-and-stools-due-to-violation-of-federal-lead-paint-ban</link>
    <description>Paint on the chairs and stools contain levels of lead that exceed the federal lead paint ban. Lead is toxic if ingested by young children and can cause adverse health effects.</description>
     <pubDate>August 30, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Rite Aid Recalls Folding Patio Chairs Due to Fall Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/rite-aid-recalls-folding-patio-chairs-due-to-fall-hazard</link>
    <description>The chair frame can bend causing the user to fall, posing a risk of injury.</description>
     <pubDate>August 29, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Pearhead Recalls Ubbi Connecting Bath Toys Due To Choking Hazard </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/pearhead-recalls-ubbi-connecting-bath-toys-due-to-choking-hazard</link>
    <description>The recalled toys can break and create a sharp point, posing laceration and choking hazards to young children.</description>
     <pubDate>August 29, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Sandoz Recalls Losartan Potassium and Ezetimibe Prescription Drug Bottles Due to Failure to Meet Child-Resistant Closure Requirements</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/sandoz-recalls-losartan-potassium-and-ezetimibe-prescription-drug-bottles-due-to</link>
    <description>The prescription drug packaging is not child resistant as required by the Poison Prevention Packaging Act, posing a poisoning risk if swallowed by children.</description>
     <pubDate>August 29, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Decathlon USA Recalls Carabiners Due to Risk of Serious Injury or Death  </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/decathlon-usa-recalls-carabiners-due-to-risk-of-serious-injury-or-death</link>
    <description>Incorrect assembly can cause the carabiner to unlock while in use, posing a risk of serious injury or death to the user.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>August 29, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Whirlpool Recalls Glass Cooktops with Touch Controls Due to Burn and Fire Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/whirlpool-recalls-glass-cooktops-with-touch-controls-due-to-burn-and-fire-hazards</link>
    <description>The recalled cooktop surface elements can turn on by themselves, posing burn and fire hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>August 28, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
