<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls-old?field_rc_date_value%5Bmin%5D&amp;field_rc_date_value%5Bmax%5D&amp;field_rc_heading_value=&amp;field_rc_hazard_description_value=&amp;field_rc_manufactured_in_value=&amp;field_rc_manufacturers_value=&amp;field_rc_number_value=" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:fb="http://www.facebook.com/2008/fbml" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:article="http://ogp.me/ns/article#" xmlns:book="http://ogp.me/ns/book#" xmlns:profile="http://ogp.me/ns/profile#" xmlns:video="http://ogp.me/ns/video#" xmlns:product="http://ogp.me/ns/product#" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#">
  <channel>
    <title>Recall List</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls-old?field_rc_date_value%5Bmin%5D&amp;field_rc_date_value%5Bmax%5D&amp;field_rc_heading_value=&amp;field_rc_hazard_description_value=&amp;field_rc_manufactured_in_value=&amp;field_rc_manufacturers_value=&amp;field_rc_number_value=</link>
    <description></description>
    <language>en</language>
     <atom:link href="https://www.cpsc.gov/Newsroom/CPSC-RSS-Feed/Recalls-RSS" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
    <title>Air Rifles Recalled by DIANA Can Unexpectedly Discharge; Risk of Serious Injury and Death </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/air-rifles-recalled-by-diana-can-unexpectedly-discharge-risk-of-serious-injury-and</link>
    <description>The air rifle can unexpectedly discharge even if the safety is engaged. This can result in a serious injury or death.</description>
     <pubDate>September 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Ragdoll &amp;amp; Rockets Recalls Children’s Loungewear Due to Violation of Federal Flammability Standard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/ragdoll-rockets-recalls-childrens-loungewear-due-to-violation-of-federal-flammability</link>
    <description>The children’s loungewear fails to meet the flammability standards for children’s sleepwear, posing a risk of burn injuries to children.</description>
     <pubDate>September 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>MW Company Recalls MOMO Quick Release Steering Wheel Adapters Due to Crash Hazard; Risk of Serious Injury and Death</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/mw-company-recalls-momo-quick-release-steering-wheel-adapters-due-to-crash-hazard-risk</link>
    <description>The steering wheel adapter’s quick release can activate inadvertently and cause the race car’s steering wheel to suddenly detach from its steering column while the vehicle is in motion, rendering the vehicle impossible to steer and posing a crash hazard and risk of serious injury and death to the driver.</description>
     <pubDate>September 5, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Walker Edison Furniture Recalls Children’s Bunk Beds Due to Fall and Injury Hazards (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/walker-edison-furniture-recallschildrens-bunk-beds-due-to-fall-and-injury-hazards</link>
    <description>The bunk bed’s support boards can break, posing fall and injury hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>September 5, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>STIHL PolyCut Mowing Heads Recalled Due to Injury Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/stihl-polycut-mowing-heads-recalled-due-to-injury-hazard</link>
    <description>The bolts connecting the plastic blades and holding the mowing head together can come loose and the mowing head can come apart, posing a risk of injury to the user or bystanders.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>September 5, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Kawasaki USA Recalls Recreational Off-Highway Vehicles Due to Crash and Injury Hazards (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/kawasaki-usa-recalls-recreational-offhighway-vehicles-due-to-crash-and-injury-hazards</link>
    <description>Incorrect joint assembly can cause steering control loss, posing crash and injury hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>September 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>John Deere Recalls Frontier Grooming Mowers Due to Entanglement Injury Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/john-deere-recalls-frontier-grooming-mowers-due-to-entanglement-injury-hazard-recall</link>
    <description>Incorrect assembly of the mower’s drivelines can prevent the safety shield from spinning independently, posing an entanglement injury hazard to consumers.</description>
     <pubDate>September 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Artizen Oils Recalls Essential Oils Due to Failure to Meet Child Resistant Packaging Requirements, Risk of Poisoning</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/artizen-oils-recalls-essential-oils-due-to-failure-to-meet-child-resistant-packaging</link>
    <description>The bottles are not child resistant as required by the Poison Prevention Packaging Act, posing a poisoning risk if the contents are swallowed by young children.</description>
     <pubDate>September 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gator Utility Vehicles Recalled by John Deere Due to Crash Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/gator-utility-vehicles-recalled-by-john-deere-due-to-crash-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The plastic sheathing on the throttle cable can melt due to improper routing, causing the throttle to stick. This could result in the operator not being able to stop the vehicle, posing a crash hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>September 4, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Beaufort Bonnet Company Recalls Handmade Knit Dolls Due to Injury Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/the-beaufort-bonnet-company-recalls-handmade-knit-dolls-due-to-injury-hazard</link>
    <description>A sewing needle was discovered in the stuffing of one of the handmade knit dolls, posing a puncture injury hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>September 3, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>GreatCall Recalls Lively Mobile Plus Emergency Alert Device Due to Risk of Call Button Failing in an Emergency (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/greatcall-recalls-lively-mobile-plus-emergency-alert-device-due-to-risk-of-call-button</link>
    <description>The call button can fail when pushed by the consumer in an emergency.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>August 30, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>RH Recalls Turkish Robes Due to Violation of Federal Flammability Standard </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/rh-recalls-turkish-robes-due-to-violation-of-federal-flammability-standard</link>
    <description>The Turkish robes fail to meet the flammability standards for clothing textiles, posing a risk of burn injuries to consumers.</description>
     <pubDate>August 30, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>RH Recalls Children’s Chairs and Stools Due to Violation of Federal Lead Paint Ban</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/rh-recalls-childrens-chairs-and-stools-due-to-violation-of-federal-lead-paint-ban</link>
    <description>Paint on the chairs and stools contain levels of lead that exceed the federal lead paint ban. Lead is toxic if ingested by young children and can cause adverse health effects.</description>
     <pubDate>August 30, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Rite Aid Recalls Folding Patio Chairs Due to Fall Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/rite-aid-recalls-folding-patio-chairs-due-to-fall-hazard</link>
    <description>The chair frame can bend causing the user to fall, posing a risk of injury.</description>
     <pubDate>August 29, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Pearhead Recalls Ubbi Connecting Bath Toys Due To Choking Hazard </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/pearhead-recalls-ubbi-connecting-bath-toys-due-to-choking-hazard</link>
    <description>The recalled toys can break and create a sharp point, posing laceration and choking hazards to young children.</description>
     <pubDate>August 29, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Sandoz Recalls Losartan Potassium and Ezetimibe Prescription Drug Bottles Due to Failure to Meet Child-Resistant Closure Requirements</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/sandoz-recalls-losartan-potassium-and-ezetimibe-prescription-drug-bottles-due-to</link>
    <description>The prescription drug packaging is not child resistant as required by the Poison Prevention Packaging Act, posing a poisoning risk if swallowed by children.</description>
     <pubDate>August 29, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Decathlon USA Recalls Carabiners Due to Risk of Serious Injury or Death  </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/decathlon-usa-recalls-carabiners-due-to-risk-of-serious-injury-or-death</link>
    <description>Incorrect assembly can cause the carabiner to unlock while in use, posing a risk of serious injury or death to the user.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>August 29, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Whirlpool Recalls Glass Cooktops with Touch Controls Due to Burn and Fire Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/whirlpool-recalls-glass-cooktops-with-touch-controls-due-to-burn-and-fire-hazards</link>
    <description>The recalled cooktop surface elements can turn on by themselves, posing burn and fire hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>August 28, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Yamaha Recalls Golf Cars, Personal Transportation and Specialty Vehicles Due to Fire Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/yamaha-recalls-golf-cars-personal-transportation-and-specialty-vehicles-due-to-fire</link>
    <description>The module that regulates power to the vehicle’s USB ports can overheat and melt, posing a fire hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>August 28, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Kirkland’s Recalls Chests of Drawers Due to Tip-Over and Entrapment Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/kirklands-recalls-chests-of-drawers-due-to-tip-over-and-entrapment-hazards</link>
    <description>The recalled chests are unstable if they are not anchored to the wall, posing serious tip-over and entrapment hazards that can result in death or injuries to children. The dressers do not comply with the performance requirements of the U.S. voluntary industry standard (ASTM 2057-17).</description>
     <pubDate>August 28, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Contigo Recalls 5.7 Million Kids Water Bottles Due to Choking Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/contigo-recalls-57-million-kids-water-bottles-due-to-choking-hazard</link>
    <description>The water bottle’s clear silicone spout can detach, posing a choking hazard to children.</description>
     <pubDate>August 27, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>At Home Recalls Shag Rugs Due to Violation of Federal Flammability Standard; Fire Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/at-home-recalls-shag-rugs-due-to-violation-of-federal-flammability-standard-fire-hazard</link>
    <description>The recalled large shag rugs fail to meet the federal flammability standard for carpets and rugs, posing a fire hazard. The small shag rugs fail to meet federal labeling requirements. Small rugs are not required to meet the federal flammability standard; however, they are required to be permanently labeled with the following statement: “FLAMMABLE (FAILS U.S. DEPARTMENT OF COMMERCE STANDARD FF 2-70): SHOULD NOT BE USED NEAR SOURCES OF IGNITION.”</description>
     <pubDate>August 27, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Happy Plugs Recalls Wireless Headphones Due to Burn Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/happy-plugs-recalls-wireless-headphones-due-to-burn-hazard</link>
    <description>The micro-USB charging cable packaged with Happy Plugs wireless headphones can cause the headphones to overheat, posing a burn hazard to consumers.</description>
     <pubDate>August 27, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>BRP Recalls Snowmobiles Due to Fire Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/brp-recalls-snowmobiles-due-to-fire-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The vehicle can have a fuel leak at the fuel injector, posing a fire hazard.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>August 26, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Piping Rock Health Products Recalls Wintergreen Essential Oil Due to Failure to Meet Child Resistant Closure Requirements; Risk of Poisoning (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/piping-rock-health-products-recalls-wintergreen-essential-oil-due-to-failure-to-meet</link>
    <description>The bottles are not child resistant as required by the Poison Prevention Packaging Act, posing a poisoning risk if the contents are swallowed by young children.</description>
     <pubDate>August 22, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Norwex Recalls Rubber Brooms Due to Laceration Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/norwex-recalls-rubber-brooms-due-to-laceration-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The broom handles can break in half, exposing a metal inner rim, posing a laceration hazard to the user.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>August 22, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Crate and Barrel Recalls Push Walkers Due to Choking and Laceration Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/crate-and-barrel-recalls-push-walkers-due-to-choking-and-laceration-hazards</link>
    <description>Walkers can be damaged over time exposing sharp points and small parts, posing choking and laceration hazards to small children.</description>
     <pubDate>August 20, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>SAMpark Recalls Children’s Pajamas Due to Violation of Federal Flammability Standard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/sampark-recalls-childrens-pajamas-due-to-violation-of-federal-flammability-standard</link>
    <description>The pajamas fail to meet the federal flammability standard for children’s sleepwear that requires sleepwear to be either snug-fitting or flame resistant, posing a risk of burn injuries to children.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>August 20, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Southwire Recalls Electrical Outlet Boxes Due to Fire Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/southwire-recalls-electrical-outlet-boxes-due-to-fire-hazard</link>
    <description>The electrical receptacles can overheat when in use, posing a fire hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>August 20, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Club Car Recalls Gas Golf and Transport Vehicles Due to Fire and Burn Hazards (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/club-car-recalls-gas-golf-and-transport-vehicles-due-to-fire-and-burn-hazards-recall</link>
    <description>Fuel can leak from an improperly-routed fuel line, posing fire and burn hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>August 19, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Club Car Recalls Gas Utility and Transport Vehicles Due to Risk of Fuel Leak and Fire Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/club-car-recalls-gas-utility-and-transport-vehicles-due-to-risk-of-fuel-leak-and-fire</link>
    <description>Under continuous operations with low speed idling periods and a full gas tank, the fuel vent can allow fuel to leak, posing a fire hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>August 19, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>SSR Motorsports Recalls Off‐Highway Competition Motorcycles Due to Crash and Injury Hazards (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/ssr-motorsports-recalls-off-highway-competition-motorcycles-due-to-crash-and-injury</link>
    <description>The vehicle’s front fork assembly can fail during use, causing the rider to lose control, and result in a crash hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>August 15, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>SunSetter Recalls Vinyl Covers for Motorized Awnings Due to Impact and Fall Hazards; One Death Reported (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/sunsetter-recalls-vinyl-covers-for-motorized-awnings-due-to-impact-and-fall-hazards-one</link>
    <description>If a powered awning is activated while the cover is secured with bungee tie-downs, when the cover is removed, the awning can open unexpectedly with enough force to strike a consumer standing in the awning’s path, causing them to fall and suffer death or serious injury.</description>
     <pubDate>August 13, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Seattle Manufacturing Corporation Recalls Ice Axes Due to Serious Injury and Fall Hazards

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/seattle-manufacturing-corporation-recalls-ice-axes-due-to-serious-injury-and-fall</link>
    <description>The spike and/or head of the ice axe can detach from the handle during use, posing serious injury and fall hazards to the climber.</description>
     <pubDate>August 7, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>BRP Expands Recall of Snowmobiles Due to Fuel Leak and Fire Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/brp-expands-recall-of-snowmobiles-due-to-fuel-leak-and-fire-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The vehicle’s fuel delivery system can leak fuel, posing a fire hazard. &amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>August 6, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Super Jumper Recalls Trampolines Due to Fall and Injury Hazards </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/super-jumper-recalls-trampolines-due-to-fall-and-injury-hazards</link>
    <description>The welds on the metal railings (legs) can fail, posing fall and injury hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>August 1, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>London Bridge Recalls Sock and Wrist Rattle Sets Due to Choking Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/london-bridge-recalls-sock-and-wrist-rattle-sets-due-to-choking-hazard</link>
    <description>Rattles sewn inside the socks and wristbands can detach, posing a choking hazard to young children.</description>
     <pubDate>July 31, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Dorel Juvenile Group USA Recalls Inclined Sleepers Due to Safety Concerns About Inclined Sleep Products</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/dorel-juvenile-group-usa-recalls-inclined-sleepers-due-to-safety-concerns-about</link>
    <description>Infant fatalities have been reported while using other inclined sleep products, after the infants rolled from their back to their stomach or side while unrestrained, or under other circumstances.</description>
     <pubDate>July 31, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Tristar Products Recalls Magnetic Trivets Due to Magnet Ingestion Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/tristar-products-recalls-magnetic-trivets-due-to-magnet-ingestion-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>Magnets can detach from the trivets, posing an ingestion hazard to children.When two or more magnets are swallowed, they can link together inside the intestines and clamp onto body tissues, causing intestinal obstructions, perforations, sepsis and death. Internal injury from magnets can pose serious lifelong health effects.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>July 30, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Spansive Recalls Wireless Phone Chargers Due To Burn Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/spansive-recalls-wireless-phone-chargers-due-to-burn-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>Metallic accessories attached to phones placed on the chargers can overheat while phones charge, posing a burn hazard to users</description>
     <pubDate>July 26, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
