<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls-old?field_rc_date_value%5Bmin%5D&amp;field_rc_date_value%5Bmax%5D&amp;field_rc_heading_value=&amp;field_rc_hazard_description_value=&amp;field_rc_manufactured_in_value=&amp;field_rc_manufacturers_value=&amp;field_rc_number_value=" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:fb="http://www.facebook.com/2008/fbml" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:article="http://ogp.me/ns/article#" xmlns:book="http://ogp.me/ns/book#" xmlns:profile="http://ogp.me/ns/profile#" xmlns:video="http://ogp.me/ns/video#" xmlns:product="http://ogp.me/ns/product#" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#">
  <channel>
    <title>Recall List</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls-old?field_rc_date_value%5Bmin%5D&amp;field_rc_date_value%5Bmax%5D&amp;field_rc_heading_value=&amp;field_rc_hazard_description_value=&amp;field_rc_manufactured_in_value=&amp;field_rc_manufacturers_value=&amp;field_rc_number_value=</link>
    <description></description>
    <language>en</language>
     <atom:link href="https://www.cpsc.gov/Newsroom/CPSC-RSS-Feed/Recalls-RSS" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
    <title>SunSetter Recalls Vinyl Covers for Motorized Awnings Due to Impact and Fall Hazards; One Death Reported (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/sunsetter-recalls-vinyl-covers-for-motorized-awnings-due-to-impact-and-fall-hazards-one</link>
    <description>If a powered awning is activated while the cover is secured with bungee tie-downs, when the cover is removed, the awning can open unexpectedly with enough force to strike a consumer standing in the awning’s path, causing them to fall and suffer death or serious injury.</description>
     <pubDate>August 13, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Seattle Manufacturing Corporation Recalls Ice Axes Due to Serious Injury and Fall Hazards

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/seattle-manufacturing-corporation-recalls-ice-axes-due-to-serious-injury-and-fall</link>
    <description>The spike and/or head of the ice axe can detach from the handle during use, posing serious injury and fall hazards to the climber.</description>
     <pubDate>August 7, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>BRP Expands Recall of Snowmobiles Due to Fuel Leak and Fire Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/brp-expands-recall-of-snowmobiles-due-to-fuel-leak-and-fire-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The vehicle’s fuel delivery system can leak fuel, posing a fire hazard. &amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>August 6, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Super Jumper Recalls Trampolines Due to Fall and Injury Hazards </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/super-jumper-recalls-trampolines-due-to-fall-and-injury-hazards</link>
    <description>The welds on the metal railings (legs) can fail, posing fall and injury hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>August 1, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>London Bridge Recalls Sock and Wrist Rattle Sets Due to Choking Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/london-bridge-recalls-sock-and-wrist-rattle-sets-due-to-choking-hazard</link>
    <description>Rattles sewn inside the socks and wristbands can detach, posing a choking hazard to young children.</description>
     <pubDate>July 31, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Dorel Juvenile Group USA Recalls Inclined Sleepers Due to Safety Concerns About Inclined Sleep Products</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/dorel-juvenile-group-usa-recalls-inclined-sleepers-due-to-safety-concerns-about</link>
    <description>Infant fatalities have been reported while using other inclined sleep products, after the infants rolled from their back to their stomach or side while unrestrained, or under other circumstances.</description>
     <pubDate>July 31, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Tristar Products Recalls Magnetic Trivets Due to Magnet Ingestion Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/tristar-products-recalls-magnetic-trivets-due-to-magnet-ingestion-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>Magnets can detach from the trivets, posing an ingestion hazard to children.When two or more magnets are swallowed, they can link together inside the intestines and clamp onto body tissues, causing intestinal obstructions, perforations, sepsis and death. Internal injury from magnets can pose serious lifelong health effects.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>July 30, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Spansive Recalls Wireless Phone Chargers Due To Burn Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/spansive-recalls-wireless-phone-chargers-due-to-burn-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>Metallic accessories attached to phones placed on the chargers can overheat while phones charge, posing a burn hazard to users</description>
     <pubDate>July 26, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Britax Recalls Modified Thru-Bolt Axles for Use with BOB Jogging Strollers Distributed Through the BOB Information Campaign Due to Fall and Injury Hazards (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/britax-recalls-modified-thru-bolt-axles-for-use-with-bob-jogging-strollers-distributed</link>
    <description>The modified thru-bolt on the front wheel can fracture, allowing the wheel to detach from the stroller, posing fall and injury hazards to children in the stroller and adults operating the stroller.</description>
     <pubDate>July 25, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>H&amp;amp;M Recalls Children’s Pajamas Due to Violation of Federal Flammability Standard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/hm-recalls-childrens-pajamas-due-to-violation-of-federal-flammability-standard</link>
    <description>The children’s pajama sets fail to meet the flammability standard for children’s sleepwear, posing a risk of burn injuries to children.</description>
     <pubDate>July 25, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Cycling Sports Group Recalls Cannondale CAADX Cyclocross Bicycles Due to Fall and Serious Injury Hazard; One Fatality Reported</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/cycling-sports-group-recalls-cannondale-caadx-cyclocross-bicycles-due-to-fall-and</link>
    <description>The fork can break, posing a fall hazard with the risk of death and serious injury.</description>
     <pubDate>July 25, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Stokke Recalls Infant Steps Bouncers Due to Fall Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/stokke-recalls-infant-steps-bouncers-due-to-fall-hazard</link>
    <description>The Stokke Steps Bouncer can detach from the Stokke Steps Chair, posing a fall hazard to the child in the Bouncer. &amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>July 25, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Porter Cable Table Saws Sold Exclusively at Lowe’s Stores Recalled Due to Fire Hazard; Made by Chang Type</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/porter-cable-table-saws-sold-exclusively-at-lowes-stores-recalled-due-to-fire-hazard</link>
    <description>The motor can overheat, creating a fire hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>July 24, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Trek Recalls Kickster Bikes Due to Fall Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/trek-recalls-kickster-bikes-due-to-fall-hazard</link>
    <description>The steer tube clamp on the bike can break, posing a fall hazard to children.</description>
     <pubDate>July 24, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Boppy Company Recalls Infant Head and Neck Support Accessories Due to Suffocation Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/the-boppy-company-recalls-infant-head-and-neck-support-accessories-due-to-suffocation</link>
    <description>The head support area can be overstuffed and cause the infant’s head to be tilted too far forward, posing a suffocation hazard</description>
     <pubDate>July 23, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Factory Direct Wholesale Recalls Folding Mattresses Due to Violation of Federal Mattress Flammability Standard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/factory-direct-wholesale-recalls-folding-mattresses-due-to-violation-of-federal</link>
    <description>The mattresses fail to meet the mandatory federal flammability standard for mattresses, posing a fire hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>July 18, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Bodum Recalls Toasters Due to Shock Hazard

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/bodum-recalls-toasters-due-to-shock-hazard</link>
    <description>The recalled toasters can leak electric current when operating at the maximum normal temperature, posing a shock hazard to consumers.</description>
     <pubDate>July 17, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Wintergreen Essential Oil Recalled by Epic Business Services Due to Failure to Meet Child Resistant Closure Requirement; Risk of Poisoning (Recall Alert) </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/wintergreen-essential-oil-recalled-by-epic-business-services-due-to-failure-to-meet</link>
    <description>The packaging is not child resistant as required by the Poison Prevention Packaging Act, posing a risk of poisoning to young children if they ingest it.</description>
     <pubDate>July 16, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>VIVO Recalls Speaker Wall Mounts Due to Fall and Injury Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/vivo-recalls-speaker-wall-mounts-due-to-fall-and-injury-hazards</link>
    <description>The ledge on the front of the speaker wall mount can loosen, allowing both the ledge and the speakers to fall, posing an injury hazard to bystanders</description>
     <pubDate>July 16, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>K2 Sports Recalls Inline Skates Due to Fall Hazard

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/k2-sports-recalls-inline-skates-due-to-fall-hazard</link>
    <description>The skate axle can become loose or a portion of the axle can sheer off during use resulting in a wheel separating from the skate’s frame, posing a fall hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>July 16, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Lifetime Brands Recalls Fitz and Floyd Nevaeh White Can Mugs Due to Burn and Laceration Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/lifetime-brands-recalls-fitz-and-floyd-nevaeh-white-can-mugs-due-to-burn-and-laceration</link>
    <description>The mugs can crack or break when used with or exposed to hot liquids, posing burn and laceration hazards. &amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>July 11, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Levolor Recalls Custom Cellular Shades Due to Strangulation Hazard (Recall Alert) </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/levolor-recalls-custom-cellular-shades-due-to-strangulation-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The pull cords are joined by a non-breakaway cord connector, which poses a strangulation hazard for small children. &amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>July 11, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Lidl Recalls Wooden Grasping Toys Due to Choking Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/lidl-recalls-wooden-grasping-toys-due-to-choking-hazard</link>
    <description>The wooden wheels can detach and release small parts, posing a choking hazard to young children.</description>
     <pubDate>July 11, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Office Depot Recalls Desks Due To Shock Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/office-depot-recalls-desks-due-to-shock-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The desk’s control box has an electrical issue resulting in reverse polarity, which could pose a shock hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>July 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Universal Security Instruments Recalls to Inspect Smoke Alarms Due to Risk of Failure to Alert Consumers to a Fire</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/universal-security-instruments-recalls-to-inspect-smoke-alarms-due-to-risk-of-failure</link>
    <description>The smoke alarms can have a misaligned internal switch causing the alarms to not activate properly, posing a risk of failure to alert consumers to a fire.</description>
     <pubDate>July 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Winco Fireworks Recalls Black Cat “Cat Mobiles” Due to Explosion, Burn and Projectile Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/winco-fireworks-recalls-black-cat-cat-mobiles-due-to-explosion-burn-and-projectile</link>
    <description>When ignited, the device can burst and spread sparks and pyrotechnic materials upward and outward instead of on the ground as intended, posing explosion, burn and projectile hazards to bystanders.</description>
     <pubDate>July 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Bose Recalls EdgeMax® and FreeSpace® Loudspeakers Due to Injury Hazard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/bose-recalls-edgemax-and-freespace-loudspeakers-due-to-injury-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The loudspeaker’s mounting components can break causing the speakers to dislodge and fall from its installed location, posing an injury hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>July 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Everbilt Door Pulls Recalled Due to Laceration Hazard; Sold Exclusively at Home Depot; Made by Wellsco International Group

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/everbilt-door-pulls-recalled-due-to-laceration-hazard-sold-exclusively-at-home-depot</link>
    <description>The door pulls can have sharp edges on the back, posing a laceration hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>July 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Custom Molded Products Recalls Valve Caps Sold With Hot Tubs/Swim Spas Due to Impact Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/custom-molded-products-recalls-valve-caps-sold-with-hot-tubs-swim-spas-due-to-impact</link>
    <description>The valve cap on the hot tubs and swim spas can become loose, pop off and strike a bystander, posing an impact hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>July 10, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Swaddle Bee Recalls Children’s Security Blankets Due to Choking Hazard (Recall Alert) </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/swaddle-bee-recalls-childrens-security-blankets-due-to-choking-hazard-recall-alert</link>
    <description>The blanket’s snaps can detach, posing a choking hazard.</description>
     <pubDate>July 9, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Disney Recalls the Forky 11” Plush Toy Due to Choking Hazard</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/disney-recalls-the-forky-11%25E2%2580%259D-plush-toy-due-to-choking-hazard</link>
    <description>The “googly” plastic eyes on the toy can detach, posing a choking hazard to young children.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>July 8, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Company Store Recalls Girl’s Pajama Sets Due to Violation of Federal Flammability Standard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/the-company-store-recalls-girls-pajama-sets-due-to-violation-of-federal-flammability</link>
    <description>The pajama sets fail to meet the federal flammability standard for children&#039;s sleepwear, posing a risk of burn injuries to children.</description>
     <pubDate>July 3, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Just Love Fashion Recalls Children’s Pajama Pants Due to Violation of Federal Flammability Standard (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/just-love-fashion-recalls-childrens-pajama-pants-due-to-violation-of-federal</link>
    <description>The children’s pajama pants fail to meet the flammability standard for children’s sleepwear, posing a risk of burn injuries to children.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>July 3, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Nature’s Truth Recalls Wintergreen Essential Oil Due to Failure to Meet Child Resistant Closure Requirements
</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/natures-truth-recalls-wintergreen-essential-oil-due-to-failure-to-meet-child-resistant</link>
    <description>The bottles are not child resistant as required by the Poison Prevention Packaging Act, posing a poisoning risk if the contents are swallowed by young children.&amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>July 3, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>SRAM Recalls RockShox Front Suspension Forks Due to Crash and Injury Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/sram-recalls-rockshox-front-suspension-forks-due-to-crash-and-injury-hazards</link>
    <description>The fork’s lower leg assembly can break and cause the rider to lose control, posing crash and injury hazards.</description>
     <pubDate>July 2, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Electric Bicycles Recalled by Faraday; Seat Post Poses Fall Hazard

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/electric-bicycles-recalled-by-faraday-seat-post-poses-fall-hazard</link>
    <description>The seat post on the bicycles can break, posing a fall hazard to the rider. &amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>July 2, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Yamaha Recalls Grizzly ATVs and Wolverine X2 ROVs Due to Incorrect Owner’s Manual (Recall Alert)</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/yamaha-recalls-grizzly-atvs-and-wolverine-x2-rovs-due-to-incorrect-owners-manual-recall</link>
    <description>Purchasers were given a defective owner’s manual which shows the correct model on the cover, but the contents are for another model.</description>
     <pubDate>June 28, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Chandeliers Recalled by Dolan Northwest Due to Impact and Laceration Hazards</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/chandeliers-recalled-by-dolan-northwest-due-to-impact-and-laceration-hazards</link>
    <description>The top loop of the fixture can bend and break causing the chandelier to fall, posing an impact and laceration hazard to consumers.</description>
     <pubDate>June 27, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>BRP Recalls Coolers Due to Entrapment and Suffocation Hazards  </title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/brp-recalls-coolers-due-to-entrapment-and-suffocation-hazards</link>
    <description>The cooler latch can automatically lock when the lid is closed, allowing a person to become locked inside the air tight container posing entrapment and suffocation hazards. &amp;nbsp;</description>
     <pubDate>June 27, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Gillette Recalls Venus Simply3 Disposable Razors Due to Laceration and Injury Hazards 

</title>
    <link>https://www.cpsc.gov/Recalls/2019/gillette-recalls-venus-simply3-disposable-razors-due-to-laceration-and-injury-hazards</link>
    <description>A problem during manufacturing resulted in the misalignment of the blades in the razors, posing a higher risk of cuts during normal use.</description>
     <pubDate>June 27, 2019</pubDate>
 <dc:creator />
 <guid isPermaLink="false" />
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
