<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 19:27:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Legacy Pharmaceutical Packaging, LLC Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP, 25mg, 50mg, And 100mg Due to The Detection of Trace Amounts Of N-Nitroso N-Methyl 4-Amino Butyric Acid (NMBA) Impurity Found in The Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient (API)</title>
	 <description>Earth City, MO, Legacy Pharmaceutical Packaging, LLC is recalling 40 repackaged lots of Losartan Tablets USP 25mg, 50mg, and 100mg to the consumer level. This recall was prompted due to Camber Pharmaceuticals, Inc. issuing a Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Tablets, USP, due to the detection of trace amounts of N-Nitroso N-Methyl 4-amino butyric acid (NMBA) a possible process impurity or contaminant in an active pharmaceutical ingredient, manufactured by Hetero Labs Limited, (API manufacturer).</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 19:27:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633664.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633664.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Hospira, Inc. Issues a Voluntary Nationwide Recall of 8.4% Sodium Bicarbonate Injection, USP Due to the Presence of Particulate Matter</title>
	 <description>Hospira, Inc., a Pfizer company, is voluntarily recalling lot numbers 79-238-EV, 79-240-EV and 80-088-EV, NDC# 0409-6625-02, of 8.4% Sodium Bicarbonate Injection USP, 50 mEq/50 mL (1 mEq/mL), to the Hospital/Institution level. The recall was initiated due to the presence of particulate matter, confirmed as glass.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:57:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633663.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633663.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Surtidoras Bakery Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Marble Muffin, Banana Muffin, and Blueberry Muffin</title>
	 <description>Surtidoras Bakery Inc. of Auburn, Washington is recalling Marble Muffin, Banana Muffin, and Blueberry Muffin because it may contain undeclared milk.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:56:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633577.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633577.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Stokes Healthcare Inc. Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Pilocarpine 0.1% Ophthalmic Solution Due to a High Level of Preservative</title>
	 <description>Stokes Healthcare Inc. is voluntarily recalling 1 lot of 81 units of Pilocarpine 0.1% Ophthalmic Solution, to the consumer and veterinarian office levels. The ophthalmic solution has been found to contain a higher level of the preservative benzalkonium chloride than is typical.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 17:27:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633445.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633445.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Hometown Food Company Recalls Two Production LOT Codes of Pillsbury® Unbleached All-Purpose 5lb Flour Due to Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Please be advised the Hometown Food Company initiated a limited, voluntary retail-level recall on two specific lot codes of its Pillsbury® Unbleached All-Purpose 5 lb Flour (UPC 51500-22241) because it may be contaminated with Salmonella.  Only Best If Used By Dates APR 19 2020 and APR 20 2020 are impacted.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 11:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633320.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633320.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Claire’s Stores, Inc., Announces Voluntary Recall of Three Make-Up Products</title>
	 <description>Out of an abundance of caution, today Claire’s Stores, Inc., announced a voluntary recall of three cosmetic products: Claire’s Eye Shadows, Claire’s Compact Powder and Claire’s Contour Palette. We initiated this voluntary recall after testing by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration indicated the possible presence of asbestos fibers in product samples from one lot of each product.
Inhalation of asbestos over time has been linked to serious adverse health consequences.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 14:47:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633237.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633237.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Fullei Fresh Recalls Organic Bean Sprouts Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Fullei Fresh of Miami, Florida is voluntarily recalling Organic Bean Sprouts because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 17:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633081.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm633081.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Norbrook Laboratories Limited Recalls Veterinary Products for Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Norbrook Laboratories Limited of Newry, Northern Ireland is recalling two lots of Enroflox® 100 Injection (enrofloxacin), two lots of Noromectin® Injection (ivermectin) and two lots of Ivermax® 1% Injection (ivermectin) to the veterinarian/consumer level as a precautionary measure as product sterility cannot be assured. There is a concern that if the sterility of these products has been compromised, use of these products could result in introduction of infectious agents to the animal. This may result in the need for medical intervention(s) including, but not limited to the need for supportive care, antibiotics, and/or antifungal drugs.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 17:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632955.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632955.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>American Health Packaging Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Valsartan Tablets Due to the Detection of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity</title>
	 <description>American Health Packaging is voluntarily recalling one lot of Valsartan Tablets, USP, 160 mg to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in the finished drug product. The impurity detected in the finished drug product is N-Nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA), which is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, and has been classified as a probable human carcinogen as per International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC) classification. This recall is being initiated in response to the recall by the manufacturer (Aurobindo Pharma USA, Inc.), which included the affected lot that was repackaged by American Health Packaging.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 13:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632924.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632924.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>McDaniel Life-Line LLC Issues Voluntary Worldwide Recall of Life-Line Water</title>
	 <description>McDaniel Life-Line LLC is voluntarily recalling all lots of Life-Line Water to the consumer level. This product is being recalled because FDA analysis found the product to be contaminated with Pseudomonas aeruginosa.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 17:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632843.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632843.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Apotex Corp. Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Drospirenone and Ethinyl Estradiol Tablets, USP, 28x3 Blister Pack/Carton Due to Possibility of Missing/Incorrect Tablet Arrangement</title>
	 <description>Weston, Florida, Apotex Corp. is voluntarily recalling four lots of Drospirenone and Ethinyl Estradiol Tablets, USP to the patient /user level. The four recalled lots of Drospirenone and Ethinyl Estradiol Tablets, USP may possibly contain defective blisters with incorrect tablet arrangements and/or an empty blister pocket. The affected product is manufactured by Oman Pharmaceutical Products Co. LLC. Oman under the subcontract from Helm AG, Nordkanalstrasse 28, Hamburg, 20097, Germany.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 11:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632629.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632629.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sunstone Organics Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Select Kratom Products Due to Potential Contamination by &lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt;</title>
	 <description>Springfield, OR, Sunstone Organics is voluntarily recalling two lots of Sunstone Organics Kratom. These two lots include Sunstone Organics White Vein Kratom Lot 119 and Sunstone Organics Maeng Da Kratom Lot 124A in both capsules and powder form and in all sizes. The products have been found to potentially be contaminated with salmonella.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 16:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632554.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632554.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Updated: Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP and Losartan Potassium /Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP</title>
	 <description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited is voluntarily recalling 60 lots of Losartan potassium tablets USP and 54 lots of Losartan potassium/ hydrochlorothiazide tablets, USP, to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in an active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) manufactured by Hetero Labs Limited.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 15:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632509.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632509.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Asia Foods Distributor Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk Allergens in “Nova Salted Biscuit”</title>
	 <description>Asia foods Distributor Inc of 56-29 56 Drive, Maspeth, NY 11378 is recalling its 14.08 ounce packages of “Nova Salted Biscuit” food treats because they may contain undeclared milk allergens. Consumers who are allergic to milk allergens may run the risk of serious or lifethreatening allergic reactions if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 14:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632529.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632529.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>AurobindoPharma USA, Inc. Initiates a Voluntary Nationwide Consumer Level Recall Expansion of 38 Lots of Amlodipine Valsartan Tablets USP and Valsartan Tablets, USP due to the detection of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity.</title>
	 <description>AurobindoPharma USA, Inc. is conducting a voluntary recall expansion of 38 lots of Valsartan and Amlodipine and Valsartan tablets to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in the finished drug product. This recall is an expansion of the recall initiated 12/31/18  The impurity detected in the finished drug product is N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA), which is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, and has been classified as a probable human carcinogen as per International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC) classification. The expansion relates to lots distributed under the labels for AurobindoPharma USA, Inc. and Acetris Health, LLC.  To date, AurobindoPharma USA, Inc. has not received any reports of adverse events related to this recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 11:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632442.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632442.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Camber Pharmaceuticals, Inc. Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP, 25 mg, 50 mg and 100 mg Due to the Detection of Trace Amounts of N-Nitroso N-Methyl 4-amino butyric acid (NMBA) Impurity found in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient (API)</title>
	 <description>Camber Pharmaceuticals, Inc. is recalling 87 lots of Losartan Tablets USP 25 mg, 50 mg, and 100 mg to consumer level. This recall was prompted due to the detection of trace amounts of N-Nitroso N-Methyl 4-amino butyric acid (NMBA) a possible process impurity or contaminant in an active pharmaceutical ingredient, manufactured by Hetero Labs Limited, Unit – I (API manufacturer).</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 19:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632395.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632395.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Joy Gourmet Foods LLC  Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Sulfites</title>
	 <description>Joy Gourmet Foods Inc. of Maspeth, NY is recalling its Joy Brand Chutneys and Pastes products because they contain undeclared sulfites.. People who have allergies to sulfites run the risk of serious or
life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.
The recalled Joy Brand Chutneys and Pastes were distributed in NY, NJ,and CT in retail stores.The products comes in 8 oz,14 oz,16 oz, and 26 oz, 32 oz. clear glass jar packages and marked on the labels as follows:</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 17:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632223.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632223.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>UTZ Quality Foods Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Bachman 10 Ounce Twist</title>
	 <description>Utz Quality Foods, LLC., is voluntarily recalling a specific expiration date code of Bachman 10 oz Twist Pretzel packages due to undeclared milk. This recall was initiated after reviewing production records which identified a small number of packages were mislabeled.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 14:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632095.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632095.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>ICU Medical Issues a Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Certain Lots of ChemoLock™ and ChemoClave® Vial Spikes Due to the Potential for Burr Particulate</title>
	 <description>ICU Medical, Inc. today announced a voluntary recall of certain lots of ChemoLock™ and ChemoClave® Vial Spikes due to the potential for burr particulate originating from the protective cap used in the assembly of the device</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 11:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632065.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632065.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Southern Specialties Voluntarily Recalls Bagged Green Beans and Butternut Squash Distributed in Southeast because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Southern Specialties Inc. of Pompano Beach, Florida is voluntarily recalling select bags of Marketside brand green beans and butternut squash because they have the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 18:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632027.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632027.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
