<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 19:50:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Apio, Inc. Voluntarily Recalls Five Skus of Eat Smart Single-Serve Salad Shake Ups™</title>
	 <description>Apio, Inc. of Guadalupe, California is voluntarily recalling five SKUs of Eat Smart® Single-Serve Salad Shake Ups™ (bowls). The recall comes after the Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA) informed the company that one random sample of Eat Smart Single-Serve Salad Shake Ups Sweet Kale/Chou Frise Doux 156 gr. (5.5oz) with Best Before of Dec 14, 2018 tested positive for Listeria Monocytogenes. As a precautionary measure, we are recalling all products produced on the same day, same production line, as the one sample that tested positive by CFIA. At this time, we are not aware of any illnesses linked by health officials to this recall and no other products are affected by this recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 19:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628566.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628566.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Del Monte Foods Announces Limited Recall of Canned Fiesta Corn Seasoned with Red &amp; Green Peppers Due to Under Processing</title>
	 <description>Del Monte Foods Inc. announced a recall of 64,242 cases of FIESTA CORN Seasoned with Red &amp; Green Peppers due to under-processing. These deviations were part of the commercial sterilization process and could result in contamination by spoilage organisms or pathogens, which could lead to life-threatening illness if consumed. It is important to note that there have been no reports of illness associated with these products to date. No other production codes or products are affected by this recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 12:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628259.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628259.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Kimberly-Clark Announces Voluntary Recall of U by Kotex® Sleek® Tampons, Regular Absorbency,Throughout U.S. and Canada</title>
	 <description>Kimberly-Clark announced a voluntary product recall of its U by Kotex® Sleek® Tampons, Regular Absorbency, sold throughout the United States and Canada for a quality-related defect that could impact the performance of this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 10:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628237.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628237.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Moonstruck Chocolate Co. Issues Allergy Alert On Undeclared Hazelnuts In 4 Oz. Sea Salt Caramels Tumbled In Milk Chocolate</title>
	 <description>Moonstruck Chocolate Company of Portland, Oregon is recalling 600/4 oz. bags of Sea Salt Caramels Tumbled In Milk Chocolate, because it may contain undeclared hazelnuts. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to hazelnuts run the risk of a serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 22:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628194.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628194.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Inspired Organics Issues Voluntary Recall of Organic Sunflower Butter Due to Potential Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Inspired Organics, LLC has issued a voluntary recall of Organic Sunflower Butter due to potential contamination of Listeria monocytogenes. Listeria monocytogenes is an organism, which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 16:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628186.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628186.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>The J.M. Smucker Company Issues Voluntary Recall of Specific Lots of 9Lives® Protein Plus® Wet, Canned Cat Food Due to Low Levels of Thiamine (Vitamin B1)</title>
	 <description>The J.M. Smucker Company today announced a voluntary recall of specific lots of 9Lives® Protein Plus® wet, canned cat food due to possible low levels of thiamine (Vitamin B1). No illnesses related to this issue have been reported to date and the product is being recalled out of an abundance of caution.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 12:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628058.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628058.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Fine Land Corp Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk Allergens in “Meiqili Durian Candy”</title>
	 <description>Fine Land Corp is recalling it’s 12 ounce (340 g) Meiqili Durian Candy in plastic bag with clear
window because it contains undeclared milk allergens. Consumers who are allergic to milk
allergens may run the risk of serious or life – threatening allergic reactions if they consume this
product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 08:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627880.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627880.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Accra Super Market Issues Allergy Alert On Undeclared Peanuts In &#39;Suya Barbecue Seasoning&#39;</title>
	 <description>Accra Super Market of Worcester MA, is recalling 0.53 lbs packages of &quot;Suya Barbecue Seasoning&quot; because it may contain undeclared peanuts. People who have allergies to peanuts run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 22:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627855.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627855.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Kroger Louisville Division Recalls Abound Chicken and Brown Rice Dog Food Because of Elevated Vitamin D Levels</title>
	 <description>Following a recall by Sunshine Mills, Inc., the Kroger Louisville division announced it has removed from sale Abound Chicken &amp; Brown Rice Recipe dog food produced by the supplier. The dog food was sold in one Kroger store located at 2440 Bardstown Road in Louisville, KY.  Only Abound Chicken &amp; Brown Rice Recipe dog food with the listed UPC numbers and Best by Dates are affected by this recall. The recall was initiated because the product had the potential to contain an elevated level of Vitamin D, which may cause renal failure.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627843.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627843.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>King Soopers and City Market Recalls Abound Chicken and Brown Rice Dog Food Because of Elevated Vitamin D Levels</title>
	 <description>Following a recall by Sunshine Mills, Inc., King Soopers announced it has removed from sale Abound Chicken &amp; Brown Rice Recipe dog food produced by Sunshine Mills, Inc. sold in King Soopers and City Market stores, located in Colorado, Utah, New Mexico and Wyoming. Only Abound Chicken &amp; Brown Rice Recipe dog food with the listed UPC numbers and Best by Dates are affected by this recall. The recall was initiated because the product had the potential to contain an elevated level of Vitamin D, which may cause renal failure.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 16:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627838.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627838.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Danone North America Issues Allergy Alert and Recall for Light &amp; Fit Greek Crunch S’mores Flavor</title>
	 <description>Danone North America is voluntarily recalling 3,521 cases of Light &amp; Fit® Greek Crunch Nonfat Yogurt &amp; Toppings S’Mores Flavor sold in the United States with an expiration date of December 30, 2018 and UPC of 36632 03825. It was discovered that some of the toppers sold on the product contain peanuts and are improperly labeled. People who have an allergy to peanuts run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 13:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627792.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627792.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Tris Pharma Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Infants’ Ibuprofen Concentrated Oral Suspension, USP (NSAID) 50 mg per 1.25 mL, Due to Potential Higher Concentrations of Ibuprofen</title>
	 <description>Tris Pharma, Inc. has voluntarily recalled three (3) lots of Infants’ Ibuprofen Concentrated Oral Suspension, USP (NSAID) 50 mg per 1.25 mL, to the retail level. The recalled lots of the product have been found to potentially have higher concentrations of ibuprofen.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627780.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627780.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Country Flavor Inc Issues Alert on Undeclared Sulfites In &quot;Best Taste Brand Dried Bamboo Shoot&quot;</title>
	 <description>Country Favor Inc. of Maspeth, New York is recalling its 12 ounce packages of &quot;Best Taste Brand DRIED BAMBOO SHOOT&quot; food treats because they contained undeclared sulfites. Consumers who have severe sensitivity to sulfites run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reactions if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627727.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627727.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Columbia River Natural Pet Foods Inc. Recalls Cow Pie Fresh Frozen Meats for Dogs and Cats Because of Possible &lt;em&gt;Listeria monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt; Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Columbia River Natural Pet Foods of Vancouver, WA is voluntarily recalling 933 packages of Cow Pie fresh frozen meats for dogs and cats, produced in August 2017, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 15:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627721.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627721.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Chukar Cherries Expands Recall of Ultra Dark Chocolate Product Due to Undeclared Milk</title>
	 <description>Chukar Cherries of Prosser, WA expands a recall on Ultra Dark Chocolate product because it may contain undeclared milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627711.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627711.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Hiland Dairy Announces Voluntary Recall of Hiland Dairy Half-Gallon Whole Chocolate Milk</title>
	 <description>Hiland Dairy is announcing a voluntary recall of half-gallon premium whole milk chocolate that is produced at the Kansas City, Missouri facility, over concerns the products may contain eggnog that could affect those individuals that have sensitivity to egg allergens. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to eggs run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627712.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627712.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Mylan Expands Its Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Valsartan Tablets, USP, Amlodipine and Valsartan Tablets, USP, and Valsartan and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP, to all Lots Within Expiry Due to The Detection of Trace Amounts of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity Found in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient</title>
	 <description>– Mylan N.V. (NASDAQ: MYL) today announced that its U.S. based Mylan Pharmaceuticals business is expanding its consumer-level voluntary nationwide recall to include all lots of Valsartan-containing products within expiry. The 104 additional lots include 26 lots of Amlodipine and Valsartan Tablets, USP (including the 5mg/160mg, 10mg/160mg, 5mg/320mg and 10mg/320mg strengths), 51 lots of Valsartan Tablets, USP (including 40 mg, 80 mg, 160 mg and 320 mg strengths), and 27 lots of Valsartan and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP (80mg/12.5mg, 160mg/12.5mg, 160mg/25mg, 320mg/12.5mg and 320mg/25mg strengths).</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627647.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627647.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Tres Hermanos Bakery Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Telera and Bolillo Breads</title>
	 <description>Tres Hermanos Bakery of Wyoming, MI is recalling its white Telera and Bolillo Mexican salt breads because they may contain undeclared milk. People who have allergies to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627350.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627350.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Gemini Food Corporation Conducts Voluntary Recall of Imperial Taste Fried Red Onions and Fried Garlic Due to Undeclared Wheat</title>
	 <description>Gemini Food Corporation has voluntarily recalled all Imperial Taste Fried Red Onions &amp; Fried Garlic canisters as a precautionary measure because it’s missing an allergen statement and the ingredient panel does not include wheat.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 16:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627188.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627188.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>ELM Pet Foods Recall of Dry Dog Food Due to Elevated Levels of Vitamin D</title>
	 <description>ELM Pet Foods, Inc is issuing a voluntary recall of Elm Chicken and Chickpea Recipe dog food because the products could contain elevated levels of Vitamin D.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627139.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627139.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
