<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 22:53:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Aurobindo Pharma USA, Inc. Initiates Voluntary Nationwide Consumer Level Recall of 80 Lots of Amlodipine Valsartan Tablets USP, Valsartan HCTZ Tablets, USP and Valsartan Tablets USP, Due to the Detection of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity</title>
	 <description>Aurobindo Pharma USA, Inc. is conducting a voluntary recall of 80 lots of Amlodipine Valsartan Tablets USP, Valsartan HCTZ Tablets, USP and Valsartan Tablets USP to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in the finished drug product.   The impurity detected in the finished drug product is N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA), which is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, and has been classified as a probable human carcinogen as per International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC) classification. To date, Aurobindo Pharma USA, Inc. has not received any reports of adverse events related to this recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 22:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629213.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629213.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Apio Inc. Expands Voluntary Recall of Eat Smart Salad Shake Ups Single-Serve Bowls</title>
	 <description>Apio Inc. of Guadalupe, California is expanding a voluntary recall of Eat Smart Salad Shake Ups single-serve bowls. The recall comes after the Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA) informed the company that another random sample of Eat Smart Salad Shake Ups Sweet Kale/Chou Frise Doux 156 gr. single-serve bowls (5.5oz) with Best Before Date of Dec 29, 2018, Lot 112 346, tested positive for Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 17:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629152.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629152.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Columbia River Natural Pet Foods Inc. Voluntarily Expands Recall to Include Cow Pie and Chicken &amp; Vegetables Fresh Frozen Meats for Dogs and Cats Due to Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Columbia River Natural Pet Foods of Vancouver, WA is voluntarily expanding their current recall to include additional products: 261 packages of Cow Pie Lot # 72618 and 82 packages of Chicken &amp; Vegetables Lot# 111518 fresh frozen meats for dogs and cats, produced in July 2018 and November 2018, due to their potential to be contaminated with Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 09:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629119.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629119.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Funky Chunky, Llc Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Almond and Cashew Tree-Nut in 10 Oz. Nutty Choco Pop Found in Chocolate Popcorn Gift Box, Holiday Crowd Pleaser and Crowd Pleaser Gifts</title>
	 <description>Funky Chunky, LLC of Eden Prairie, MN is recalling 10 oz Nutty Choco Pop Gift Box, 50 oz. Holiday Crowd Pleaser and 50 oz. Crowd Pleaser, because it may contain undeclared Almond and Cashew Tree Nut. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to Almonds and Cashews run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629106.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629106.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Inspired Organics Issues Voluntary Recall of Organic Nut &amp; Seed Butters Due to Potential Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Inspired Organics, LLC has issued a voluntary recall of Organic Almond, Peanut, and Tahini Butters due to potential contamination of Listeria monocytogenes. Listeria monocytogenes is an organism, which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short- term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 17:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628989.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628989.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Terrific Care, LLC. / Medex Supply Dist, Inc. issues Nationwide Recall of CoaguChek Test Strips</title>
	 <description>On 12/19/2018, Terrific Care, LLC. / Medex Supply Dist, Inc. initiated a nationwide recall of Roche CoaguChek test strips distributed directly to U.S. consumers by Terrific Care, LLC. / Medex Supply Dist, Inc. The products have been found to inaccurately report high INR test results.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 15:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628976.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628976.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP</title>
	 <description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited is voluntarily recalling 2 lots of Losartan potassium tablets, USP to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in an active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) manufactured by Hetero Labs Limited. The impurity detected in the API is N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA), which is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, and has been classified as a probable human carcinogen as per International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC) classification.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 14:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628966.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628966.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Wegmans Issues Voluntary Recall of Fresh Cauliflower Rice, Veggie/Cauliflower Rice Blend and Stir-Fry Mix with Cauliflower</title>
	 <description>Rochester, NY – Wegmans Food Markets, Inc. has issued a voluntary recall of fresh Cauliflower Rice, Veggie Cauliflower Rice Blend and Stir-Fry Mix with Cauliflower, sold in the produce department between 12/7/18 and 12/18/18, because it may be contaminated with Escherichia coli O157:H7 bacteria (E. Coli O157:H7). E. coli O157:H7 causes a diarrheal illness often with bloody stools. Although most healthy adults can recover completely within a week, some people can develop a form of kidney failure called Hemolytic Uremic Syndrome (HUS). HUS is most likely to occur in young children and the elderly. The condition can lead to serious kidney damage and even death.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 09:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628826.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628826.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Medtronic Announces Worldwide Voluntary Field Corrective Action; Company Issues Software Update for Puritan Bennett™ 980 (Pb980) Ventilator Series</title>
	 <description>Medtronic (NYSE:MDT) is notifying customers worldwide of a voluntary field corrective action for its Puritan Bennett™ 980 (PB980) ventilator series.
Medtronic initiated this field action on September 19, 2018.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 22:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628812.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628812.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Adam Bros. Farming, Inc. Recalls Red and Green Leaf Lettuce and Cauliflower Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Adam Bros. Farming, Inc. of Santa Maria, California is recalling red leaf lettuce, green leaf lettuce and cauliflower harvested on November 27 through 30, 2018 out of an abundance of caution, because it may be contaminated with Escherichia coli O157:H7 bacteria (E. Coli O157:H7).</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 22:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628722.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628722.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Atherstone Foods Inc Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Soy in “Greens and Grains Hummus and Quinoa Tabouleh Wrap”</title>
	 <description>ATHERSTONE FOODS INC of Richmond, CA is recalling 14.6 ounce (414g) Greens and Grains Hummus and Quinoa Tabouleh Wrap, because it may contain undeclared soy, people who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to soy run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 22:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628719.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628719.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Enovachem Pharmaceuticals Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Dyural-40 and Dyural-80 Convenience Kits Containing Recalled Sodium Chloride Injection, USP, 0.9% Due to Latex Hazard</title>
	 <description>Torrance, CA, Asclemed USA Inc is voluntarily recalling 20 lots of Dyural-40 and 61 lots of Dyural-80, to the user level. The products include recalled Sodium Chloride, USP, 0.9% manufactured by Fresenius Kabi, which has been recalled due to product labeling incorrectly stating stoppers do not contain latex.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 18:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628712.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628712.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Inspired Organics Issues Voluntary Recall of Organic Almond Butter Due to Potential Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Inspired Organics, LLC has issued a voluntary recall of Organic Almond Butter due to potential contamination of Listeria monocytogenes. Listeria monocytogenes is an organism, which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 14:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628680.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628680.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Spokane Produce Voluntarily Recalls Northwest Cuisine Creations and Fresh&amp;Local Sandwiches and Green Leaf Lettuce Filets</title>
	 <description>Spokane Produce Inc. of Spokane, WA initiates a voluntary recall of sandwiches containing green leaf lettuce and foodservice lettuce filets following notice of a produce industry ingredient recall by Adam Bros.
Farming Inc. Sandwich products bearing the Northwest Cuisine Creations and Fresh&amp;Local labels. These prod- ucts are recalled because they may be contaminated with Escherichia coli O157:H7 bacteria (E. Coli O157:H7).
E. coli O157:H7 causes a diarrheal illness often with bloody stools. Although most healthy adults can recover completely within a week, some people can develop a form of kidney failure called Hemolytic Uremic Syndrome (HUS). HUS is most likely to occur in young children and the elderly. The condition can lead to serious kidney damage and even death</description>
	 <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 10:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628583.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628583.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Apio, Inc. Voluntarily Recalls Five Skus of Eat Smart Single-Serve Salad Shake Ups™</title>
	 <description>Apio, Inc. of Guadalupe, California is voluntarily recalling five SKUs of Eat Smart® Single-Serve Salad Shake Ups™ (bowls). The recall comes after the Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA) informed the company that one random sample of Eat Smart Single-Serve Salad Shake Ups Sweet Kale/Chou Frise Doux 156 gr. (5.5oz) with Best Before of Dec 14, 2018 tested positive for Listeria Monocytogenes. As a precautionary measure, we are recalling all products produced on the same day, same production line, as the one sample that tested positive by CFIA. At this time, we are not aware of any illnesses linked by health officials to this recall and no other products are affected by this recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 19:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628566.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628566.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Del Monte Foods Announces Limited Recall of Canned Fiesta Corn Seasoned with Red &amp; Green Peppers Due to Under Processing</title>
	 <description>Del Monte Foods Inc. announced a recall of 64,242 cases of FIESTA CORN Seasoned with Red &amp; Green Peppers due to under-processing. These deviations were part of the commercial sterilization process and could result in contamination by spoilage organisms or pathogens, which could lead to life-threatening illness if consumed. It is important to note that there have been no reports of illness associated with these products to date. No other production codes or products are affected by this recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 12:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628259.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628259.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Kimberly-Clark Announces Voluntary Recall of U by Kotex® Sleek® Tampons, Regular Absorbency,Throughout U.S. and Canada</title>
	 <description>Kimberly-Clark announced a voluntary product recall of its U by Kotex® Sleek® Tampons, Regular Absorbency, sold throughout the United States and Canada for a quality-related defect that could impact the performance of this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 10:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628237.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628237.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Moonstruck Chocolate Co. Issues Allergy Alert On Undeclared Hazelnuts In 4 Oz. Sea Salt Caramels Tumbled In Milk Chocolate</title>
	 <description>Moonstruck Chocolate Company of Portland, Oregon is recalling 600/4 oz. bags of Sea Salt Caramels Tumbled In Milk Chocolate, because it may contain undeclared hazelnuts. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to hazelnuts run the risk of a serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 22:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628194.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628194.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Inspired Organics Issues Voluntary Recall of Organic Sunflower Butter Due to Potential Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Inspired Organics, LLC has issued a voluntary recall of Organic Sunflower Butter due to potential contamination of Listeria monocytogenes. Listeria monocytogenes is an organism, which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 16:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628186.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628186.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>The J.M. Smucker Company Issues Voluntary Recall of Specific Lots of 9Lives® Protein Plus® Wet, Canned Cat Food Due to Low Levels of Thiamine (Vitamin B1)</title>
	 <description>The J.M. Smucker Company today announced a voluntary recall of specific lots of 9Lives® Protein Plus® wet, canned cat food due to possible low levels of thiamine (Vitamin B1). No illnesses related to this issue have been reported to date and the product is being recalled out of an abundance of caution.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 12:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628058.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628058.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
