<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 15:15:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Purina Animal Nutrition Voluntarily Recalling Purina&#174; Honor&#174; Show Chow&#174; Showlamb Grower Due to Elevated Copper Level</title>
	 <description>)&#8211; Purina Animal Nutrition is voluntarily recalling two lots of Purina&#174; Honor&#174; Show Chow&#174; Showlamb Grower due to elevated copper levels. The feed is packaged in purple branded Purina Honor Show Chow bags.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 15:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630003.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630003.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Oskri Organics Corporation Recalls All Nut Butters because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Oskri Organics Corporation of Lake Mills, WI is recalling ALL Oskri Corporation manufactured nut butters. This recall has been initiated due to positive test results for Listeria monocytogenes found in multiple Oskri Corporation manufactured nut butters.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 14:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630036.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630036.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>SL: Recall of Thrive Market Nut Butters Due to Potential Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Thrive Market, Inc, is recalling all unexpired lots of the Thrive Market-branded nut butters listed below (&#8220;Product(s)&#8221;) due to the potential for contamination with Listeria monocytogenes. On January 21, 2019, one of our  suppliers notified us that it was issuing a recall of all nut butters it has manufactured since January 2018 because of a positive test for Listeria monocytogenes in recent lots.  Because the safety of our members is our absolute priority, we are expanding on our supplier&#8217;s recall and are voluntarily recalling all unexpired lots of all  Thrive Market-branded nut butters manufactured by this supplier.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 18:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629819.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629819.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Mrs. Grissom&#8217;s Salads Issues a Voluntary Recall</title>
	 <description>For immediate release- January 18,2019 &#8211; Nashville, TN &#8211; Mrs. Grissom&#8217;s Salads is voluntarily recalling a single days production of Mrs. Grissom&#8217;s SELECT Old Fashioned Pimento Cheese because of a labeling issue. Product produced on December 13, 2018 may have been packaged incorrectly, with the correct Pimento Cheese label on top lid, but a Chicken salad label on the container. The Pimento Cheese may contain allergens not listed on the products ingredient label, Specifically Milk.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 16:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629807.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629807.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Jac. Vandenberg, Inc. Recalls Fresh Peaches, Fresh Nectarines and Fresh Plums Because They May Be Contaminted with Listeria Monocytogenes</title>
	 <description>Jac. Vandenberg, Inc. of Yonkers, New York is recalling 1,727 cartons of Fresh Peaches, 1,207 cartons of Fresh Nectarines and 365 cartons of Fresh Plums because they have the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 10:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629797.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629797.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Satur Farms&#8217; Recall of Baby Spinach Affects Prepared Food Items from Whole Foods Market Stores in Eight States</title>
	 <description>In response to a recall by Satur Farms, Whole Foods Market is voluntarily recalling various prepared foods items in eight states containing baby spinach because of a potential contamination of Salmonella.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 21:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629788.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629788.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Product Recall Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Satur Farms, 3705 Alvah&#39;s Lane, Cutchogue, NY 11935 is voluntarily recalling Baby Spinach and Mesclun with the specific lot numbers listed below because it has the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people and others with weakened immune systems. Healthy persons infected with Salmonella often experience fever, diarrhea (which may be bloody), nausea, vomiting and abdominal pain.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629755.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629755.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>General Mills Recalls Five Pound Bags of Gold Medal Unbleached Flour</title>
	 <description>General Mills announced today a voluntary national recall of five-pound bags of its Gold Medal Unbleached Flour with a better if used by date of April 20, 2020. The recall is being issued for the potential presence of Salmonella which was discovered during sampling of the five-pound bag product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629754.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629754.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Perrigo Issues Allergy Alert For Simple Truth Organic Banana, Strawberry &amp; Apple Puree With Nonfat Greek Yogurt</title>
	 <description>Perrigo Company, in coordination with The Kroger Company, is initiating a voluntary recall of one production lot of Simple Truth Organic Banana, Strawberry &amp; Apple Fruit Puree with Nonfat Greek Yogurt (LOT L8159, best by 08/06/2019, produced in Spain) due to improper labeling that does not indicate the presence of milk, posing a potential risk to consumers with milk allergies.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629753.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629753.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>UPDATED: Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP and Losartan Potassium and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP</title>
	 <description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited is expanding its voluntary recall from 10 lots of Losartan potassium tablets USP to include 6 lots of Losartan potassium and hydrochlorothiazide tablets, USP, to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in an active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) manufactured by Hetero Labs Limited.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 16:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629693.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629693.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Ottogi America, Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Egg in Products</title>
	 <description>Ottogi America, Inc. announced today it is recalling below 21 items due to a possibility of containing egg ingredient undeclared on the packages.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to eggs run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction of they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 21:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629663.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629663.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Prinston Pharmaceutical Inc. issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Irbesartan and Irbesartan HCTZ Tablets Due to detection of a Trace Amount of Unexpected Impurity, N- nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA) in the Products</title>
	 <description>-- Prinston
Pharmaceutical Inc., dba Solco Healthcare LLC., has initiated a voluntary recall of one (1) lot of Irbesartan and seven (7) lots of Irbesartan HCTZ Tablets to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amount of an unexpected impurity found in an active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) manufactured by Zhejiang Huahai Pharmaceuticals.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 14:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629627.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629627.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>RXBAR Recalls Certain Varieties of Bars Due to a Potential Undeclared Peanut Allergen</title>
	 <description>RXBAR is voluntarily recalling certain varieties of bars because they may contain undeclared peanuts. People who have peanut allergies run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:39:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629527.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629527.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Voluntary Recall Notice of El Guapo Chile Habanero and Chile Pasilla-Ancho Pouches Due to Unlabeled Peanut Allergen</title>
	 <description>Mojave Foods Corporation is initiating a voluntary recall of El Guapo Chile Habanero and Chile Pasilla-Ancho pouches due to an unlabeled peanut allergen.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 20:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629522.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629522.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Happy Together, Inc. Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Product Due to Presence of Undeclared Sildenafil and Tadalafil</title>
	 <description>Happy Together, Inc. Boynton Beach, FL is voluntarily recalling all lots within expiry of the Rhino 5k capsules to the consumer level. FDA analysis founds these products to be tainted with sildenafil and Tadalafil. Sildenafil/Tadalafil is an FDA approved drug for the treatment of erectile dysfunction, the presence of sildenafil in the Rhino 5k products renders them unapproved drugs for which safety and efficacy have not been established, therefor subject to recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 17:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629353.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629353.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries, Inc. Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Vecuronium Bromide for Injection Due to the Presence of Particulate Matter Identified as Glass</title>
	 <description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries, Inc. (SPII), a wholly owned subsidiary of Sun Pharmaceutical Industries, Ltd. is voluntarily recalling three lots of Vecuronium Bromide for Injection, 10 mg (lyophilized powder), and one lot of Vecuronium Bromide for Injection, 20 mg (lyophilized powder) to the hospital level. The Vecuronium Bromide for Injection has been found to contain particulate matter identified as glass.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 11:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629328.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629328.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Grand Strand Sandwich Company Recalls Lunch Box Sandwiches Italian Subs Lunch Box Sandwiches Ham &amp; Swiss Croissants And Lunch Box Sandwiches Ham &amp; Cheese Due To Possible &lt;em&gt;Listeria Monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt; Contamination</title>
	 <description>&#8211; Grand Strand Sandwich is recalling Lunch Box Italian Subs, Lunch Box Ham &amp; Swiss Croissants and Lunch Box Ham &amp; Cheese Frozen Wedges due to a potential contamination of &lt;em&gt;Listeria Monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt;.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 21:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629322.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629322.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Hy-Vee Voluntarily Recalls Cheesecakes Made with Diamond Crystal Mix</title>
	 <description>Hy-Vee, Inc., based in West Des Moines, Iowa, is voluntarily recalling its cheesecakes made with Diamond Crystal Brands cheesecake mix due to the potential that they may be contaminated with Salmonella. The potential for contamination was brought to Hy-Vee&#8217;s attention today after receiving a letter from the supplier. The voluntary recall includes 32 varieties of cheesecakes in both 8-ounce and 32-ounce packages with best if used by dates of Dec. 6, 2018, through Jan. 11, 2019. No illnesses have been reported to date.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 13:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629310.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629310.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Lupin Pharmaceuticals, Inc. Issues Voluntary Recall of Ceftriaxone for Injection USP, 250mg, 500mg, 1g and 2g</title>
	 <description>Lupin Pharmaceuticals, Inc. is voluntarily recalling 5 lots of Ceftriaxone for Injection, USP, 250mg, 10 lots of Ceftriaxone for Injection, USP, 500mg, 24 lots of Ceftriaxone for Injection, USP, 1g and 3 lots of Ceftriaxone for Injection, USP 2g, to the hospital/physician level. The products have been found to contain visual grey particulate matter in reconstituted vials.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 18:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629298.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629298.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Olde York Potato Chips Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in One Lot of Clancy&#39;s Wavy Potato Chips 10 Oz</title>
	 <description>Olde York Potato Chips of
Brampton, Ontario is recalling Clancy&#39;s Wavy Potato Chips 10 oz (UPC 0 41498 16306 8) with the specific lot code BEST If Used By FEB 22 19 1A6 because they may contain undeclared milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products. No other lot codes and no other products are involved in this action.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 17:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629293.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629293.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
