<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:schema="http://schema.org/" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#" version="2.0" xml:base="http://www.fda.gov/about-fda/contact-fda/stay-informed/rss-feeds/recalls/rss.xml">
  <channel>
    <title>Food and Drugs Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
    <link>http://www.fda.gov/about-fda/contact-fda/stay-informed/rss-feeds/recalls/rss.xml</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Broddzenatti Holding LLC. Recalls Karawan Brand Tahini Because Of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/broddzenatti-holding-llc-recalls-karawan-brand-tahini-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Broddzenatti Holding LLC of Jupiter, Florida is recalling retail and bulk Karawan brand Tahini, sold in 16-ounce jars and 39-pound buckets that were imported from Palestine between the dates of December 2018 to January 2019, because it has the potential to be contaminated with &lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-16T03:35:04Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/broddzenatti-holding-llc-recalls-karawan-brand-tahini-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>GHSW, LLC Issues Allergy Alert On Undeclared Soy in Certain Salads, Wraps and Salad Bar Trays Sold at Select Whole Foods Market and Whole Foods Market 365 Stores</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ghsw-llc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-soy-certain-salads-wraps-and-salad-bar-trays-sold-select</link>
  <description>GHSW, LLC is voluntarily recalling select salads, wraps and salad bar trays sold two Whole Foods Markets 365 in Texas and at Whole Foods Markets in Louisiana, Oklahoma and Texas because the product labels fail to declare soy as a sub-ingredient of the mayonnaise used to manufacture the products.</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-16T03:30:20Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ghsw-llc-issues-allergy-alert-undeclared-soy-certain-salads-wraps-and-salad-bar-trays-sold-select</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Seven Seas International USA, LLC Recalls Biltmore Smoked Sockeye Salmon Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/seven-seas-international-usa-llc-recalls-biltmore-smoked-sockeye-salmon-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Seven Seas International USA, LLC of St. Petersburg, Florida is recalling its 4 oz. Biltmore Smoked Sockeye Salmon, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes&lt;br /&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-15T14:40:13Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/seven-seas-international-usa-llc-recalls-biltmore-smoked-sockeye-salmon-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Novartis Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Promacta® 12.5 mg for Oral Suspension Due to Potential Peanut Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/novartis-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-promactar-125-mg-oral-suspension-due-potential-peanut</link>
  <description>Novartis today announced a voluntary recall of three lots of Promacta (eltrombopag) 12.5 mg for oral suspension to the consumer level. The oral suspension lots are being recalled because of a risk of potential peanut flour contamination that occurred at a third-party contract manufacturing site. </description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-12T15:30:47Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/novartis-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-promactar-125-mg-oral-suspension-due-potential-peanut</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Deshi Distributors LLC Issues Alert on Undeclared Sulfites in Deshi “Golden Raisins”</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/deshi-distributors-llc-issues-alert-undeclared-sulfites-deshi-golden-raisins</link>
  <description>Deshi Distributors LLC. of Jamaica, NY, is recalling its 3.5 oz,  7 oz and 14 oz  packages of Deshi “Golden Raisins”  because they contained undeclared sulfites. Consumers who have severe sensitivity to sulfites run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reactions if they consume this prod</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-10T20:24:00Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/deshi-distributors-llc-issues-alert-undeclared-sulfites-deshi-golden-raisins</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sunstone Organics Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Select Kratom Products Due to Potential Contamination by Salmonella</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sunstone-organics-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-select-kratom-products-due-potential-0</link>
  <description>Two lots of Sunstone Organics Kratom. These two lots include Sunstone Organics White Vein Kratom Lot 119 and Sunstone Organics Maeng Da Kratom Lot 124A in both capsules and powder form and in all sizes. The products have been found to potentially be contaminated with salmonella</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T20:37:15Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sunstone-organics-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-select-kratom-products-due-potential-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Nature’s Path Foods Recalls A Specific Production Run Of Envirokidz Choco Chimps, Gorilla Munch And Jungle Munch Cereals Due To Undeclared Gluten</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/natures-path-foods-recalls-specific-production-run-envirokidz-choco-chimps-gorilla-munch-and-jungle</link>
  <description>EnviroKidz Choco Chimps, Gorilla Munch and Jungle Munch cereals for they may contain undeclared gluten (wheat and barley)</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T20:37:14Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/natures-path-foods-recalls-specific-production-run-envirokidz-choco-chimps-gorilla-munch-and-jungle</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sid Wainer and Son Initiates Class 2 Recall for Jansal Valley Dukkah Due to Potential Glass Pieces</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sid-wainer-and-son-initiates-class-2-recall-jansal-valley-dukkah-due-potential-glass-pieces-0</link>
  <description>Sid Wainer and Son of New Bedford, MA is voluntarily recalling Jansal Valley brand Dukkah in 2.5oz containers because of the potential of it containing glass pieces</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T20:37:14Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/sid-wainer-and-son-initiates-class-2-recall-jansal-valley-dukkah-due-potential-glass-pieces-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Ottogi America, Inc. Expands Recall on Undeclared Egg in Products</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ottogi-america-inc-expands-recall-undeclared-egg-products-0</link>
  <description>Ottogi America, Inc. announced today it is expanding its recall to include the two items below due to a possibility of containing egg ingredient undeclared on the packages.  </description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T20:37:13Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/ottogi-america-inc-expands-recall-undeclared-egg-products-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Allergy Alert Issued by Santa Rosa Whole Foods Market for Undeclared Walnut, Milk and Eggs in “Hipster Chipster” Cookies</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/allergy-alert-issued-santa-rosa-whole-foods-market-undeclared-walnut-milk-and-eggs-hipster-chipster-0</link>
  <description>The Santa Rosa Whole Foods Market store is voluntarily recalling eight packages of its “Hipster Chipster” cookies because they contain undeclared tree nut (walnut), milk, and egg allergens that were not listed on the product label.</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T20:37:13Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/allergy-alert-issued-santa-rosa-whole-foods-market-undeclared-walnut-milk-and-eggs-hipster-chipster-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Nature’s Rx Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Silver Bullet 10x to Undeclared PDE-5 Inhibitors in the Product</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/natures-rx-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-silver-bullet-10x-undeclared-pde-5-inhibitors-product</link>
  <description>Nature’s Rx is voluntarily recalling quantity lots of Silver Bullet 10x, description of dosage form to the hospital, retail or consumer level. This recall has been initiated because the product was found to contain undeclared sildenafil and tadalafil.</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T20:37:13Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/natures-rx-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-silver-bullet-10x-undeclared-pde-5-inhibitors-product</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Working Cow Homemade, Inc. Expands Recall of Ice Cream Products Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/working-cow-homemade-inc-expands-recall-ice-cream-products-because-possible-health-risk-0</link>
  <description>Working Cow Homemade, Inc. of St. Petersburg, FL is expanding its voluntary recall to include all ice cream manufactured from August 29, 2017 – October 11, 2018, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T20:37:12Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/working-cow-homemade-inc-expands-recall-ice-cream-products-because-possible-health-risk-0</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Vivimed Life Sciences Pvt Ltd Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium 25 mg, 50 mg and 100 mg Tablets, USP Due to the Detection of Trace Amounts of N-Nitroso-N-methyl-4-aminobutyric acid (NMBA) Impurity</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/vivimed-life-sciences-pvt-ltd-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-losartan-potassium-25-mg-50-mg-and</link>
  <description>Vivimed Life Sciences Pvt Ltd (Vivimed) is recalling 19 lots of Losartan Potassium Tablets USP 25 mg, 50 mg, and 100 mg to consumer level. Due to the detection of an impurity – N-Nitroso-N-methyl-4-aminobutyric acid (NMBA) – that is above the US Food &amp; Drug Administration’s interim acceptable exposu</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T20:20:04Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/vivimed-life-sciences-pvt-ltd-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-losartan-potassium-25-mg-50-mg-and</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Kingston Pharma, LLC RECALLS " DG™/health NATURALS baby Cough Syrup + Mucus”  Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kingston-pharma-llc-recalls-dgtmhealth-naturals-baby-cough-syrup-mucus-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Kingston Pharma, LLC of Massena, NY is recalling Lot KL180157 of its 2-fluid ounce (59 mL) bottles of DG™/health NATURALS baby Cough Syrup + Mucus” because it has the potential to be contaminated with Bacillus cereus/ Bacillus circulans. Bacillus cereus in food products has the potential to produce </description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T17:22:27Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/kingston-pharma-llc-recalls-dgtmhealth-naturals-baby-cough-syrup-mucus-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Legacy Pharmaceutical Packaging, LLC Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP, 50mg Due to the Detection of Trace Amounts of N-Nitroso N-Methyl 4-amino butyric acid (NMBA) Impurity found in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient (API)</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/legacy-pharmaceutical-packaging-llc-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-losartan-potassium-tablets-1</link>
  <description>Legacy Pharmaceutical Packaging, LLC is recalling 3 repackaged lots of Losartan Tablets USP 50mg to the consumer level. This recall was prompted due to Torrent Pharmaceuticals LTD issuing a Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Tablets, USP, due to the detection of trace amounts of N-Nitroso N-Met</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T17:05:20Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/legacy-pharmaceutical-packaging-llc-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-losartan-potassium-tablets-1</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Mecox Bay Dairy, LLC Recalls “Mecox Sunrise” Cheese Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/mecox-bay-dairy-llc-recalls-mecox-sunrise-cheese-because-possible-health-risk</link>
  <description>Mecox Bay Dairy, LLC, is recalling their Mecox Sunrise washed-rind Tomme style cheese because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-09T15:16:13Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/mecox-bay-dairy-llc-recalls-mecox-sunrise-cheese-because-possible-health-risk</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Maribel’s Sweets Inc. Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk Allergens in Chocolate Bars</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/maribels-sweets-inc-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-allergens-chocolate-bars</link>
  <description>Maribel’s Sweets Inc. of Brooklyn, NY is recalling its 2.82oz MarieBelle Japanese Matcha Japanese Green Tea and White Chocolate Bar, container code 101619, Cacao Market by MarieBelle Rosemary Truffle Salt 60% Dark Chocolate Bar, all container codes, and the Cacao Market by MarieBelle Orange Peels 60</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-07T21:21:31Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/maribels-sweets-inc-allergy-alert-undeclared-milk-allergens-chocolate-bars</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Product Quest Manufacturing LLC Recalls All Nasal Products and Baby Oral Gels Manufactured at Florida Facility Due to Possible Microbial Contamination</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/product-quest-manufacturing-llc-recalls-all-nasal-products-and-baby-oral-gels-manufactured-florida</link>
  <description>Product Quest Manufacturing (“Product Quest”) announced its voluntary recall of Lot# 173089J of CVS Health 12 Hour Sinus Relief Nasal Mist due to a finding of microbial contamination identified as Pseudomonas aeruginosa.</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-07T21:05:19Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/product-quest-manufacturing-llc-recalls-all-nasal-products-and-baby-oral-gels-manufactured-florida</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>PharMEDium Services, LLC Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Certain Lots of Compounded Sterile Products due to Lack of Sterility Assurance</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/pharmedium-services-llc-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-certain-lots-compounded-sterile-products</link>
  <description>December 27, 2017 Lake Forest, IL PharMEDium Services, LLC (PharMEDium) is voluntarily recalling the below lots of drug products to the hospital/user level due to a lack of assurance of sterility.  Administration of a drug product intended to be sterile that is not sterile could result in serious infections that may be life-threatening.  To date, PharMEDium has not received any reports of complaints related to the products but is issuing this recall out of an abundance of caution following a commitment made during a recent inspection of the company’s facility.</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-07T21:05:11Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/pharmedium-services-llc-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-certain-lots-compounded-sterile-products</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Pharmedium Services, LLC Expands Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Additional Lots of Compounded Sterile Products Within Expiry Due to Lack of Sterility Assurance</title>
  <link>http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/pharmedium-services-llc-expands-voluntary-nationwide-recall-additional-lots-compounded-sterile</link>
  <description>January 10, 2018 Lake Forest, IL PharMEDium Services, LLC (PharMEDium) is voluntarily expanding the recall issued on December 27, 2017 to include the below lots of sterile drug products to the hospital/user level due to a lack of assurance of sterility.  Administration of a drug product intended to be sterile that is not sterile could result in serious infections that may be life-threatening.</description>
  <pubDate>2019-05-07T19:35:11Z</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>FDA</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/pharmedium-services-llc-expands-voluntary-nationwide-recall-additional-lots-compounded-sterile</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
