<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 08:47:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Macleods Pharmaceuticals Limited Issues Voluntary Nationwide Consumer Level Recall of One Lot (BLM 715A) of Losartan Potassium/Hydrochlorothiazide Combination Tablets 100mg/25mg Due to detection of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity</title>
	 <description>Macleods Pharmaceuticals Limited is voluntarily recalling one lot of Losartan Potassium/Hydrochlorothiazide combination tablets 100mg/25mg to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity (NDEA) found in finished product manufactured with active pharmaceutical ingredient made by Hetero Labs Limited.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 08:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631880.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631880.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Meijer Recalls Mint Meijer Brand Ultimate Chocolate Mint Chip Cookies Due to an Undeclared Soy Allergen</title>
	 <description>Meijer is announcing a voluntary recall of its Meijer brand Ultimate Chocolate Mint Chip Cookies because soy it is not properly declared on the label.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 16:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631919.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631919.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Jacques Torres Manufacturing LLC Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk Allergens in “Jacques” Big Daddy Dark Chocolate Bar</title>
	 <description>Jacques Torres Manufacturing LLC of Brooklyn, New York is recalling its 2.2 lbs. (1kg), “Jacques” Big Daddy Dark Chocolate Bar, because it contains undeclared milk allergens.  Consumers who are allergic to milk allergens may run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 21:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631689.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631689.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Gilda Industries, Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Butter Pound Cake</title>
	 <description>Gilda Industries, Inc voluntarily recalls select code dates and manufacturing lot numbers of Panque – Butter pound cake because they may contain undeclared milk . People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of a serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume the product contained inside the recalled panque –butter pound cake</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 18:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631720.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631720.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Concord Fresh Success Recall Mild Salsa Seasoning Mix Due To Undeclared Milk Allergen</title>
	 <description>Concord Foods, LLC of Brockton, Massachusetts is recalling Concord Fresh Success Mild Salsa Seasoning Mix because it may contain undeclared milk allergen. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk allergen run the risk of serious or lifethreatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 18:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631634.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631634.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Chukar Cherries Expands Recall Of Amaretto Rainier Ultra Dark Chocolate Cherries Pouches Due To Undeclared Milk</title>
	 <description>February 18, 2019, Chukar Cherries of Prosser, WA is recalling 7.5oz Amaretto Rainier Ultra Dark Chocolate Cherries because they may contain undeclared milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 18:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631537.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631537.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Smoked Alaska Seafoods, Inc. Recalls 6.5 oz Jars &amp; Cans of Smoked Silver Salmon Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Smoked Alaska Seafoods, Inc. of Wasilla, AK is recalling all jars and cans of Smoked Silver Salmon in 6.5 oz. containers with the production code of AL81111133 on the bottom of the jar/can because it has the potential to be contaminated with Clostridium botulinum, a bacterium which can cause life-threatening illness or death. Consumers are warned not to use the product even if it does not look or smell spoiled.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 10:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631531.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631531.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Nature’s Path Foods Recalls A Specific Production Run Of Envirokidz Choco Chimps, Gorilla Munch And Jungle Munch Cereals Due To Undeclared Gluten</title>
	 <description>Today, Nature’s Path Foods announced a voluntary recall of a specific production run of EnviroKidz Choco Chimps, Gorilla Munch and Jungle Munch cereals for they may contain undeclared gluten (wheat and barley). People who have a wheat allergy, celiac disease or sensitivity to gluten and wheat should not consume the cereals with the BEST BEFORE DATE listed below due to potential adverse health effects. Nature’s Path is also removing any affected cereals from customer store shelves and warehouses.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 19:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631510.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631510.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Kingston Pharma, LLC Issues Voluntary Recall of All Lots of “DG™ Baby Gripe Water Due to Undissolved Ingredient, Citrus Flavonoid</title>
	 <description>Kingston Pharma, LLC is voluntarily recalling all lots of “DG™ Baby Gripe Water herbal supplement with organic ginger and fennel extracts” to the consumer level due to the presence of an undissolved ingredient, citrus flavonoid.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 16:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631500.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631500.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sid Wainer and Son Initiates Class 2 Recall for Jansal Valley Dukkah Due to Potential Glass Pieces</title>
	 <description>Sid Wainer and Son of New Bedford, MA is voluntarily recalling Jansal Valley brand Dukkah in 2.5oz containers because of the potential of it containing glass pieces</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 13:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631481.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631481.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Ottogi America, Inc. Expands Recall on Undeclared Egg in Products</title>
	 <description>Ottogi America, Inc. announced today it is expanding its recall to include the two items below due to a possibility of containing egg ingredient undeclared on the packages.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to eggs run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction of they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 10:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631285.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631285.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>World Waters Issues Voluntary Recall of Select WTRMLN WTR Original 12 Packs Due To The Possible Presence of Soft Plastic Pieces. Company Urges Consumers to Check Packages Prior to Consumption</title>
	 <description>World Waters, LLC is initiating a voluntary recall of certain lots of Cold Pressed Juice Watermelon WTRMLN WTR Original 12 packs due to the potential presence of soft plastic that may be loosely floating in some of the finished products</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 11:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631095.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631095.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Birdseed Food Co. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Cashews in Craft Granola Goldenola Turmeric &amp; Ginger</title>
	 <description>BIRDSEED FOOD CO. of Bend, OR is recalling Craft Granola Goldenola Turmeric &amp; Ginger that was sold between the dates of 10/03/18 - 02/07/19, because it contains undeclared cashews. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to cashews run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 21:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631041.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631041.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>McDaniel Life-Line LLC Issues Voluntary Worldwide Recall of Indian Herb</title>
	 <description>Felt, OK, McDaniel Life-Line LLC is voluntarily recalling all lots of Indian Herb to the consumer level. This product is being recalled because it is marketed without an approved NDA/ANDA. The therapeutic claims made in the labeling for this product establish that it is a drug because it is an article (other than food) intended to affect the structure or any function of the body.  Additionally, the product contains ingredients that the Agency has determined to be caustic in nature that can cause serious injury.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 18:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631039.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631039.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Frito-Lay Issues Voluntary Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk In Small Number of Stacy’s Simply Naked Pita Chips</title>
	 <description>Frito-Lay announced a limited voluntary recall of a very small number of 7 1/3 oz. bags of Stacy’s Simply Naked Pita Chips because they may contain undeclared milk ingredients. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of a serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume the product contained inside the recalled pita chips bags.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 22:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630685.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630685.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Allergy Alert Issued by Santa Rosa Whole Foods Market for Undeclared Walnut, Milk and Eggs in “Hipster Chipster” Cookies</title>
	 <description>The Santa Rosa Whole Foods Market store is voluntarily recalling eight packages of its “Hipster Chipster” cookies because they contain undeclared tree nut (walnut), milk, and egg allergens that were not listed on the product label.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 19:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630684.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630684.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Dr. Reddy&#39;s Laboratories Continues its Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Levetiracetam in 0.54% Sodium Chloride Injection 1500mg/100mL Due to Mislabeling</title>
	 <description>Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories Ltd. (BSE: 500124, NSE: DRREDDY, NYSE: RDY) announced that it’s wholly owned subsidiary, Dr Reddy’s Laboratories, Inc is continuing its voluntary nationwide recall of lot ABD807 of Levetiracetram in 0.54% Sodium Chloride Injection, 1,500 mg/100 mL (15 mg/mL) single-dose infusion bags to the hospital level in U.S.A.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 10:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630542.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630542.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Stryker Launches Voluntary Field Action for Specific Units of the LIFEPAK® 15 Monitor/Defibrillator</title>
	 <description>The company is notifying certain LIFEPAK 15 customers of an issue that may cause the device to lock up after a defibrillation shock is delivered. The lock-up condition is defined as a blank monitor display with LED lights on, indicating power to the device, but no response in the keypad and device functions. A device in this condition has the potential to delay delivery of therapy, and this delay in therapy has the potential to result in serious injury or death.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 16:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630455.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630455.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Hill’s Pet Nutrition Voluntarily Recalls Select Canned Dog Food for Excessive Vitamin D</title>
	 <description>Hill’s Pet Nutrition is voluntarily recalling select canned dog food products due to potentially elevated levels of vitamin D. While vitamin D is an essential nutrient for dogs, ingestion of elevated levels can lead to potential health issues depending on the level of vitamin D and the length of exposure, and dogs may exhibit symptoms such as vomiting, loss of appetite, increased thirst, increased urination, excessive drooling, and weight loss. Vitamin D, when consumed at very high levels, can lead to serious health issues in dogs including renal dysfunction. Pet parents with dogs who have consumed any of the products listed and are exhibiting any of these signs should contact their veterinarian.  In most cases, complete recovery is expected after discontinuation of feeding.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 15:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630232.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630232.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Tris Pharma, Inc Expands Its Voluntary Nationwide Retail Recall of Ibuprofen Oral Suspension Drops, USP, 50 mg per 1.25 mL, Due to Higher Concentration of Ibuprofen</title>
	 <description>Monmouth Junction, NJ, Tris Pharma, Inc. is expanding the scope of its November 2018 recall by adding three (3) additional lots of Ibuprofen Oral Suspension Drops, USP, 50 mg per 1.25 mL, to the retail (pharmacy) level. Some units from these batches have been found to have higher levels of Ibuprofen concentration.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 13:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630112.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630112.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
