<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:54:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Chukar Cherries Expands Recall of Ultra Dark Chocolate Product Due to Undeclared Milk</title>
	 <description>Chukar Cherries of Prosser, WA expands a recall on Ultra Dark Chocolate product because it may contain undeclared milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627711.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627711.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Hiland Dairy Announces Voluntary Recall of Hiland Dairy Half-Gallon Whole Chocolate Milk</title>
	 <description>Hiland Dairy is announcing a voluntary recall of half-gallon premium whole milk chocolate that is produced at the Kansas City, Missouri facility, over concerns the products may contain eggnog that could affect those individuals that have sensitivity to egg allergens. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to eggs run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 20:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627712.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627712.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Mylan Expands Its Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Valsartan Tablets, USP, Amlodipine and Valsartan Tablets, USP, and Valsartan and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP, to all Lots Within Expiry Due to The Detection of Trace Amounts of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity Found in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient</title>
	 <description>&#8211; Mylan N.V. (NASDAQ: MYL) today announced that its U.S. based Mylan Pharmaceuticals business is expanding its consumer-level voluntary nationwide recall to include all lots of Valsartan-containing products within expiry. The 104 additional lots include 26 lots of Amlodipine and Valsartan Tablets, USP (including the 5mg/160mg, 10mg/160mg, 5mg/320mg and 10mg/320mg strengths), 51 lots of Valsartan Tablets, USP (including 40 mg, 80 mg, 160 mg and 320 mg strengths), and 27 lots of Valsartan and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP (80mg/12.5mg, 160mg/12.5mg, 160mg/25mg, 320mg/12.5mg and 320mg/25mg strengths).</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 04 Dec 2018 17:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627647.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627647.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Tres Hermanos Bakery Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Telera and Bolillo Breads</title>
	 <description>Tres Hermanos Bakery of Wyoming, MI is recalling its white Telera and Bolillo Mexican salt breads because they may contain undeclared milk. People who have allergies to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 22:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627350.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627350.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Gemini Food Corporation Conducts Voluntary Recall of Imperial Taste Fried Red Onions and Fried Garlic Due to Undeclared Wheat</title>
	 <description>Gemini Food Corporation has voluntarily recalled all Imperial Taste Fried Red Onions &amp; Fried Garlic canisters as a precautionary measure because it&#8217;s missing an allergen statement and the ingredient panel does not include wheat.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 16:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627188.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627188.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>ELM Pet Foods Recall of Dry Dog Food Due to Elevated Levels of Vitamin D</title>
	 <description>ELM Pet Foods, Inc is issuing a voluntary recall of Elm Chicken and Chickpea Recipe dog food because the products could contain elevated levels of Vitamin D.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627139.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627139.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>ANF Pet Inc. Issues Voluntary Precautionary Recall of Dry Dog Food Due to Potentially Elevated Levels of Vitamin D</title>
	 <description>ANF, Inc. is issuing a voluntary recall of select products of ANF Pet Lamb and Rice Dog Food (reference below) due to potentially elevated levels of Vitamin D.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 17:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627087.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627087.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sprout Creek Farm Recalls &#8220;Kinkead&#8221; Cheese due to Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Sprout Creek Farm of Poughkeepsie, New York is recalling 4 wheels of &#8220;Kinkead&#8221; cheese made on 5-10-18, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes. Listeria monocytogenes is an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 16:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627077.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm627077.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Allergen Alert: Kitchen Cravings Strawberry and Mixed Berry Parfaits with Trace Tree Nuts</title>
	 <description>Kwik Trip, Inc. located in La Crosse, WI is recalling Kitchen Cravings Strawberry and Mixed Berry Parfaits in an 8.25 oz. cup because they may contain undeclared traces of cashews or almonds</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 19:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626868.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626868.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Achdut Recalls Multiple Brands of &quot;Tahini&quot; Because It May Be Contaminated with Salmonella</title>
	 <description>Achdut LTD. of Ariel, Israel, is recalling its Tahini products of all packages and
sizes produced on the following dates: April 7th to May 21st 2018, because it
may be contaminated with &lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt;, an organism which can cause serious
and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and
others with weakened immune systems.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626750.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626750.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Teva Pharmaceuticals USA Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of All Amlodipine/Valsartan Combination Tablets and Amlodipine/Valsartan/Hydrochlorothiazide Combination Tablets That Are Within Expiry</title>
	 <description>Teva Pharmaceuticals has initiated a voluntary recall in the United States, to the patient level, of all lots of Amlodipine / Valsartan combination tablets and Amlodipine / Valsartan / Hydrochlorothiazide combination tablets (see table below) due to an impurity detected above specification limits in an active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) manufactured by Mylan India.
The impurity found in Mylan&#8217;s valsartan API is known as N-nitroso-diethylamine (NDEA), which has been classified as a probable human carcinogen. This chemical is typically found in very small amounts in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and certain industrial processes.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 15:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626802.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626802.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sunshine Mills, Inc. Issues Voluntary Recall of Dry Dog Food Due to Potentially Elevated Levels of Vitamin D</title>
	 <description>Sunshine Mills, Inc. is issuing a voluntary recall of select products of Evolve&#61650; Puppy, Sportsman&#8217;s Pride&#61650; Large Breed Puppy and Triumph&#61650; Chicken and Rice Dog Food (reference below) due to potentially elevated levels of Vitamin D.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 12:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626746.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626746.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Pfizer Inc. Issues A Voluntary Nationwide Consumer Level Recall of Six Lots of Thermacare&#174; Heatwraps Due to Leaking Wraps With The Potential For Skin Injuries</title>
	 <description>Pfizer Consumer Healthcare, a division of Pfizer Inc., is voluntarily recalling six lots of ThermaCare&#174; HeatWrap product to the consumer level. Pfizer Consumer Healthcare initiated this recall because product from these lots has a potential to leak ingredients that are contained in the heat cell wrap.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 13:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626671.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626671.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Ottogi America, Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Egg in Product</title>
	 <description>Ottogi America, Inc. of Gardena, California announced today it is recalling 1lb 5.16ounce of Jin Ramen Mild 5pk. (Best Before Aug. 19th 2019) and Jin Ramen Spicy 5pk. (Best Before Aug. 20th 2019) due to undeclared egg as an ingredient on the packages.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to eggs run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 14:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626554.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626554.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>FDA Classifies Field Action Related to Fc 500&#8482; And Epics&#174; As Class 1 Recall Beckman Coulter Life Sciences Committed to Helping Customers Take Prompt, Appropriate Actions</title>
	 <description>Beckman Coulter Life Sciences today announced the previously communicated global voluntary recall launched in January 2018 related to the FC 500&#8482; Series Flow Cytometers (FC 500), COULTER&#174; EPICS&#174; XL&#8482; and COULTER&#174; EPICS&#174; XL-MCL&#8482; Flow Cytometer with System II Software (together referred to as the EPICS) has been classified as Class 1 by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA).</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 12:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626534.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626534.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Fresenius Kabi Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Sodium Chloride Injection, USP, 0.9% Due to Product Labeling Incorrectly Stating Stoppers Do Not Contain Latex</title>
	 <description>Fresenius Kabi USA is voluntarily recalling 163 lots of Sodium Chloride Injection, USP, 0.9%, 10 mL fill in a 10 mL vial and Sodium Chloride Injection, USP, 0.9%, 20 mL fill in a 20 mL vial to the user level. The product insert states that stoppers for both the 10mL and the 20mL vials do not contain natural rubber latex; the tray label for the two vial sizes and the vial label for the 20mL vial also state that the stoppers do not contain latex. The product is being recalled because the stoppers contain natural rubber latex.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 14:39:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626450.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626450.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Mylan Initiates Voluntary Nationwide Recall of 15 Lots of Valsartan Tablets, USP, Amlodipine and Valsartan Tablets, USP, and Valsartan and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP, Due to the Detection of Trace Amounts of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity Found in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient</title>
	 <description>Mylan N.V. (NASDAQ: MYL) today announced that its U.S. based Mylan Pharmaceuticals business is conducting a voluntary nationwide recall to the consumer level of select lots of Valsartan-containing products, including six lots of Amlodipine and Valsartan Tablets, USP (including the 5mg/160mg, 10mg/160mg, and 10mg/320mg strengths), seven lots of Valsartan Tablets, USP (including 40 mg, 80 mg, 160 mg, and 320 mg strengths), and two lots of Valsartan and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP 320mg/25mg strength.  These products are being recalled due to detected trace amounts of an impurity, N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA) contained in the API Valsartan, USP, manufactured by Mylan Laboratories Limited. NDEA is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, and has been classified as a probable human carcinogen according to the International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC).</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626367.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626367.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>First Source Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Pecan and Cashew in Chocolate and Nut Tray</title>
	 <description>First Source of Tonawanda, NY, is voluntarily recalling Chocolate and Nut Tray because it contains undeclared tree nuts, pecan and cashew. People who have an allergy or sensitivity to tree nuts (Pecan &amp; Cashew) run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626380.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626380.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Jay Robb Enterprises Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk Allergen in Unflavored Egg White Protein</title>
	 <description>Jay Robb Enterprises is recalling Jay Robb Unflavored Egg White Protein Product,
manufactured by Agropur MSI, LLC of La Crosse, Wisconsin, because it may contain
undeclared milk allergen. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the
risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626168.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626168.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Roche Diagnostics to Replace CoaguChek&#174; XS PT Test Strips</title>
	 <description>Roche Diagnostics will be proactively replacing all CoaguChek XS PT Test Strips in the United States.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 09:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626140.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626140.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
