<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:32:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Mylan Initiates Voluntary Nationwide Recall of 15 Lots of Valsartan Tablets, USP, Amlodipine and Valsartan Tablets, USP, and Valsartan and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP, Due to the Detection of Trace Amounts of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity Found in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient</title>
	 <description>Mylan N.V. (NASDAQ: MYL) today announced that its U.S. based Mylan Pharmaceuticals business is conducting a voluntary nationwide recall to the consumer level of select lots of Valsartan-containing products, including six lots of Amlodipine and Valsartan Tablets, USP (including the 5mg/160mg, 10mg/160mg, and 10mg/320mg strengths), seven lots of Valsartan Tablets, USP (including 40 mg, 80 mg, 160 mg, and 320 mg strengths), and two lots of Valsartan and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP 320mg/25mg strength.  These products are being recalled due to detected trace amounts of an impurity, N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA) contained in the API Valsartan, USP, manufactured by Mylan Laboratories Limited. NDEA is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, and has been classified as a probable human carcinogen according to the International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC).</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626367.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626367.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>First Source Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Pecan and Cashew in Chocolate and Nut Tray</title>
	 <description>First Source of Tonawanda, NY, is voluntarily recalling Chocolate and Nut Tray because it contains undeclared tree nuts, pecan and cashew. People who have an allergy or sensitivity to tree nuts (Pecan &amp; Cashew) run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626380.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626380.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Jay Robb Enterprises Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk Allergen in Unflavored Egg White Protein</title>
	 <description>Jay Robb Enterprises is recalling Jay Robb Unflavored Egg White Protein Product,
manufactured by Agropur MSI, LLC of La Crosse, Wisconsin, because it may contain
undeclared milk allergen. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the
risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626168.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626168.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Roche Diagnostics to Replace CoaguChek&#174; XS PT Test Strips</title>
	 <description>Roche Diagnostics will be proactively replacing all CoaguChek XS PT Test Strips in the United States.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 09:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626140.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626140.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>The Quaker Oats Company Issues Voluntary Recall of a Small Quantity of Cap&#8217;n Crunch&#8217;s Peanut Butter Crunch Cereal Distributed to Five Target Stores Due to Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>The Quaker Oats Company, a subsidiary of PepsiCo, Inc., today announced a voluntary recall of a small quantity of Cap&#8217;n Crunch&#8217;s Peanut Butter Crunch cereal due to the potential presence of Salmonella. While the potentially affected product only reached five specific Target stores and is limited to 21 boxes of one variety with two Best Before Dates, Quaker is initiating the voluntary recall to protect public health.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 22:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626142.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626142.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Chukar Cherries Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in 7.5 Oz Amaretto Rainier Chocolate Cherries Pouches</title>
	 <description>Chukar Cherries of Prosser, WA is recalling 7.5oz Amaretto Rainier Chocolate Cherries because they may contain undeclared milk.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 21:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626137.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626137.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Recall of Green Cedar Dairy Ackawi Cheese Bearing a Sell by Date of March 26, 2019 or Later</title>
	 <description>Routine samples of the Green Cedar Ackawi cheese collected and tested by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration and the Michigan Department of Agriculture and Rural Development tested positive for the presence of &lt;em&gt;Listeria monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt;.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 20:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626134.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm626134.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Nor Cal Food Solutions, LLC ISSUES ALLERGY ALERT ON UNDECLARED Tree Nut &#8211; Walnut in The Purveyors Kitchen - Pumpkin Pesto Tapenade</title>
	 <description>Nor Cal Food Solutions, LLC of Auburn, CA is announcing a recall of 567 cases of Pumpkin Pesto Tapenade, manufactured by Purveyors Kitchen, because it contains an undeclared tree nut (walnut). People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to tree nuts (walnuts) run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 17:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625923.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625923.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>The Pictsweet Company Recalls 8-ounce Steam&#8217;ables Asparagus Spears due to Potential for &lt;em&gt;Listeria Monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt;</title>
	 <description>The Pictsweet Company has recalled 1,872 cases of Pictsweet Farms 8-ounce Steam&#8217;ables Asparagus Spears because they have the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 16:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625788.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625788.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Oscor Inc. Issues Recall Product Expansion of TB &#8211; Temporary Bipolar Pacing Lead (Unshrouded 2 mm Pins Models)</title>
	 <description>On September 26, 2018 Oscor notified customers of a recall for certain lots (Recall No. 1035166- 09/07/2018-01-R) of TB Unshrouded Bipolar Pacing Leads. As part of the recall correction activities, Oscor is retrieving any remaining inventory out in the field. The recall scope is being expanded to include expired inventory for devices distributed between December 21, 2011 to May 17, 2018. The recall expansion is to ensure proper disposition of expired units. The FDA has been notified and is aware Oscor Inc. is voluntarily taking this action.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 15:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625786.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625786.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Alebrije Dist Wholesale Recalls Quesillo Queseria &#8220;La Milagrosa&#8221; and &#8220;Alebrije Cheese&#8221; Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>ALEBRIJE DIST WHOLESALE is collaborating with health of&#64257;cials due to a positive &#64257;nding of Salmonella in a sample of Quesillo &#8220;Queseria La Milagrosa&#8221;. ALEBRIJE DIST WHOLESALE is voluntarily recalling the amount of 100 kilos of Quesillo &#8220;Queseria La Milagrosa&#8221;. While &#8220;Alebrije Cheese&#8221; has not been found positive for Salmonella, ALEBRIJE DIST WHOLESALE has decided to voluntarily recall the speci&#64257;c 498 &#8220;Alebrije Cheese&#8221; pieces that were imported during the same period out of an abundance of caution.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 20:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625686.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625686.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Recall of Bittersweet &amp; Feve Chocolate Bars Due to High Levels of Milk Allergens</title>
	 <description>Today, Recchiuti Confections (San Francisco, CA) discovered two batches of their Bittersweet Chocolate Bar and two batches of their Feve Chocolate Bar contain high levels of milk protein after FDA sampling. No illnesses have been reported to date. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products. The chocolate bars can be enjoyed if you do not have milk allergies or sensitivities. Recchiuti Confections is issuing an immediate recall for bars with the following lot codes and best buy dates:</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 21:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625679.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625679.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>In Association With Sunshine Mills, Lidl Voluntarily Recalls Orlando Brand Grain Free Chicken &amp; Chickpea Superfood Recipe Dog Food Due to Elevated Levels of Vitamin D.</title>
	 <description>In association with Sunshine Mills, Lidl is voluntarily recalling specific lots of Orlando brand Grain Free Chicken &amp; Chickpea Superfood Recipe Dog Food because the products may contain elevated levels of Vitamin D.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 15:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625631.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625631.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Natural Life Pet Products Expands Recall of Dry Food Due to Elevated Levels of Vitamin D</title>
	 <description>We regret to inform you that Natural Life&#174; Chicken &amp; Potato dry dog food has been confirmed to contain elevated levels of Vitamin D.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625624.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625624.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sandoz Inc. Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of One Lot of Losartan Potassium and Hydrochlorothiazide Due to the Detection of Trace Amounts of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity Found in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient (API)</title>
	 <description>Sandoz Inc. is voluntarily recalling one lot of Losartan Potassium Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP 100mg/25mg to the consumer level. This product is being recalled due to the trace amount of an impurity, N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA) contained in the API Losartan, USP manufactured by Zhejiang Huahai Pharmaceutical Co. Ltd. Sandoz Inc. Losartan Potassium Hydrochlorothiazide product is manufactured by Lek Pharmaceuticals dd, Ljubljana, Slovenia. This impurity, which is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, has been classified as a probable human carcinogen as per International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC).</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 09:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625492.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625492.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Baked Potatoes with Cheddar Cheese and Bacon (2 Count) Mis-Labeled as Herb Roasted Potatoes</title>
	 <description>Ukrop&#8217;s Homestyle Foods is voluntarily recalling Baked Potatoes with Cheddar Cheese and Bacon (2 count), as the product is mislabeled Herb Roasted Potatoes (see photo attached).</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 20:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625462.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625462.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Wegmans Food Markets, Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Wegmans Pumpkin Loaf, 11 oz., and Wegmans Placek Coffee Cake, 11 oz. and 22 oz.</title>
	 <description>Wegmans has initiated a voluntary recall of the following products because they may contain milk not declared on the label. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 19:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625327.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625327.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Kadesh Incorporation Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Puriton Eye Relief Drops Due to Non-Sterile Production Conditions</title>
	 <description>Kadesh, Inc. of Garden Grove, CA is voluntarily recalling all lots of Puriton Eye Relief Drops, 0.5 oz. (15ml) bottle, UPC 7 36972 1679 0, to the consumer level. During a recent FDA inspection, investigators observed that ophthalmic drugs, which are required to be sterile, are manufactured without necessary production controls and conditions to assure sterility.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 14:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625305.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625305.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sprout Creek Farm Recalls &quot;Margie&quot; Cheese Due to Listeria Monocytogenes</title>
	 <description>Sprout Creek Farm of Poughkeepsie, New York is recalling 132 wheels of &quot;Margie&quot; cheese, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes. Listeria monocytogenes is an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 22:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625254.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625254.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Duncan Hines Classic White, Classic Butter Golden, Signature Confetti and Classic Yellow Cake Mixes Recalled Due to Potential Presence of Salmonella</title>
	 <description>Conagra Brands is collaborating with health officials in connection with a positive finding of Salmonella in a retail sample of Duncan Hines Classic White cake mix that may be linked to a Salmonella outbreak that is currently being investigated by CDC and FDA. While it has not been definitively concluded that this product is linked to the outbreak and the investigation is still ongoing, Conagra has decided to voluntarily recall the specific Duncan Hines variety identified (Classic White) and three other varieties (Classic Butter Golden, Signature Confetti and Classic Yellow) made during the same time period out of an abundance of caution.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 19:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625144.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm625144.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
