<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 19:04:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Allergy Alert Issued by Santa Rosa Whole Foods Market for Undeclared Walnut, Milk and Eggs in “Hipster Chipster” Cookies</title>
	 <description>The Santa Rosa Whole Foods Market store is voluntarily recalling eight packages of its “Hipster Chipster” cookies because they contain undeclared tree nut (walnut), milk, and egg allergens that were not listed on the product label.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 19:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630684.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630684.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Dr. Reddy&#39;s Laboratories Continues its Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Levetiracetam in 0.54% Sodium Chloride Injection 1500mg/100mL Due to Mislabeling</title>
	 <description>Dr. Reddy’s Laboratories Ltd. (BSE: 500124, NSE: DRREDDY, NYSE: RDY) announced that it’s wholly owned subsidiary, Dr Reddy’s Laboratories, Inc is continuing its voluntary nationwide recall of lot ABD807 of Levetiracetram in 0.54% Sodium Chloride Injection, 1,500 mg/100 mL (15 mg/mL) single-dose infusion bags to the hospital level in U.S.A.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 10:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630542.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630542.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Stryker Launches Voluntary Field Action for Specific Units of the LIFEPAK® 15 Monitor/Defibrillator</title>
	 <description>The company is notifying certain LIFEPAK 15 customers of an issue that may cause the device to lock up after a defibrillation shock is delivered. The lock-up condition is defined as a blank monitor display with LED lights on, indicating power to the device, but no response in the keypad and device functions. A device in this condition has the potential to delay delivery of therapy, and this delay in therapy has the potential to result in serious injury or death.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 16:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630455.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630455.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Hill’s Pet Nutrition Voluntarily Recalls Select Canned Dog Food for Excessive Vitamin D</title>
	 <description>Hill’s Pet Nutrition is voluntarily recalling select canned dog food products due to potentially elevated levels of vitamin D. While vitamin D is an essential nutrient for dogs, ingestion of elevated levels can lead to potential health issues depending on the level of vitamin D and the length of exposure, and dogs may exhibit symptoms such as vomiting, loss of appetite, increased thirst, increased urination, excessive drooling, and weight loss. Vitamin D, when consumed at very high levels, can lead to serious health issues in dogs including renal dysfunction. Pet parents with dogs who have consumed any of the products listed and are exhibiting any of these signs should contact their veterinarian.  In most cases, complete recovery is expected after discontinuation of feeding.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 15:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630232.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630232.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Tris Pharma, Inc Expands Its Voluntary Nationwide Retail Recall of Ibuprofen Oral Suspension Drops, USP, 50 mg per 1.25 mL, Due to Higher Concentration of Ibuprofen</title>
	 <description>Monmouth Junction, NJ, Tris Pharma, Inc. is expanding the scope of its November 2018 recall by adding three (3) additional lots of Ibuprofen Oral Suspension Drops, USP, 50 mg per 1.25 mL, to the retail (pharmacy) level. Some units from these batches have been found to have higher levels of Ibuprofen concentration.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 13:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630112.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630112.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Nature’s Rx Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Silver Bullet 10x to Undeclared PDE-5 Inhibitors in the Product</title>
	 <description>Nature’s Rx is voluntarily recalling quantity lots of Silver Bullet 10x, description of dosage form to the hospital, retail or consumer level. This recall has been initiated because the product was found to contain undeclared sildenafil and tadalafil, the active ingredient in Viagra and Cialis respectively, which are PDE-5 inhibitors. The undeclared PDE-5 inhibitors in the product may pose serious health risks because consumers with underlying medical issues may take the products without knowing that they can cause serious harm or interact in dangerous ways with other drugs they may be taking</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 12:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630104.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630104.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Purina Animal Nutrition Voluntarily Recalling Purina® Honor® Show Chow® Showlamb Grower Due to Elevated Copper Level</title>
	 <description>)– Purina Animal Nutrition is voluntarily recalling two lots of Purina® Honor® Show Chow® Showlamb Grower due to elevated copper levels. The feed is packaged in purple branded Purina Honor Show Chow bags.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 15:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630003.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630003.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Oskri Organics Corporation Recalls All Nut Butters because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Oskri Organics Corporation of Lake Mills, WI is recalling ALL Oskri Corporation manufactured nut butters. This recall has been initiated due to positive test results for Listeria monocytogenes found in multiple Oskri Corporation manufactured nut butters.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 14:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630036.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm630036.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>SL: Recall of Thrive Market Nut Butters Due to Potential Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Thrive Market, Inc, is recalling all unexpired lots of the Thrive Market-branded nut butters listed below (“Product(s)”) due to the potential for contamination with Listeria monocytogenes. On January 21, 2019, one of our  suppliers notified us that it was issuing a recall of all nut butters it has manufactured since January 2018 because of a positive test for Listeria monocytogenes in recent lots.  Because the safety of our members is our absolute priority, we are expanding on our supplier’s recall and are voluntarily recalling all unexpired lots of all  Thrive Market-branded nut butters manufactured by this supplier.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 18:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629819.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629819.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Mrs. Grissom’s Salads Issues a Voluntary Recall</title>
	 <description>For immediate release- January 18,2019 – Nashville, TN – Mrs. Grissom’s Salads is voluntarily recalling a single days production of Mrs. Grissom’s SELECT Old Fashioned Pimento Cheese because of a labeling issue. Product produced on December 13, 2018 may have been packaged incorrectly, with the correct Pimento Cheese label on top lid, but a Chicken salad label on the container. The Pimento Cheese may contain allergens not listed on the products ingredient label, Specifically Milk.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 16:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629807.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629807.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Jac. Vandenberg, Inc. Recalls Fresh Peaches, Fresh Nectarines and Fresh Plums Because They May Be Contaminted with Listeria Monocytogenes</title>
	 <description>Jac. Vandenberg, Inc. of Yonkers, New York is recalling 1,727 cartons of Fresh Peaches, 1,207 cartons of Fresh Nectarines and 365 cartons of Fresh Plums because they have the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 10:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629797.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629797.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Satur Farms’ Recall of Baby Spinach Affects Prepared Food Items from Whole Foods Market Stores in Eight States</title>
	 <description>In response to a recall by Satur Farms, Whole Foods Market is voluntarily recalling various prepared foods items in eight states containing baby spinach because of a potential contamination of Salmonella.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 21:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629788.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629788.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Product Recall Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Satur Farms, 3705 Alvah&#39;s Lane, Cutchogue, NY 11935 is voluntarily recalling Baby Spinach and Mesclun with the specific lot numbers listed below because it has the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people and others with weakened immune systems. Healthy persons infected with Salmonella often experience fever, diarrhea (which may be bloody), nausea, vomiting and abdominal pain.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629755.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629755.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>General Mills Recalls Five Pound Bags of Gold Medal Unbleached Flour</title>
	 <description>General Mills announced today a voluntary national recall of five-pound bags of its Gold Medal Unbleached Flour with a better if used by date of April 20, 2020. The recall is being issued for the potential presence of Salmonella which was discovered during sampling of the five-pound bag product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629754.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629754.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Perrigo Issues Allergy Alert For Simple Truth Organic Banana, Strawberry &amp; Apple Puree With Nonfat Greek Yogurt</title>
	 <description>Perrigo Company, in coordination with The Kroger Company, is initiating a voluntary recall of one production lot of Simple Truth Organic Banana, Strawberry &amp; Apple Fruit Puree with Nonfat Greek Yogurt (LOT L8159, best by 08/06/2019, produced in Spain) due to improper labeling that does not indicate the presence of milk, posing a potential risk to consumers with milk allergies.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 19:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629753.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629753.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>UPDATED: Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP and Losartan Potassium and Hydrochlorothiazide Tablets, USP</title>
	 <description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited is expanding its voluntary recall from 10 lots of Losartan potassium tablets USP to include 6 lots of Losartan potassium and hydrochlorothiazide tablets, USP, to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in an active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) manufactured by Hetero Labs Limited.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 16:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629693.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629693.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Ottogi America, Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Egg in Products</title>
	 <description>Ottogi America, Inc. announced today it is recalling below 21 items due to a possibility of containing egg ingredient undeclared on the packages.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to eggs run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction of they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 21:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629663.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629663.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Prinston Pharmaceutical Inc. issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Irbesartan and Irbesartan HCTZ Tablets Due to detection of a Trace Amount of Unexpected Impurity, N- nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA) in the Products</title>
	 <description>-- Prinston
Pharmaceutical Inc., dba Solco Healthcare LLC., has initiated a voluntary recall of one (1) lot of Irbesartan and seven (7) lots of Irbesartan HCTZ Tablets to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amount of an unexpected impurity found in an active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) manufactured by Zhejiang Huahai Pharmaceuticals.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 14:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629627.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629627.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>RXBAR Recalls Certain Varieties of Bars Due to a Potential Undeclared Peanut Allergen</title>
	 <description>RXBAR is voluntarily recalling certain varieties of bars because they may contain undeclared peanuts. People who have peanut allergies run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:39:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629527.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629527.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Voluntary Recall Notice of El Guapo Chile Habanero and Chile Pasilla-Ancho Pouches Due to Unlabeled Peanut Allergen</title>
	 <description>Mojave Foods Corporation is initiating a voluntary recall of El Guapo Chile Habanero and Chile Pasilla-Ancho pouches due to an unlabeled peanut allergen.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 20:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629522.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629522.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
