<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 11:45:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries, Inc. Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Vecuronium Bromide for Injection Due to the Presence of Particulate Matter Identified as Glass</title>
	 <description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries, Inc. (SPII), a wholly owned subsidiary of Sun Pharmaceutical Industries, Ltd. is voluntarily recalling three lots of Vecuronium Bromide for Injection, 10 mg (lyophilized powder), and one lot of Vecuronium Bromide for Injection, 20 mg (lyophilized powder) to the hospital level. The Vecuronium Bromide for Injection has been found to contain particulate matter identified as glass.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 11:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629328.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629328.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Grand Strand Sandwich Company Recalls Lunch Box Sandwiches Italian Subs Lunch Box Sandwiches Ham &amp; Swiss Croissants And Lunch Box Sandwiches Ham &amp; Cheese Due To Possible &lt;em&gt;Listeria Monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt; Contamination</title>
	 <description>– Grand Strand Sandwich is recalling Lunch Box Italian Subs, Lunch Box Ham &amp; Swiss Croissants and Lunch Box Ham &amp; Cheese Frozen Wedges due to a potential contamination of &lt;em&gt;Listeria Monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt;.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 21:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629322.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629322.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Hy-Vee Voluntarily Recalls Cheesecakes Made with Diamond Crystal Mix</title>
	 <description>Hy-Vee, Inc., based in West Des Moines, Iowa, is voluntarily recalling its cheesecakes made with Diamond Crystal Brands cheesecake mix due to the potential that they may be contaminated with Salmonella. The potential for contamination was brought to Hy-Vee’s attention today after receiving a letter from the supplier. The voluntary recall includes 32 varieties of cheesecakes in both 8-ounce and 32-ounce packages with best if used by dates of Dec. 6, 2018, through Jan. 11, 2019. No illnesses have been reported to date.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 13:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629310.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629310.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Lupin Pharmaceuticals, Inc. Issues Voluntary Recall of Ceftriaxone for Injection USP, 250mg, 500mg, 1g and 2g</title>
	 <description>Lupin Pharmaceuticals, Inc. is voluntarily recalling 5 lots of Ceftriaxone for Injection, USP, 250mg, 10 lots of Ceftriaxone for Injection, USP, 500mg, 24 lots of Ceftriaxone for Injection, USP, 1g and 3 lots of Ceftriaxone for Injection, USP 2g, to the hospital/physician level. The products have been found to contain visual grey particulate matter in reconstituted vials.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 18:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629298.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629298.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Olde York Potato Chips Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in One Lot of Clancy&#39;s Wavy Potato Chips 10 Oz</title>
	 <description>Olde York Potato Chips of
Brampton, Ontario is recalling Clancy&#39;s Wavy Potato Chips 10 oz (UPC 0 41498 16306 8) with the specific lot code BEST If Used By FEB 22 19 1A6 because they may contain undeclared milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products. No other lot codes and no other products are involved in this action.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 17:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629293.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629293.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Shamrock Farms Issues Voluntary Recall of 2% Reduced Fat Vanilla Half Gallon Milk Due to Undeclared Almonds</title>
	 <description>Shamrock Farms of Phoenix, Arizona is issuing a voluntary recall of Shamrock Farms 2% Reduced Fat Vanilla Half Gallon Milk with Best Before Date 3/16/2019. The recall comes after a product retain of Shamrock Farms 2% Reduced Fat Vanilla Half Gallon Milk with Use By 03/16/19 Time Stamp 08:18-11:13 04-05 #1, tested positive for an undeclared tree nut (almond) allergen.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 17:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629295.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629295.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited Expands Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP</title>
	 <description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited is expanding its voluntary recall from 2 lots of Losartan potassium tablets USP to a total of 10 lots, to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in an active 
pharmaceutical ingredient (API) manufactured by Hetero Labs Limited.  Torrent is only recalling lots of losartan-containing products that contain N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA) above the acceptable daily intake levels released by the FDA.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 13:29:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629261.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629261.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Results RNA LLC Issues Voluntary Worldwide/Nationwide Recall of Lubrisine Eye Drops Due to Manufacturing Sterility Concerns and Undeclared Colloidal Silver</title>
	 <description>Results RNA LLC is 
voluntarily recalling Lubrisine Eye Drops to the healthcare practitioner, retail or consumer level. This product, in a recent FDA inspection, was found to be manufactured using practices that do not support its sterility and contained undeclared colloidal silver.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 20:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629256.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629256.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Oskri Organics Corporation Recalls Oskri Organic Sunflower Butter Lot #099, Oskri Tahini Butter Lot #193 and Thrive Sunflower Butter Lot  #233 Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Oskri Organics Corporation of Lake Mills, WI is recalling Oskri Organic Sunflower 
Butter Lot # 099, Oskri Tahini Butter LOT # 193 and Thrive Sunflower Butter LOT # 233, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 15:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629246.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629246.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Aurobindo Pharma USA, Inc. Initiates Voluntary Nationwide Consumer Level Recall of 80 Lots of Amlodipine Valsartan Tablets USP, Valsartan HCTZ Tablets, USP and Valsartan Tablets USP, Due to the Detection of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity</title>
	 <description>Aurobindo Pharma USA, Inc. is conducting a voluntary recall of 80 lots of Amlodipine Valsartan Tablets USP, Valsartan HCTZ Tablets, USP and Valsartan Tablets USP to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in the finished drug product.   The impurity detected in the finished drug product is N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA), which is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, and has been classified as a probable human carcinogen as per International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC) classification. To date, Aurobindo Pharma USA, Inc. has not received any reports of adverse events related to this recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 22:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629213.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629213.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Apio Inc. Expands Voluntary Recall of Eat Smart Salad Shake Ups Single-Serve Bowls</title>
	 <description>Apio Inc. of Guadalupe, California is expanding a voluntary recall of Eat Smart Salad Shake Ups single-serve bowls. The recall comes after the Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA) informed the company that another random sample of Eat Smart Salad Shake Ups Sweet Kale/Chou Frise Doux 156 gr. single-serve bowls (5.5oz) with Best Before Date of Dec 29, 2018, Lot 112 346, tested positive for Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 17:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629152.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629152.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Columbia River Natural Pet Foods Inc. Voluntarily Expands Recall to Include Cow Pie and Chicken &amp; Vegetables Fresh Frozen Meats for Dogs and Cats Due to Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Columbia River Natural Pet Foods of Vancouver, WA is voluntarily expanding their current recall to include additional products: 261 packages of Cow Pie Lot # 72618 and 82 packages of Chicken &amp; Vegetables Lot# 111518 fresh frozen meats for dogs and cats, produced in July 2018 and November 2018, due to their potential to be contaminated with Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 09:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629119.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629119.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Funky Chunky, Llc Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Almond and Cashew Tree-Nut in 10 Oz. Nutty Choco Pop Found in Chocolate Popcorn Gift Box, Holiday Crowd Pleaser and Crowd Pleaser Gifts</title>
	 <description>Funky Chunky, LLC of Eden Prairie, MN is recalling 10 oz Nutty Choco Pop Gift Box, 50 oz. Holiday Crowd Pleaser and 50 oz. Crowd Pleaser, because it may contain undeclared Almond and Cashew Tree Nut. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to Almonds and Cashews run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629106.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm629106.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Inspired Organics Issues Voluntary Recall of Organic Nut &amp; Seed Butters Due to Potential Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Inspired Organics, LLC has issued a voluntary recall of Organic Almond, Peanut, and Tahini Butters due to potential contamination of Listeria monocytogenes. Listeria monocytogenes is an organism, which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short- term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 17:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628989.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628989.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Terrific Care, LLC. / Medex Supply Dist, Inc. issues Nationwide Recall of CoaguChek Test Strips</title>
	 <description>On 12/19/2018, Terrific Care, LLC. / Medex Supply Dist, Inc. initiated a nationwide recall of Roche CoaguChek test strips distributed directly to U.S. consumers by Terrific Care, LLC. / Medex Supply Dist, Inc. The products have been found to inaccurately report high INR test results.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 15:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628976.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628976.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP</title>
	 <description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited is voluntarily recalling 2 lots of Losartan potassium tablets, USP to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in an active pharmaceutical ingredient (API) manufactured by Hetero Labs Limited. The impurity detected in the API is N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA), which is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, and has been classified as a probable human carcinogen as per International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC) classification.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 14:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628966.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628966.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Wegmans Issues Voluntary Recall of Fresh Cauliflower Rice, Veggie/Cauliflower Rice Blend and Stir-Fry Mix with Cauliflower</title>
	 <description>Rochester, NY – Wegmans Food Markets, Inc. has issued a voluntary recall of fresh Cauliflower Rice, Veggie Cauliflower Rice Blend and Stir-Fry Mix with Cauliflower, sold in the produce department between 12/7/18 and 12/18/18, because it may be contaminated with Escherichia coli O157:H7 bacteria (E. Coli O157:H7). E. coli O157:H7 causes a diarrheal illness often with bloody stools. Although most healthy adults can recover completely within a week, some people can develop a form of kidney failure called Hemolytic Uremic Syndrome (HUS). HUS is most likely to occur in young children and the elderly. The condition can lead to serious kidney damage and even death.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 09:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628826.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628826.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Medtronic Announces Worldwide Voluntary Field Corrective Action; Company Issues Software Update for Puritan Bennett™ 980 (Pb980) Ventilator Series</title>
	 <description>Medtronic (NYSE:MDT) is notifying customers worldwide of a voluntary field corrective action for its Puritan Bennett™ 980 (PB980) ventilator series.
Medtronic initiated this field action on September 19, 2018.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 22:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628812.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628812.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Adam Bros. Farming, Inc. Recalls Red and Green Leaf Lettuce and Cauliflower Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Adam Bros. Farming, Inc. of Santa Maria, California is recalling red leaf lettuce, green leaf lettuce and cauliflower harvested on November 27 through 30, 2018 out of an abundance of caution, because it may be contaminated with Escherichia coli O157:H7 bacteria (E. Coli O157:H7).</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 22:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628722.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628722.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Atherstone Foods Inc Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Soy in “Greens and Grains Hummus and Quinoa Tabouleh Wrap”</title>
	 <description>ATHERSTONE FOODS INC of Richmond, CA is recalling 14.6 ounce (414g) Greens and Grains Hummus and Quinoa Tabouleh Wrap, because it may contain undeclared soy, people who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to soy run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 22:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628719.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm628719.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
