<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 11:53:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>AurobindoPharma USA, Inc. Initiates a Voluntary Nationwide Consumer Level Recall Expansion of 38 Lots of Amlodipine Valsartan Tablets USP and Valsartan Tablets, USP due to the detection of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity.</title>
	 <description>AurobindoPharma USA, Inc. is conducting a voluntary recall expansion of 38 lots of Valsartan and Amlodipine and Valsartan tablets to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity found in the finished drug product. This recall is an expansion of the recall initiated 12/31/18  The impurity detected in the finished drug product is N-nitrosodiethylamine (NDEA), which is a substance that occurs naturally in certain foods, drinking water, air pollution, and industrial processes, and has been classified as a probable human carcinogen as per International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC) classification. The expansion relates to lots distributed under the labels for AurobindoPharma USA, Inc. and Acetris Health, LLC.  To date, AurobindoPharma USA, Inc. has not received any reports of adverse events related to this recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 11:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632442.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632442.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Camber Pharmaceuticals, Inc. Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Losartan Potassium Tablets, USP, 25 mg, 50 mg and 100 mg Due to the Detection of Trace Amounts of N-Nitroso N-Methyl 4-amino butyric acid (NMBA) Impurity found in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient (API)</title>
	 <description>Camber Pharmaceuticals, Inc. is recalling 87 lots of Losartan Tablets USP 25 mg, 50 mg, and 100 mg to consumer level. This recall was prompted due to the detection of trace amounts of N-Nitroso N-Methyl 4-amino butyric acid (NMBA) a possible process impurity or contaminant in an active pharmaceutical ingredient, manufactured by Hetero Labs Limited, Unit – I (API manufacturer).</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 19:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632395.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632395.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Joy Gourmet Foods LLC  Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Sulfites</title>
	 <description>Joy Gourmet Foods Inc. of Maspeth, NY is recalling its Joy Brand Chutneys and Pastes products because they contain undeclared sulfites.. People who have allergies to sulfites run the risk of serious or
life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.
The recalled Joy Brand Chutneys and Pastes were distributed in NY, NJ,and CT in retail stores.The products comes in 8 oz,14 oz,16 oz, and 26 oz, 32 oz. clear glass jar packages and marked on the labels as follows:</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 17:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632223.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632223.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>UTZ Quality Foods Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Bachman 10 Ounce Twist</title>
	 <description>Utz Quality Foods, LLC., is voluntarily recalling a specific expiration date code of Bachman 10 oz Twist Pretzel packages due to undeclared milk. This recall was initiated after reviewing production records which identified a small number of packages were mislabeled.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 14:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632095.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632095.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>ICU Medical Issues a Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Certain Lots of ChemoLock™ and ChemoClave® Vial Spikes Due to the Potential for Burr Particulate</title>
	 <description>ICU Medical, Inc. today announced a voluntary recall of certain lots of ChemoLock™ and ChemoClave® Vial Spikes due to the potential for burr particulate originating from the protective cap used in the assembly of the device</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 11:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632065.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632065.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Southern Specialties Voluntarily Recalls Bagged Green Beans and Butternut Squash Distributed in Southeast because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Southern Specialties Inc. of Pompano Beach, Florida is voluntarily recalling select bags of Marketside brand green beans and butternut squash because they have the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 18:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632027.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632027.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Golean Detox USA Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Golean DETOX Capsules Due to Presence of Undeclared Sibutramine and Phenolphthalein</title>
	 <description>Golean Detox USA, Charlotte, NC is voluntarily recalling all lots within expiry of Golean DETOX capsules to the consumer level. FDA analysis has found Golean DETOX capsules to be tainted with undeclared sibutramine and phenolphthalein. Sibutramine is an appetite suppressant that was withdrawn from the U.S. market due to safety concerns. Phenolphthalein was once an ingredient used in over-the-counter laxatives, but because of concerns of carcinogenicity is not currently approved for marketing in the United States. The presence of sibutramine and phenolphthalein in Golean DETOX renders it an unapproved drug for which safety and efficacy has not been established and, therefore, subject to recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 14:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632004.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm632004.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>B&amp;G Foods Voluntarily Recalls a Limited Number of Jars of Victoria® Marinara Sauce Due to Possible Undeclared Cashew</title>
	 <description>B&amp;G Foods announced today it is voluntarily recalling 1,280 cases of a single date code of 40 oz. Victoria Marinara Sauce, with a “best by” date of 03/06/2022, after learning that the product may contain cashew allergens that are not declared on the product’s ingredient statement. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to cashew run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product. There is no health risk associated with this product for individuals without an allergy to tree nuts.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631992.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631992.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Macleods Pharmaceuticals Limited Issues Voluntary Nationwide Consumer Level Recall of One Lot (BLM 715A) of Losartan Potassium/Hydrochlorothiazide Combination Tablets 100mg/25mg Due to detection of NDEA (N-Nitrosodiethylamine) Impurity</title>
	 <description>Macleods Pharmaceuticals Limited is voluntarily recalling one lot of Losartan Potassium/Hydrochlorothiazide combination tablets 100mg/25mg to the consumer level due to the detection of trace amounts of an unexpected impurity (NDEA) found in finished product manufactured with active pharmaceutical ingredient made by Hetero Labs Limited.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 08:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631880.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631880.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Meijer Recalls Mint Meijer Brand Ultimate Chocolate Mint Chip Cookies Due to an Undeclared Soy Allergen</title>
	 <description>Meijer is announcing a voluntary recall of its Meijer brand Ultimate Chocolate Mint Chip Cookies because soy it is not properly declared on the label.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 16:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631919.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631919.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Jacques Torres Manufacturing LLC Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk Allergens in “Jacques” Big Daddy Dark Chocolate Bar</title>
	 <description>Jacques Torres Manufacturing LLC of Brooklyn, New York is recalling its 2.2 lbs. (1kg), “Jacques” Big Daddy Dark Chocolate Bar, because it contains undeclared milk allergens.  Consumers who are allergic to milk allergens may run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 21:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631689.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631689.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Gilda Industries, Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Butter Pound Cake</title>
	 <description>Gilda Industries, Inc voluntarily recalls select code dates and manufacturing lot numbers of Panque – Butter pound cake because they may contain undeclared milk . People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of a serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume the product contained inside the recalled panque –butter pound cake</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 18:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631720.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631720.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Concord Fresh Success Recall Mild Salsa Seasoning Mix Due To Undeclared Milk Allergen</title>
	 <description>Concord Foods, LLC of Brockton, Massachusetts is recalling Concord Fresh Success Mild Salsa Seasoning Mix because it may contain undeclared milk allergen. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk allergen run the risk of serious or lifethreatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 18:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631634.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631634.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Chukar Cherries Expands Recall Of Amaretto Rainier Ultra Dark Chocolate Cherries Pouches Due To Undeclared Milk</title>
	 <description>February 18, 2019, Chukar Cherries of Prosser, WA is recalling 7.5oz Amaretto Rainier Ultra Dark Chocolate Cherries because they may contain undeclared milk. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 18:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631537.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631537.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Smoked Alaska Seafoods, Inc. Recalls 6.5 oz Jars &amp; Cans of Smoked Silver Salmon Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Smoked Alaska Seafoods, Inc. of Wasilla, AK is recalling all jars and cans of Smoked Silver Salmon in 6.5 oz. containers with the production code of AL81111133 on the bottom of the jar/can because it has the potential to be contaminated with Clostridium botulinum, a bacterium which can cause life-threatening illness or death. Consumers are warned not to use the product even if it does not look or smell spoiled.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2019 10:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631531.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631531.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Nature’s Path Foods Recalls A Specific Production Run Of Envirokidz Choco Chimps, Gorilla Munch And Jungle Munch Cereals Due To Undeclared Gluten</title>
	 <description>Today, Nature’s Path Foods announced a voluntary recall of a specific production run of EnviroKidz Choco Chimps, Gorilla Munch and Jungle Munch cereals for they may contain undeclared gluten (wheat and barley). People who have a wheat allergy, celiac disease or sensitivity to gluten and wheat should not consume the cereals with the BEST BEFORE DATE listed below due to potential adverse health effects. Nature’s Path is also removing any affected cereals from customer store shelves and warehouses.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 19:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631510.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631510.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Kingston Pharma, LLC Issues Voluntary Recall of All Lots of “DG™ Baby Gripe Water Due to Undissolved Ingredient, Citrus Flavonoid</title>
	 <description>Kingston Pharma, LLC is voluntarily recalling all lots of “DG™ Baby Gripe Water herbal supplement with organic ginger and fennel extracts” to the consumer level due to the presence of an undissolved ingredient, citrus flavonoid.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 16:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631500.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631500.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sid Wainer and Son Initiates Class 2 Recall for Jansal Valley Dukkah Due to Potential Glass Pieces</title>
	 <description>Sid Wainer and Son of New Bedford, MA is voluntarily recalling Jansal Valley brand Dukkah in 2.5oz containers because of the potential of it containing glass pieces</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 13:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631481.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631481.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Ottogi America, Inc. Expands Recall on Undeclared Egg in Products</title>
	 <description>Ottogi America, Inc. announced today it is expanding its recall to include the two items below due to a possibility of containing egg ingredient undeclared on the packages.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to eggs run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction of they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 10:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631285.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631285.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>World Waters Issues Voluntary Recall of Select WTRMLN WTR Original 12 Packs Due To The Possible Presence of Soft Plastic Pieces. Company Urges Consumers to Check Packages Prior to Consumption</title>
	 <description>World Waters, LLC is initiating a voluntary recall of certain lots of Cold Pressed Juice Watermelon WTRMLN WTR Original 12 packs due to the potential presence of soft plastic that may be loosely floating in some of the finished products</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 11:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631095.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm631095.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
