<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:35:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Ladyfingers Gourmet to Go Voluntarily Recalls Signature Shaved Country Ham Rolls Due to Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Ladyfingers Caterers is voluntarily recalling its Signature Shaved Country Ham Rolls as a result of the Johnston County Hams recall. The rolls were made with ham produced by Johnston County Hams, which recently initiated a recall of its ham products due to possible contamination with Listeria monocytogenes. Listeria monocytogenes can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:35:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622719.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622719.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Consumer Alert: Sprout Creek Farm “Margie” Cheese Batch Recalled</title>
	 <description>Today the New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets alerted consumers to a pasteurization problem with one of Sprout Creek Farm&#39;s pasteurized cow&#39;s milk cheeses, &quot;Margie,&quot; made on 8/28/2018. Sprout Creek Farm is located in Poughkeepsie, NY.

The reason for the recall is the air temperature at the start and end of the pasteurization process is required to be above 150deg F per the Grade &quot;A&quot; Pasteurized Milk Ordinance; the batch in question did not meet that standard. The recall pertains only to &quot;Margie&quot; cheese with a Made Date of 8/28/2018 and Best By date of 11/12/2018. To date, no illnesses have been reported to the Department in connection with this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 14:55:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622705.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622705.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Callie&#39;s Charleston Biscuits Issues Voluntary Product Recall for Country Ham Biscuits and Cocktail Ham Biscuits Produced Using Johnston County Hams</title>
	 <description>Johnston County Hams, Inc. issued a voluntary recall on October 3, 2018 for approximately 89,096 pounds of ready-to-eat ham products due to possible contamination with Listeria monocytogenes. In response, Callie&#39;s Charleston Biscuits, LLC is issuing a voluntary product recall for two products that may contain the potentially affected Johnston County Hams.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 12:23:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622685.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622685.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Working Cow Homemade, Inc. Recalls Product Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Working Cow Homemade Ice Cream, Inc. of St. Petersburg, FL is conducting a voluntary recall of No Sugar Added Vanilla and No Sugar Added Chocolate ice cream manufactured in three-gallon tubs during the month of May 2018. The recall is being conducted due to a potential contamination with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria monocytogenes infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 12:19:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622688.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622688.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Silver Star Brands, Inc. Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Human and Animal Drug Products Due to Microbial Contamination</title>
	 <description>Silver Star Brands, Inc., is initiating a voluntary recall of six products for humans (including four Native Remedies® and two Healthful Naturals™) and two PetAlive® products for pets for a total of eight products with  lot numbers, see table below, to the consumer level. The products have been tested and found to contain microbial contamination.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 11:41:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622488.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622488.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Endo Pharmaceuticals Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall for Two Lots of Robaxin® 750mg Tablets 100 Count Bottle Packs Due to Incorrect Daily Dosing Information on Label</title>
	 <description>Endo International plc (NASDAQ: ENDP) today announced that one of its operating companies, Endo Pharmaceuticals Inc., is voluntarily recalling two lots of Robaxin® (methocarbamol tablets, USP) 750mg Tablets 100 Count Bottle pack to the consumer level. The products have been found to have incorrect daily dosing information on the label due to a labeling error which misstates the daily dose as &quot;two to four tablets four times daily&quot; rather than the correct dosage of &quot;two tablets three times daily.&quot; (see picture below for location of incorrect text).</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 16:17:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622008.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622008.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Oscor Inc. Issues Recall of TB – Temporary Bipolar Pacing Lead (Unshrouded 2 mm Pins Models)</title>
	 <description>During the use of some TB - Temporary Bipolar Pacing Leads, featuring the 2mm unshrouded connectors, the connector cap housing (see Picture 1, No. 2 Pin Cap and Cover) may slide and potentially expose the connection wire. In some instances, this may cause the wire to be more susceptible to loss of connectivity or breakage during movement of the cables causing interruption of the pacing system.  The analysis of the returned devices attributed the failure to a design change of the cap housing of the pins.  In the last six years, a total of four serious injuries were reported to Oscor which were attributed to a connector cap malfunction causing the lead connector to separate during use potentially leading to an interruption of the pacing system.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 16:28:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621931.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621931.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Mauna Loa Macadamia Nut Corporation Voluntarily Recalls</title>
	 <description>Mauna Loa Macadamia Nut Corporation is
voluntarily recalling all of its products produced at the Keaau facility between Sept. 6 - 21, 2018 due to a potential contamination of Escherichia coli (E. coli). The recall was
initiated due to E. coli being detected in the well water and distribution system that
supplies the firm&#39;s operations. No illnesses related to the water have been reported to
the state.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 18:47:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621806.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621806.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Allergy Alert Issued in Whole Foods Market Stores Nationwide for Undeclared Milk in 365 Everyday Value White Corn Tortilla Chips</title>
	 <description>Whole Foods Market is voluntarily recalling 365 Everyday Value White Corn Tortilla Chips because the product may contain undeclared milk that was not listed on the product label. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 17:58:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621665.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621665.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Voluntary Recall on Harris Teeter Low Fat Cookies &amp; Cream Frozen Yogurt Due to Undeclared Peanut Product</title>
	 <description>Harris Teeter is notifying shoppers of a voluntarily recall of Harris Teeter Low Fat Frozen Yogurt Cookies &amp; Cream 1.5 qt laminated cartons, UPC 0 72036 98182 0, with all SELL BY DATES up to 07/30/19 due to undeclared peanut product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 16:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621651.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621651.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Purus Labs Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk and Soy in MyoWhey</title>
	 <description>Purus Labs, Inc of Plano, Texas is recalling MyoWhey Chocolate Cookie Crunch,
because it may contain undeclared milk and soy. This only effects products with Lot
number PL: 0100518 Exp: 04/2020. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to
milk and soy run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume
these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2018 10:37:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621293.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621293.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Getinge Issues Worldwide Voluntary Correction of Maquet/Getinge Cardiosave Intra-Aortic Balloon Pump (IABP) For Interruption and/or Inability to Start Therapy at Altitudes above 3,200 Feet/975 Meters</title>
	 <description>Getinge is voluntarily initiating a Worldwide recall involving a field correction of approximately 5,223 Maquet/Getinge Cardiosave Intra-Aortic Balloon Pumps (IABP) sold by Datascope Corp., for a potential interruption and/or inability to start therapy to the patient regarding the use of certain Intra-Aortic Balloons (IABs) prior to or during the use with Cardiosave IABP for users who are at altitudes above 3200 feet/975 meters. This condition could potentially lead to patient hemodynamic instability.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 14:11:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621203.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm621203.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Lidl Voluntarily Recalls Bellona Brand Hazelnut Wafers Due to Improperly Declared Wheat Allergen</title>
	 <description>Lidl US has voluntarily recalled all Bellona brand “Milk Chocolate Flavored Coated Wafer with Hazelnut Crème Filling and White Chocolate Flavor” confections as a precautionary measure because the allergen statement does not include wheat.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 12:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620864.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620864.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>BioLyte Laboratories Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall Due to the Voluntary Nationwide Recall initiated by King Bio Inc. (a Raw Material Supplier) for NeoRelief for Muscle Cramping and Restlessness Topical Gel Due to Possible Microbial Contamination</title>
	 <description>BioLyte Laboratories is voluntarily recalling lot numbers 1138, 1139, 1146, and 1160 of NeoRelief for Muscle Cramping and Restlessness Topical Gel to the retail and consumer level. King Bio Inc., a manufacturer of some of the active ingredients in this product, has been found to have some water contamination issues that potentially could have affected this product. King Bio has issued a recall of these active ingredients in BioLyte’s lot specific product. To date, there have been no reports of illness or injury due to the use of this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 16:16:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620481.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620481.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Bravo Packing, Inc. Recalls Performance Dog Raw Pet Food Because of Possible Salmonella Health Risk to Humans and Animals</title>
	 <description>Bravo Packing, Inc. of Carneys Point, NJ is recalling all Performance Dog products, a frozen raw pet food, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Salmonella. Salmonella can cause illness in animals eating the products, as well as people who handle contaminated pet products, especially if they have not thoroughly washed their hands after having contact with the products, infected animals or any surfaces exposed to these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 21:41:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620371.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620371.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sarap Asian Fusion Recalls Cookies due to Undeclared Allergens</title>
	 <description>Sarap Asian Fusion of Garden Grove, CA is recalling Asian Fusion Cookies due to undeclared allergens of wheat, milk and soy. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to wheat or soy run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 21:26:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620366.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620366.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Voluntary Recall Notice of Meijer Taco Seasoning Mix 4.5 oz.</title>
	 <description>McCormick &amp; Company, Inc. is initiating a voluntary recall of Meijer Taco Seasoning Mix 4.5 OZ bottle due to an unlabeled milk allergen</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 13:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620304.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620304.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Market of Choice Issues Allergy Alert for Undeclared Egg in Sesame Noodle Salad Vegan</title>
	 <description>Market of Choice, based in Eugene, Ore., is recalling its Gourmet Take Away Sesame Noodle Salad Vegan, because it contains undeclared egg. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to egg run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reactions if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 21:24:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620056.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620056.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Pharm D Solutions, LLC Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of all Sterile Compounded Drugs Due to A Potential Lack of Sterility Assurance</title>
	 <description>Pharm D Solutions, LLC is voluntarily recalling all sterile compounded drug products within expiry to the clinic, physician or consumer level. These drug products are being voluntarily recalled due to concerns that practices at the pharmacy have the potential to pose a risk of contamination to products that are intended to be sterile.  These concerns arose following a routine inspection of the pharmacy by FDA.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:29:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620054.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm620054.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Steve’s Real Food Voluntarily Recalls One Lot of Turducken Recipe, One Lot of Quest Emu, and One Lot of Quest Beef Due to Possible Salmonella and L. Mono Contamination</title>
	 <description>Steve’s Real Food of Salt Lake City, Utah is voluntarily recalling one lot of 5lb Turducken Recipe, one lot of 2lb Quest Emu Diet, and one lot of 2lb Quest Beef Diet, due to their possible Salmonella and/or L. mono contamination.</description>
	 <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 15:53:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm619888.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm619888.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
