<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Food and Drug Administration--Recalls/Safety Alerts</title>
	<description>Recall Information from FDA</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/Recalls/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 13:41:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>tina.gilliam@fda.hhs.gov</webMaster>
	<item>
	 <title>Sirob Imports, Inc. Issues Recall Due to Elevated Lead in Spices</title>
	 <description>Sirob Imports, Inc of Lindenhurst, NY is recalling, Corrado, Orlando Imports, Nouri’s Syrian Bakery, Mediterranean Specialty Foods Brand and Butera Fruit Market Curry Powder because it contains elevated levels of lead.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 13:41:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm624227.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm624227.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>G &amp; C Raw, LLC is Expanding Recall to Include All Product Lots Manufactured from February 27, 2018 Through July 20, 2018, Because of Possible Listeria Monocytogenes Health Risk</title>
	 <description>G &amp; C Raw, of Versailles, OH is recalling all products lots manufactured from February 27, 2018 through July 20, 2018, as a precaution because they have the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 10:56:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm624214.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm624214.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>New Seasons Market Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Soy in Hot &amp; Sour Broth</title>
	 <description>New Seasons Market is recalling 193 jars of New Seasons Market Hot &amp; Sour Broth because it contains undeclared soy. People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to soy run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 08:58:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm624016.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm624016.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Promise Pharmacy Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Prednisolone and Gatifloxacin Ophthalmic Solution 1%/0.5% Sterile Due to Small Particulate Floating in the Solution</title>
	 <description>Promise Pharmacy is voluntarily recalling one lot of Prednisolone and Gatifloxacin Ophthalmic Solution 1%/0.5% sterile, 3ml vials, to the patient consumer level. The product has been found to have unidentified small particulate floating in the solution.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 14:49:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623994.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623994.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Working Cow Homemade, Inc. Expands Recall of Ice Cream Products Because of Possible Health Risk</title>
	 <description>Working Cow Homemade, Inc. of St. Petersburg, FL is expanding its voluntary recall to include all ice cream manufactured from August 29, 2017 – October 11, 2018, because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.  This is an expansion of an earlier recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 14:18:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623891.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623891.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Cedar’s Mediterranean Foods Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Soy in Cedar’s Chickpea Salad 8 oz.</title>
	 <description>Cedar’s Mediterranean Foods, of Ward Hill, MA is voluntarily recalling Cedar’s Chickpea Salad 8 oz. because it may contain undeclared edamame (soy).  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to soy run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 13:20:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623834.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623834.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Hy-Vee Voluntarily Recalls Several Meat and Potato Products</title>
	 <description>Hy-Vee, Inc., based in West Des Moines, Iowa, is voluntarily recalling six of its meat and potato products across its eight-state region due to possible 
contamination with Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes. The potential for contamination was discovered after Hy-Vee’s supplier, McCain Foods, announced it was recalling its caramelized mushrooms and fire-roasted tomatoes, which are ingredients that are used in six Hy-Vee products. To 
date, no illnesses have been reported in connection with these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 22:37:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623808.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623808.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Stewart’s Shops Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Milk in Cranberry Apple Refresher</title>
	 <description>Saratoga Springs, NY - Stewart’s Shops Corp. is recalling units of Stewart’s Shops brand Cranberry Apple Refresher 16 fluid oz. because the product may contain undeclared milk. People who have an allergy to milk run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product. Approximately 2,300 units of affected product were distributed in upstate New York and Southern Vermont.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 14:17:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623762.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623762.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>P. East Trading Corp. Issues Alert on Undeclared Sulfites In Fruits Du Sud Golden Seedless Raisins</title>
	 <description>P. EAST TRADING CORP.  of Bronx, NY is recalling Fruits Du Sud Golden Seedless Raisins (Lot No. FDS T499/18) 30 lbs Box, because they contain undeclared SULFITES.  People who have a severe sensitivity to sulfites run the risk of serious or life-threatening reactions if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623694.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623694.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>SLR Food Distribution Inc. Issues Alert on Undeclared Sulfites in Sugar Melon Candy</title>
	 <description>SLR Food Distribution Inc. of New Hyde Park, NY is recalling its 7.04oz package of SUGAR MELON CANDY / WAX GOURD because it contains undeclared sulfites. Consumers who have severe sensitivity to sulfites run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reactions if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 16:02:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623682.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623682.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>New Nan Fong Hong Trading Inc. Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Sulfites in Source Day Natural Treasures Dried Liquorice Slice</title>
	 <description>New Nan Fong Hong Trading Inc. is recalling its 16 oz (454g) packages of
Source Day Natural Treasures Dried Liquorice Slice because they
contain undeclared sulfites. Consumers who are allergic to
sulfite allergens run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic
reactions if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 15:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623687.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623687.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Faribault Foods, Inc. Announces Voluntary Recall of a Limited Quantity of S&amp;W Brand White Beans Due to the Presence of Undeclared (Sulfites)</title>
	 <description>Faribault Foods, Inc. of Faribault, MN is recalling its 15 ounce S&amp;W White Beans because it contains undeclared sulfites.  People who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to sulfites run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 14:32:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623660.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623660.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Clackamas Bakery Recalls Fred Meyer Bakery Angel Food Cake Bar Due to Undeclared Allergens</title>
	 <description>Clackamas Bakery has recalled Fred Meyer Bakery Angel Food Cake Bar (12 oz.) sold in its retail stores because the product may contain milk and soy not listed on the label. Clackamas Bakery initiated the recall when it was discovered that the Fred Meyer Bakery Angel Food Cake Bar label had been incorrectly applied to packages of cornbread.</description>
	 <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:40:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623586.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623586.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Feel Good Foods Inc Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Egg Product In “Vegetable Fried Rice”</title>
	 <description>Feel Good Foods Inc. of Brooklyn, NY is recalling six lots of “Vegetable Fried Rice” frozen meals, UPC 00899039002129 because they may contain undeclared egg. People who have allergies to egg run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 21:58:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623506.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623506.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Fat Burners Zone Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Zero Xtreme Due to Presence of Undeclared Sibutramine</title>
	 <description>Fat Burners Zone is voluntarily recalling 1 lot of Zero Xtreme, capsules to the consumer level. FDA analysis  has found Zero Xtreme to be tainted with sibutramine. Sibutramine is an appetite suppressant that was withdrawn from the U.S. market due to safety concerns. The presence of Sibutramine in Zero Xtreme renders it an unapproved drug for which safety and efficacy has not been established and, therefore, subject to recall.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 18:34:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623503.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623503.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Apollo Food International Inc Issues Allergy Alert on Undeclared Eggs In “Mini Roll”</title>
	 <description>Apollo Food International Inc. of Long Island City, NY, is recalling its 2.469 ounce packages of “Mini Roll” food treats because they may contain undeclared eggs. Consumers who are allergic to eggs may run the risk of serious or life-threatening allergic reactions if they consume this product.</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 17:38:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623501.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623501.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Voluntary Recall of Limited Amounts of Nuts &amp; Vanilla Protein Plant Shake</title>
	 <description>Forager Project is recalling three dates of Nuts and Vanilla – Organic Plant Protein Shake because the product contains almond flour which is not declared on the label.</description>
	 <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 09:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623242.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623242.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Liveyon, LLC Issues a Voluntary Nationwide Recall of the Regen Series ® Product, Manufactured by Genetech, Inc.</title>
	 <description>Liveyon, LLC (“Liveyon”) is a distributor of stem cell products manufactured by Genetech, Inc. (“Genetech”), a laboratory located in San Diego, CA. Liveyon marketed and distributed these products under the trade name ReGen Series®. Liveyon has voluntarily recalled all ReGen Series® products due to reported possible adverse reactions.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 17:21:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623039.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm623039.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Voluntary Recall Issued for Sweet Me Creamery Brookie Dough Ice Cream that may Contain an Undeclared Peanut Allergen</title>
	 <description>Kemps of St. Paul, Minn., is voluntarily recalling Sweet Me Creamery Brookie Dough ice cream, individual pints and pint four-packs, because it may contain an undeclared peanut allergen. Individuals who have an allergy or severe sensitivity to peanuts run the risk of a serious or life-threatening allergic reaction if they consume these products.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 16:12:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622983.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622983.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Sprayology Issues Voluntary Nationwide Recall of Homeopathic Aqueous-Based Medicines Due to Microbial Contamination</title>
	 <description>Eight and Company LLC, d/b/a Sprayology is voluntarily recalling all lots within expiry from 10/18-7/22 of its aqueous-based homeopathic product line for human use. All products manufactured by the contract manufacturer, King Bio, have been recalled due to possible microbial contamination.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 12:25:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622919.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/Recalls/ucm622919.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
