<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

	

<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>MedWatch Safety Alert RSS Feed</title>
	<description>FDA MedWatch Safety Alerts</description>
	<link>https://www.fda.gov/AboutFDA/ContactFDA/StayInformed/RSSFeeds/MedWatch/rss.xml</link>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
 
	<webMaster>jay.wattenberg@fda.hhs.gov (Jay Wattenberg)</webMaster>
  			<image> 
  				<title>FDA MedWatch</title> 
 				<url>https://www.fda.gov/ucm/groups/fdagov-public/documents/image/ucm052224.gif</url> 
  				<link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/MedWatch/default.htm</link> 
  				<width>144</width> 
  				<height>52</height> 
  				<description>FDA MedWatch Safety Alerts</description> 
  			</image> 
	<item>
	 <title>E-cigarette: Safety Communication - Related to Seizures Reported Following E-cigarette Use, Particularly in Youth and Young Adults</title>
	 <description>The FDA has become aware that some people who use e-cigarettes have experienced seizures, with most reports involving youth or young adult users.</description>
	 <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/MedWatch/SafetyInformation/SafetyAlertsforHumanMedicalProducts/ucm635240.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/MedWatch/SafetyInformation/SafetyAlertsforHumanMedicalProducts/ucm635240.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Xeljanz, Xeljanz XR (tofacitinib): Safety Communication - Safety Trial Finds Increased Risk of Blood Clots in the Lungs and Death with Higher Dose in Rheumatoid Arthritis Patients</title>
	 <description>FDA is alerting the public that a safety clinical trial found an increased risk of blood clots in the lungs and death when a 10 mg twice daily dose of tofacitinib (Xeljanz, Xeljanz XR) was used in patients with rheumatoid arthritis (RA). FDA has not approved this 10 mg twice daily dose for RA; this dose is only approved in the dosing regimen for patients with ulcerative colitis</description>
	 <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/MedWatch/SafetyInformation/SafetyAlertsforHumanMedicalProducts/ucm632016.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/MedWatch/SafetyInformation/SafetyAlertsforHumanMedicalProducts/ucm632016.htm</guid>
	</item>
	<item>
	 <title>Fluoroquinolone Antibiotics: Safety Communication - Increased Risk of Ruptures or Tears in the Aorta Blood Vessel in Certain Patients</title>
	 <description>FDA review found that fluoroquinolone antibiotics can increase the occurrence of rare but serious events of ruptures or tears in the main artery of the body, called the aorta.  These tears, called aortic dissections, or ruptures of an aortic aneurysm can lead to dangerous bleeding or even death.  They can occur with fluoroquinolones for systemic use given by mouth or through an injection.</description>
	 <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
	 <link>https://www.fda.gov/Safety/MedWatch/SafetyInformation/SafetyAlertsforHumanMedicalProducts/ucm628960.htm</link>
	 <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fda.gov/Safety/MedWatch/SafetyInformation/SafetyAlertsforHumanMedicalProducts/ucm628960.htm</guid>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
<!-- the HEAD element is required by SiteStudio
	
	
--> 
