<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>


<title>FSIS Recalls</title>
<link>
https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/current-recalls-and-alerts
</link>
<description></description>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>FSIS.Webmaster@fsis.usda.gov (FSIS webmaster)</webMaster>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 16:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
<atom:link href="https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/wcm/connect/fsis-content/rss/recalls" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<item>
<title>Bakkavor Foods USA, Inc. Recalls Ready-To-Eat Chicken Salad Products Due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-087-2019-release</link>
<description>Bakkavor Foods USA, Inc., a San Antonio, Texas establishment, is recalling approximately 1,913 pounds of ready-to-eat (RTE) chicken salad products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 12:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4cb28ef6-5da6-40cd-acb4-8aa4b4b3ba39</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Olympia Meats Recalls Ready-To-Eat Pork Sausage Products due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-086-2019-release</link>
<description>Olympia Meats, a Portland, Ore., establishment is recalling approximately 198 pounds of ready-to-eat (RTE) pork sausage products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 16:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3b3ae255-a50a-412f-a9ec-4e75658d9ac9</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tip Top Poultry, Inc. Recalls Fully Cooked Poultry Products due to Possible Listeria Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-085-2019-release</link>
<description>Tip Top Poultry, Inc., a Rockmart, Ga. establishment, is recalling approximately 135,810 pounds of fully cooked poultry products that may be adulterated with Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">0e15f796-8b2c-4329-917b-189be208716c</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tyson Foods, Inc. Recalls Weaver Brand Ready-To-Eat Chicken Patty Products due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-084-2019-release</link>
<description>Tyson Foods Inc., a Pine Bluff, Ark. establishment, is recalling approximately 39,078 pounds of Weaver brand frozen chicken patty product that may be contaminated with extraneous materials.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 20:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">5d000542-0763-4f8c-8f0a-d79b9f6c9135</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Taylor Farms Illinois Inc. Recalls Chicken Products due to Possible Processing Defect</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-083-2019-release</link>
<description>Taylor Farms Inc., a Chicago, Ill. establishment, is recalling approximately 342 pounds of breaded chicken products due to a processing defect that may have led to undercooking of products.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 9 Aug 2019 17:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">d5fc24c6-7bbb-4873-8015-ea8f7cc60e61</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Top Taste Food Warehouse Recalls Meat and Poultry Products Produced Without Benefit of Inspection</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-082-2019-release</link>
<description>Top Taste Food Warehouse, a Brooklyn, N.Y. establishment, is recalling an undetermined amount of pork and chicken dumpling product because they were produced, packed, and distributed without the benefit of USDA inspection and used the mark of inspection without authorization.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 6 Aug 2019 19:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">df0c544d-755c-42f8-9162-de2334128f4f</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Conagra Brands, Inc. Recalls Canned Beef Products Due to Possible Processing Defect</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-081-2019-release</link>
<description></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">a5248033-71e2-4cf6-8655-1c89417189d6</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Premium Foods USA, Inc., Recalls Siluriformes Products  Produced Without Benefit of Import Inspection</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-080-2019-release</link>
<description>Premium Foods USA, Inc., a Woodside, N.Y. establishment and importer of record, is recalling approximately 76,025 pounds of various Siluriformes fish products that were not presented for import re-inspection into the United States.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 14:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">cacfa220-6541-4ac6-93d0-0015b33c8797</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Kent Quality Foods, Inc. Recalls Ready-To-Eat Sausage Products due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-079-2019-release</link>
<description>Kent Quality Foods, Inc., a Grand Rapids, Mich. establishment, is recalling approximately 48,681 pounds of ready-to-eat polish sausage with beef products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically pieces of flexible pink rubber.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 21:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">c6d9ae8a-f2f2-4a21-9ba2-3cf358a3f9e9</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Home Market Foods, Inc. Recalls Frozen Ready-To-Eat Beef and Pork Meatball Products due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-078-2019-release</link>
<description>Home Market Foods, Inc., a Norwood, Mass. establishment, is recalling approximately 53,217 pounds of frozen ready-to-eat beef and pork meatball products due to misbranding and undeclared allrgens.
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 17:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">04d6e34a-9659-4a6a-88c3-d8b0f4de4ce5</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>CM&amp;R Inc. Recalls Beef Stick Products due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-077-2019-release</link>
<description>CM&amp;R Inc., a St. Paul, Minn. establishment, is recalling approximately 25 pounds of ready-to-eat beef stick products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 17:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">d36f43d4-3229-41da-8ec3-3c38d63c18d3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>US Foods Recalls Raw Beef and Pork Products Due to Possible Product Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-076-2019-release</link>
<description>Koch Foods, a Fairfield, Ohio establishment, is recalling approximately 743 pounds of fully cooked boneless chicken bites due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2019 17:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">4961d174-1d61-4f93-b3af-052b2dc259be</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Koch Foods Recalls Breaded Poultry Products Due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-075-2019-release</link>
<description>Koch Foods, a Fairfield, Ohio establishment, is recalling approximately 743 pounds of fully cooked boneless chicken bites due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 16:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">618f8357-d6a7-4366-a3ea-48f202e30882</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fieldsource Food Systems, Inc. Recalls Beef and Poultry Products Due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-074-2019-release</link>
<description>Fieldsource Food Systems, Inc., a Brea, Calif. establishment, is recalling approximately 12,953 pounds of diced beef and chicken products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 20:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">c529a92c-cfaf-4eca-bb7a-39ba973d4302</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ada Valley Gourmet Foods, Inc. Recalls Beef Products Due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-073-2019-release</link>
<description>Ada Valley Gourmet Foods, Inc., an Ada, Mich. establishment, is recalling approximately 3,490 pounds of raw ground beef meatloaf products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically broken metal bits.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 15:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">1bfb66fb-ddaf-4845-aac9-561b73a1f832</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Fairmont Foods, Inc. Recalls Ready-To-Eat Pork and Beef Gravy Products Due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-072-2019-release</link>
<description>Fairmont Foods, Inc., a Fairmont, Minn. establishment, is recalling approximately 35,145 pounds of ready-to-eat pork and beef gravy products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically clear pliable plastic.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 9 Jul 2019 22:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">7ed51e2b-ef2f-4efa-bbeb-47f29f14d0df</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>San Giuseppe Salami Co. by Giacomo Recalls Ready-To-Eat, Frozen Andouille Sausage Products due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-071-2019-release</link>
<description>San Giuseppe Salami Co. by Giacomo, an Elon, N.C., establishment, is recalling approximately 832 pounds of ready-to-eat (RTE), frozen andouille sausage products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically metal.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 16:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">1dd80cc8-3b1b-4592-92a8-9ed0145df713</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ruiz Foods Products Inc. Recalls Bacon Breakfast Wrap Products Due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-069-2019-release</link>
<description></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">e0c71b0d-5b5c-4e2d-ad18-3c124e71e8a3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Taylor Farms Illinois, Inc. Recalls Bacon Quiche Products due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-067-2019-release</link>
<description>Taylor Farms Illinois, Inc., a Chicago, Ill. establishment, is recalling approximately 51 pounds of cheese and bacon quiche products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 9 Jun 2019 05:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">1fb6ce7d-c189-4928-bdd7-853aeaaa5835</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tyson Foods, Inc. Recalls Ready-To-Eat Chicken Fritter Products due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-066-2019-release</link>
<description>Tyson Foods, Inc., a New Holland, Pa. establishment, is recalling approximately 190,757 pounds of ready-to-eat chicken fritter products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically hard plastic.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 7 Jun 2019 16:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">c476a4cc-597c-407c-93ff-e5c9cd2c019d</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Los Hernandez Tamales, LLC Recalls Chicken and Pork Products Produced Without Benefit of Inspection</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-062-2019-release</link>
<description>Los Hernandez, LLC., a Moxee, Wash. establishment, is recalling approximately 9,090 pounds of chicken and pork tamales that were produced without the benefit of federal inspection.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 18:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">11054c3a-e591-4626-845c-56982ea7fb1f</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Perdue Foods LLC Recalls Perdue Simply Smart Organics Poultry Products Due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-064-2019-release</link>
<description>Perdue Foods LLC., a Bridgewater, Va. establishment, is recalling approximately 31,703 pounds of ready-to-eat chicken products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically pieces of bone material.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 18:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">a83826df-cd70-464b-b70b-fe87122dfd86</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Johnsonville, LLC. Recalls Ready-To-Eat Jalapeño Cheddar Smoked Sausage Links Due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-063-2019-release</link>
<description>Johnsonville, LLC., a Sheboygan Falls, Wis. establishment, is recalling approximately 95,393 pounds of its ready-to-eat jalapeño 
cheddar smoked sausage products that may be contaminated with extraneous material, specifically hard green plastic.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 15:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">bb660acb-676a-45e5-9372-3099997c55c9</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>BEF Foods, Inc. Recalls Beef Products Produced without Benefit of Inspection</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-056-2019-release</link>
<description>BEF Foods, Inc., a Lima, Ohio establishment, is recalling approximately 527 pounds of beef pasta products that were produced without the benefit of federal inspection and outside of inspection hours.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 16:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">96275984-bb64-4305-8bf9-d7c7a5679d67</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Vienna Beef Ltd. Recalls Beef Products due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-055-2019-release</link>
<description>Vienna Beef Ltd., a Chicago, Ill. establishment, is recalling approximately 2,030 pounds of beef frank links products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically metal.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 10:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">977f0b9b-7225-497c-84c2-bc2a7efef797</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Caito Foods LLC. Recalls Salads with Chicken Products due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-054-2019-release</link>
<description> Caito Foods LLC., an Indianapolis, Ind. establishment, is recalling approximately 1,767 pounds of salad with chicken products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 17:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">5278d853-c95f-441a-a8b2-a1d01fa336a8</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>MIBO Fresh Foods LLC Recalls Salad with Meat Products due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-053-2019-release</link>
<description>MIBO Fresh Foods LLC, a Fort Worth, Texas establishment, is recalling approximately 1,460 pounds of salad with meat products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 15:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">970bed0b-4fea-4775-9297-8275dfae78d7</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Crab House Trading Corp. Recalls Siluriformes Products Produced without Benefit of Inspection</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-052-2019-release</link>
<description>Crab House Trading Corp., a Los Angeles, Calif. establishment, is recalling approximately 36,040 pounds of frozen Siluriformes products, specifically yellow walking fish, that were produced without the benefit of federal inspection.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 14:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">0aac3878-62ce-47bc-83e9-d9e23dd411b3</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Conagra Brands, Inc. Recalls Chicken Pad Thai and Chicken Fried Rice Products Due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-049-2019-release</link>
<description>Conagra Brands, Inc., a Russellville, Ark. establishment, is recalling approximately 2,094,186 pounds of frozen entrees due to misbranding and an undeclared allergen.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 4 May 2019 16:20:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">1210d6b3-a27a-4b77-bcfc-a39bc146d951</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tyson Foods, Inc. Recalls Chicken Strip Products Due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-034-2019-exp-release</link>
<description>Tyson Foods, Inc., a Rogers, Ark. establishment, is recalling approximately 11,829,517 pounds of frozen, ready-to-eat chicken strip products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically pieces of metal.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 4 May 2019 00:20:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">8857d6dc-aa09-4893-abde-a1ca1c65baae</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Grant Park Packing Recalls Raw Ground Beef Products Due to Possible E. coli O103 Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-048-2019-release</link>
<description>Grant Park Packing, a Franklin Park, Ill. establishment, is recalling approximately 53,200 pounds of raw ground beef products that may be contaminated with E. coli O103.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 21:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">b2591de2-6270-4a7b-ae36-3ccc72e528eb</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>K2D Foods Recalls Raw Ground Beef Products Due to Possible E. coli O103 Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-047-2019-release</link>
<description>K2D Foods, doing business as (DBA) Colorado Premium Foods, a Carrolton, Ga. establishment, is recalling approximately 113,424 pounds of raw ground beef products that may be contaminated with E. coli O103.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 23:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">0993db30-06d5-4114-8fdf-fadd30d41607</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Yoakum Packing Co. Recalls Venison Sausage Products Due to Mislabeling</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-045-2019-release</link>
<description>Yoakum Packing Co., a Yoakum, Texas establishment, is recalling approximately 12,388 pounds of smoked venison sausage that contains pork products that were not represented on the label.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 20:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">b6971741-dea1-438b-9a5d-63beeabdc6df</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Great American Marketing Co. Recalls Meat and Poultry Wrap and Salad Products Due to Possible Listeria Monocytogenes Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-044-2019-release</link>
<description>Great American Marketing, Inc., a Houston, Texas establishment, is recalling approximately 3,329 pounds of ready-to-eat meat and poultry wrap and salad products that may be adulterated with Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 9 Apr 2019 19:29:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">49a03224-4efb-41fe-9000-ce7ec91e5f70</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>J&amp;J Snack Foods Handhelds Corp. Recalls Stuffed Sandwich Products due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-042-2019-release</link>
<description>J &amp; J Snack Foods Handhelds Corp., a Holly Ridge, N.C. establishment, is recalling approximately 56,578 pounds of stuffed sandwich products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically semi-transparent plastic.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 5 Apr 2019 19:30:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">62fce207-7760-4815-b8f1-92b44c9784a4</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Aurora Packing Company, Inc. Recalls Beef Products due to Possible E. coli O157:H7 Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-038-2019-release</link>
<description>Aurora Packing Company, Inc., a North Aurora, Ill. establishment, is recalling approximately 4,838 pounds of beef heel and chuck tender products that may be contaminated with E. coli O157:H7.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 19:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">e830ac3e-56c8-462e-a063-46cf3dcea941</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tip Top Poultry, Inc. Recalls Fully Cooked, Diced Chicken Products due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-036-2019-release</link>
<description>Tip Top Poultry, Inc., a Rockmart, Ga. establishment, is recalling approximately 100 pounds of frozen, fully cooked diced white chicken meat products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">09179449-1db3-4aa7-a73d-b7a1078bee93</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Two Brothers Pork Skins Recalls Pork Skin Products Due to Misbranding and Failure to Produce Under A HACCP Plan</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-035-2019-release</link>
<description>Two Brothers Pork Skins, a Kannapolis, N.C. establishment, is recalling an undetermined amount of pork skin products because the products were produced without meeting the federal requirements to develop and implement a hazard analysis and system of preventive controls to improve the safety of the products, known as Hazard Analysis and Critical Control Points; the omission of safe handling instructions on the package; and due to misbranding.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 15:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">0fe33530-3cc3-4b86-aed8-2255ce73fc0a</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tyson Foods, Inc. Recalls Chicken Strip Products due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-034-2019-release</link>
<description>Tyson Foods, Inc., a Rogers, Ark. establishment, is recalling approximately 69,093 pounds of frozen, ready-to-eat chicken strip products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically pieces of metal.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 15:30:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2b968cf8-585a-4fac-8443-1c2352f61c61</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>La Rosita Fresh Market Inc. Recalls Ground Beef Products due to Possible E. coli O157:H7 Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-033-2019-release</link>
<description>La Rosita Fresh Market Inc., a Mt. Prospect, Ill. retail store, is recalling approximately 54 pounds of raw ground beef products that may be contaminated with E. coli O157:H7.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:30:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">01e72d4d-eb1f-4888-ad1c-71834d0d9caa</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Procesadora La Hacienda, Inc. Recalls Beef Products Due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-032-2019-release</link>
<description>Procesadora La Hacienda, Inc., a San Lorenzo, Puerto Rico establishment, is recalling approximately 4,940 pounds of ready-to-eat (RTE) corned beef products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically pieces of metal.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 17:30:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">f83518c3-1c12-424b-83cd-6959d7aeba87</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Productos La Aguadillana, Inc. Recalls Breaded Chicken Products Due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-031-2019-release</link>
<description>Productos La Aguadillana, Inc., an Aguadilla, Puerto Rico establishment, is recalling approximately 35,870 pounds of breaded chicken patty products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically pieces of metal.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 10:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">46fddec2-f8c1-4cc2-b7cd-4311fd0f74e5</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Butterball LLC Recalls Turkey Products Due to Possible Salmonella Schwarzengrund Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-030-2019-release</link>
<description>Butterball, LLC, a Mount Olive, N.C. establishment, is recalling approximately 78,164 pounds of raw ground turkey products that may be contaminated with Salmonella Schwarzengrund.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 22:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">f58514b2-98ea-47c1-ad38-194e0b9cf885</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Monogram Meat Snacks, LLC Recalls Pork Sausage Products Due to Possible Product Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-029-2019-release</link>
<description>Monogram Meat Snacks, LLC, a Martinsville, Va. establishment, is recalling approximately 191,928 pounds of ready-to-eat pork sausage products that may be adulterated due to possible product contamination.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 21:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">ac803c01-d678-4a15-961f-4c1464d1a0a4</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bellisio Foods Recalls Boneless Pork Rib Frozen Entrée Products Due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-020-2019-release</link>
<description>Bellisio Foods, a Jackson, Ohio establishment, is recalling approximately 173,376 pounds of frozen pork entrée products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically pieces of glass or hard plastic.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 13:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">f24794e6-6782-493b-a5e0-979ba761d7eb</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>TV Food LLC. Recalls Siluriformes Products Produced Without Benefit of Inspection</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-018-2019-release</link>
<description>TV Food LLC., a San Leandro, Calif. non-federally inspected establishment, is recalling approximately 27,956 pounds of Siluriformes, specifically Yellow Hito (catfish), products because the products were not presented for import re-inspection into the United States.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 18:46:00 -0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">041fc040-1f7a-45d4-8eea-aa28fd59f27c</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Panola County Processing, LLC Recalls Sausage Products Due to Possible Processing Deviation</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-015-2019-release</link>
<description>Panola County Processing, LLC, a Carthage, Texas  establishment, is voluntarily recalling approximately 59 pounds of smoked sausage products due to a processing deviation that may have led to underprocessing of products.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 20:50:08 -0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">ca635f70-728d-44f3-9219-4b409c4c5da4</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>VICS Acquisition, LLC Recalls Chicken Products  due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-014-2019-release</link>
<description>VICS Acquisition, LLC, a Harlingen, Texas, establishment, is recalling approximately 99,975 pounds of chicken products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 11:06:08 -0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">37541977-cb02-446f-bff7-f676502c8461</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Harvest Food Group, Inc. Recalls Poultry Products Due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergen</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-007-2019-release</link>
<description>Harvest Food Group, Inc., a Chicago, Ill. establishment, is recalling approximately 47,332 pounds of Not Ready-To-Eat (NRTE) chicken fried rice products due to misbranding and an undeclared allergen.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 14:50:08 -0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">bc2372d1-3f48-4097-868a-1f2588235398</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Stino Da Napoli Recalls Various Meat Products Produced without Benefit of Inspection</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2019/recall-006-2019-release</link>
<description>Stino Da Napoli, a Rocky River, Ohio establishment, is recalling approximately 11,392 pounds of various meat products that were produced, packed and distributed without the benefit of federal inspection.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 14:13:08 -0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">cb2d1707-5283-4674-b7b9-0c2ce1afeb21</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>165368 C. Corporation Recalls Pork Products Due to Possible Listeria Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-116-2018-release</link>
<description>165368 C. Corporation, doing business as Long Phung Food Products, a Houston, Texas establishment, is recalling an undetermined amount of ready-to-eat pork products that may be adulterated with Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 22:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">027ee95b-5fd8-42b1-ac82-85d303d376f5</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ganaderos Borges, Inc. Recalls Pork Products due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-109-2018-release</link>
<description>Ganaderos Borges, Inc., a Naguabo, P.R. establishment, is recalling approximately 14,760 pounds of pork patty products that may be contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically metal.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 6 Nov 2018 19:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">0e50dd7e-4d1e-40ec-8de2-a96909bd4eba</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Red Square Foods, Inc., Recalls Frozen Not-Ready-To-Eat Meat and Poultry Products due to Misbranding and Undeclared Allergens</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-106-2018-release</link>
<description>Red Square Foods, Inc., a Somerset, N.J. establishment, is recalling an undetermined amount of various frozen meat and poultry ravioli and blintzes products due to misbranding and undeclared allergens.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 13:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">8a1c2120-7014-4372-bde0-af5f321d09ee</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Recall Notification Report 104-2018 (Smoked Whole Chicken Products)</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/rnr-104-2018</link>
<description>All People&amp;rsquo;s Food, a New Castle, Del. establishment, is recalling approximately 3,904 pounds of smoked whole chicken products due to misbranding.</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 19:30:40 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">0b001c2b-0e41-4577-9d00-fe13bd67107a</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bakkavor Foods USA, Inc. Recalls Meat and Poultry Products due to Possible Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes Contamination In Onions</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-103-2018-release</link>
<description>Bakkavor Foods USA, Inc., a firm with establishments located in Carson, Calif., Charlotte, N.C. and Jessup, Penn., is recalling approximately 795,261 pounds of ready-to-eat meat and poultry products that contain an onion ingredient that may be contaminated with Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 13:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">f55874ca-6933-40cb-b414-b8608a63095f</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>SK Food Group Recalls Chicken Products due to Possible Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes Contamination in Vegetables</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-102-2018-release</link>
<description>SK Food Group, a Groveport, Ohio and Reno, Nev. establishment, is recalling approximately 174,207 pounds of chicken wrap products that contain vegetables that may be contaminated with Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 15:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">02ab0e46-7a3f-4077-9bbb-e60a0455218b</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Caito Foods, LLC Recalls Salad And Bowl Products Made With Chicken Due To Possible Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes Contamination In Corn</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-099-2018-release</link>
<description>Caito Foods, LLC, an Indianapolis, Ind. establishment, is recalling approximately 1,532 pounds of ready-to-eat salad and bowl products made with chicken that contain a corn ingredient that may be contaminated with Salmonella and Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 15:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">65ab91ae-ae29-406d-9bf5-48ad5e028afd</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Valley Fine Foods Recalls Meat and Poultry Products due to Possible Adulteration</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-090-2018-release</link>
<description>Valley Fine Foods, a Forest City, N.C. establishment, is recalling approximately 35,516 pounds of heat-treated, not fully cooked meat and poultry products that may be adulterated due to presence of spoilage organisms that have rendered it unwholesome and unfit for human food.
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 18:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">0725db53-15f0-494e-ba68-515e3de491a7</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Ukrop&#39;s Homestyle Foods Recalls Ready-To-Eat Meat and Poultry Products Due to Possible Listeria Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-087-2018-release</link>
<description>Ukrop&amp;rsquo;s Homestyle Foods, a Richmond, Va. establishment, is recalling approximately 18,296 pounds of ready-to-eat meat and poultry deli-sliced products that may be adulterated with Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 5 Oct 2018 18:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">3c1148a9-1685-4c95-9200-5821723835c4</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Johnston County Hams Recalls Ready-To-Eat Ham Products Due to Possible Listeria Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-084-2018-release</link>
<description>Johnston County Hams, a Smithfield, N.C. establishment, is recalling approximately 89,096 pounds of ready-to-eat ham products that may be adulterated with Listeria monocytogenes.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 3 Oct 2018 17:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">092585a7-7c82-4c80-a788-f42cf0b2b455</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Bob Evans Farms Inc. Recalls Pork Sausage Link Products due to Possible Foreign Matter Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-080-2018-release</link>
<description></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">ce6cd85b-5d24-4407-a02c-7ba0f014f53f</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Caito Foods, LLC Recalls Chicken Salad Products due to Misbranding and an Undeclared Allergen</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-075-2018-release</link>
<description>Caito Foods, LLC., an Indianapolis, Ind. establishment, is recalling approximately 242 pounds of fully cooked chicken salad product due to misbranding and an undeclared allergen.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 5 Sep 2018 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">56692519-15c2-4fc4-a9ce-6eee8a9b0df9</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>Aunt Kitty&#39;s Foods Inc. Recalls Canned Chicken Products Due to Possible Processing Deviation</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-056-2018-release</link>
<description>Aunt Kitty&amp;rsquo;s Foods, Inc., a Vineland, N.J. establishment, is recalling approximately 10,805 pounds of canned chicken gravy products due to a possible processing deviation that may have led to underprocessing of products.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 13:20:40 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">02d1f418-4b8a-45ce-8a2a-bf0bd2f5b215</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>HF Food Distributors Recalls Pork Products Produced without Benefit of Inspection</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-049-2018-release</link>
<description>HF Food Distributors, a Orocovis, Puerto Rico establishment, is recalling approximately 142 pounds of sliced cooked ham products that were produced without the benefit of federal inspection.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 17:00:40 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">c0153e5d-3032-43c6-b869-558b5aec6096</guid>
</item>
<item>
<title>SMI Holdings, Inc Recalls Beef Products Due to Possible Salmonella Contamination</title>
<link>https://www.fsis.usda.gov/wps/portal/fsis/topics/recalls-and-public-health-alerts/recall-case-archive/archive/2018/recall-023-2018-release</link>
<description>SMI Holdings, Inc., doing business as Stampede Meat, Inc., a Bridgeview, Ill. establishment, is recalling approximately 484,800 pounds of beef products that may be contaminated with Salmonella.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
<guid isPermaLink="false">89d3b8cf-369d-4ba9-b8f6-5a0cf327e21f</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>