<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Vehicle Recalls</title>
    <link>http://www-odi.nhtsa.dot.gov/</link>
    <description>The Office of Defects Investigation (ODI) is an office within the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration (NHTSA). ODI conducts defect investigations and administers safety recalls to support the NHTSA&apos;s mission to improve safety on our Nation&apos;s highways. NHTSA is authorized to order manufacturers to recall and repair child_seat or items of motor vehicle equipment when ODI investigations indicate that they contain serious safety defects in their design, construction, or performance. ODI also monitors the adequacy of manufacturers&apos; recall campaigns. Before initiating an investigation, ODI carefully reviews the body of consumer complaints and other available data to determine whether a defect trend may exist.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <title>www-odi.nhtsa.dot.gov</title>
      <url>http://www-odi.nhtsa.dot.gov/images/NHTSA_Logo2.gif</url>
      <link>http://www-odi.nhtsa.dot.gov/recalls</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>PREVOST  ( 19V900000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 17, 2019 Prevost Cars, Inc. (Prevost) is recalling certain 2020 Prevost X3-45 VIP, X3-45 Passenger, H3-45 VIP, and H3-45 Passenger coach buses.  The driveshaft clamp bolts may not be properly tightened.  </description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V900000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">PREVOST  ( 19V900000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUISE CAR  ( 19V905000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 18, 2019 Cruise Car, Inc. (Cruise Car) is recalling certain 2019 Moke vehicles.  The vehicles may be equipped with a windshield of the incorrect glass quality rating.  As such, these vehicles fail to comply wi...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V905000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CRUISE CAR  ( 19V905000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THOMAS BUILT BUSES  ( 19V899000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 17, 2019 Daimler Trucks North America LLC  (DTNA) is recalling certain 2011-2021 Thomas Built Saf-T Liner HDX school buses built with a wall mounted barrier at the first rafter on the passenger side.  The forw...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V899000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">THOMAS BUILT BUSES  ( 19V899000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MERCEDES-BENZ  ( 19V892000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 16, 2019 Mercedes-Benz USA, LLC. (MBUSA) is recalling certain 2015-2018 CLA250 and CLA250 4MATIC, and 2017-2018 CLA45 AMG vehicles.  The Occupant Classification System (OCS) may have been improperly calibrated...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V892000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MERCEDES-BENZ  ( 19V892000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRSTREAM  ( 19V906000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 18, 2019 Airstream, Inc.  (Airstream) is recalling certain 2018-2019 Interstate motorhomes.  The Occupant and Cargo Carrying Capacity (OCCC) Label may indicate the incorrect occupant cargo carrying capacity, w...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V906000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">AIRSTREAM  ( 19V906000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAINTAINER  ( 19V894000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 16, 2019 Maintainer Corporation of Iowa, Inc.  (Maintainer) is recalling one 2019 Custom Bodies Heavy Rescue emergency response vehicle.  The front shocks may separate from their upper mount on the front suspe...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V894000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MAINTAINER  ( 19V894000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOREST RIVER  ( 19V901000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 18, 2019 MORryde International, Inc. (MORryde) is recalling certain 2020 Forest River Georgetown and FR3 motorhomes that they modified.  The trailer hitch bolts may have been improperly tightened, which can ca...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V901000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FOREST RIVER  ( 19V901000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLIVER TRAVEL TRAILERS  ( 19V897000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 17, 2019 Oliver Travel Trailers Inc. (Oliver) is recalling certain 2017-2019 Elite II travel trailers.  The nuts and bolts that secure the brake drum to the axle shaft flange may not have been properly tighten...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V897000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">OLIVER TRAVEL TRAILERS  ( 19V897000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAINTAINER  ( 19V898000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 18, 2019 Maintainer Corporation of Iowa, Inc. (Maintainer) is recalling certain 2015-2019 Custom Bodies Heavy Rescue emergency response vehicles equipped with a pneumatically-controlled automatic tire chain sy...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V898000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MAINTAINER  ( 19V898000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DYNAMAX  ( 19V902000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 18, 2019 Forest River, Inc. (Forest River) is recalling certain 2018-2020 Dynamax Isata motorhomes. The slim-rack slide out mechanisms may activate unintentionally, extending or retracting the slide room unexp...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V902000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">DYNAMAX  ( 19V902000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACK  ( 19V896000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 16, 2019 Mack Trucks, Inc. (Mack) is recalling certain 2020 Anthem (AN), Granite (GR), and Pinnacle (PI) vehicles.  The castle nuts and cotter pins used to connect the steering drag link to the pitman arm and ...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V896000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MACK  ( 19V896000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACK  ( 19V895000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 16, 2019 Mack Trucks, Inc. (Mack) is recalling certain 2019-2020 TerraPro (TE) vehicles.  The headlamps may not be properly aimed, possibly reducing the driver&apos;s visibility.  As such, these vehicles fail to co...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V895000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MACK  ( 19V895000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORETRAVEL  ( 19V893000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 16, 2019 Foretravel, Inc. (Foretravel) is recalling certain 2020 Realm and iH45 vehicles built on a Spartan chassis.  The brake relay valve may have an air flow restriction, which may result in an extended sto...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V893000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FORETRAVEL  ( 19V893000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRIPLE E  ( 19V884000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 11, 2019 Triple E Recreational Vehicles (Triple E) is recalling certain 2020 Unity U24RL trailers.  The propane tubing for the water heater may be routed too close to the tire tread possibly resulting in conta...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V884000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">TRIPLE E  ( 19V884000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAINTAINER  ( 19V890000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 12, 2019 Maintainer Corporation of Iowa, Inc. (Maintainer) is recalling one 2019 Custom Bodies Heavy Rescue emergency response vehicle.  The brake relay valve may have an air flow restriction, which may result...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V890000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">MAINTAINER  ( 19V890000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOREST RIVER  ( 19V891000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 13, 2019 Forest River, Inc. (Forest River) is recalling certain 2020 Georgetown and FR3 motorhomes.  The trailer hitch bolts may not have been properly tightened, which can allow cause the hitch to detach from...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V891000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">FOREST RIVER  ( 19V891000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAM  ( 19V887000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 12, 2019 Chrysler (FCA US LLC) is recalling certain 2019 Ram 1500 trucks.  An incorrect Tire Pressure Monitoring System (TPMS) sensor could have been installed during production causing the sensor to not displ...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V887000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">RAM  ( 19V887000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INDIAN  ( 19V882000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 11, 2019 Indian Motorcycle Company (Indian) is recalling certain 2019 Chieftain, Vintage, Roadmaster, Dark Horse, Springfield, and FTR1200 motorcycles.  A 10A circuit breaker may be defective, tripping unexpec...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V882000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">INDIAN  ( 19V882000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POLARIS  ( 19V881000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 11, 2019 Polaris Industries, Inc. (Polaris) is recalling certain 2019 Slingshot, Slingshot SL, Slingshot SLR, and Slingshot GT motorcycles.  A 10A circuit breaker may be defective, tripping unexpectedly and ca...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V881000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">POLARIS  ( 19V881000 )</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHRYSLER  ( 19V886000 )</title>
      <description>Dated: DEC 12, 2019 Chrysler (FCA US LLC) is recalling certain 2018-2019 Pacifica vehicles equipped with an 8.4 inch radio display, 360 degree surround view camera system, and seat back video screens.  A software error c...</description>
      <link>https://www.nhtsa.gov/recalls?nhtsaId=19V886000&amp;refurl=rss</link>
      <pubDate>TUE, 31 DEC 2019 06:00:00 EST</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">CHRYSLER  ( 19V886000 )</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

